<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<string_table>

	<!--
		KITS/TOOLS
	-->

	<string id="st_itm_repairkit_tier_1_name">
		<text>Basic Tools</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_basickit_name">
		<text>Basic Tools</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_basickit_descr">
		<text>A basic repair toolkit comprising various pliers, screws, adhesives, and assorted fasteners. This kit is designed for fundamental repair tasks but lacks the precision tools required for advanced maintenance. With sufficient knowledge and experience, it can be employed in the creation of enhanced equipment. The components show signs of light use.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tier I crafting toolkit\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_repairkit_tier_2_name">
		<text>Advanced Tools</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_advancedkit_name">
		<text>Advanced Tools</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_advancedkit_descr">
		<text>An advanced set of tools including small pliers, tipped tweezers, and a probe and pick set. This kit is well-suited for more intricate repair and crafting tasks. Despite its capability, the user must possess considerable skill to fully utilize its potential. The tools are in a moderately used condition.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tier II crafting toolkit\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_repairkit_tier_3_name">
		<text>Expert Tools</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_expertkit_name">
		<text>Expert Tools</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_expertkit_descr">
		<text>A professional set of high-quality tools designed for fine-tuning and detailed repair work. Contains a drill bit set, precision tweezers, soldering iron, 4mm screwdriver bits, and a multimeter. These tools are essential for advanced equipment creation and modification, demanding a high level of expertise from the user. The set shows signs of heavy use but remains functional.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tier III crafting toolkit\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_drugkit">
		<text>Drug-Making Kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_drugkit_descr">
		<text>A compact case containing plastic packages, tablets, and ampoules for drug production and management. It includes the basic components necessary for crafting medicinal and chemical solutions. The effectiveness of this kit depends on the user's medical knowledge and access to suitable materials. The kit has been lightly used, with some components nearing expiration.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] synthesis toolkit\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_ammokit">
		<text>Gunsmithing Tools</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_ammokit_descr">
		<text>A comprehensive set of gunsmithing tools, including a pin punch set, wheeler hammer, press tool, and a black powder measure kit. This kit allows for the recycling of damaged ammunition and the creation of custom rounds. To achieve optimal results, significant gunsmithing knowledge and experience are required. The tools show moderate wear and tear from extensive use.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm and munitions toolkit\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<!--
		UTILITY
	-->

	<string id="st_binocular_name">
		<text>Binoculars</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_binocular_descr">
		<text>A pair of standard issue military binoculars. The model is designed for reconnaissance missions, offering exceptional clarity and durability. The rubberized coating ensures a firm grip even in harsh weather conditions. The lenses are multi-coated to reduce glare and enhance image quality. They are built with a variable zoom functionality to allow for comfortable observation from a safe distance.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] equipment item\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] variable zoom\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_grooming">
		<text>Grooming Kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_grooming_descr">
		<text>A compact nylon travel case containing essential grooming tools. This kit includes a beard and moustache comb, facial scissors with ultra-sharp stainless steel blades, and a precision trimming tip. The scissors' design ensures precise cuts, while the comb helps maintain a neat appearance even in the rugged conditions of the Zone. While primarily for personal care, the tools can also serve as makeshift disassembling tools in a pinch.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] disassembly tool\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_bolts_pack">
		<text>Pack of Throwables</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bolts_pack_descr">
		<text>A small pack holding a selection of bolts and spent bullet casings. These items are commonly used by stalkers as a cost-effective method for navigating and triggering anomalies safely. The pack includes 20 to 30 pieces, providing ample supply for prolonged expeditions. Despite their simple design, these throwables are crucial for maintaining safety in the unpredictable environments of the Zone.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] utility item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_swiss">
		<text>Swiss Knife</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_swiss_descr">
		<text>A versatile and elegant Swiss knife, widely used for its utility and reliability. This multi-tool is equipped with a number of blades and implements that may be be used for weapon and outfit repairs. Its compact design allows for easy carrying and accessibility. The stainless steel construction ensures longevity and resistance to corrosion, making it a valuable asset in the Zone. Even though highly portable, its small size limits its effectiveness for larger scale tasks and proper workshop tools are recommended for disassembly and c crafting tasks.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] utility item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] disassembly tool\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<!--
		ARTEFACT HANDLING
	-->
	

	<string id="st_lead_box_name">
		<text>Lead-lined Metal Container</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_lead_box_descr">
		<text>The LLMC is a robust metal containment device with thick lead-lined walls and foam inserts, designed to transport anomalous formations safely within the Zone. It features a heavy, pressure-sealing lid that ensures a secure closure, preventing any radiation leakage. The lead lining is crucial as it effectively blocks all forms of radiation, safeguarding the user from potential exposure to hazardous materials. This is particularly important in the Zone where artefacts can emit harmful levels of radiation, posing serious health risks.\n \n
		Its design takes cues from similar containers used in the storage and transport of radioactive materials outside the Zone. Lead is a preferred material for radiation shielding due to its high density. It is commonly used in the construction of containers for radioactive waste and medical isotopes, ensuring that radiation is contained and does not pose a threat to handlers. However, an LLMC cannot be attached to a belt, meaning users cannot benefit from any potential positive properties of artefacts while they are stored within. \n \n
		The LLMC is an extremely common choice for basic storage and transport and provides high shielding for its weight profile. Artefacts must be removed from the container prior to use or sale.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] artefact storage container\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] shielding capability: 50+ mSv/sec\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_lead_box_half_name">
		<text>Lead-lined Metal Container (Half-filled)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_lead_box_half_descr">
		<text>The LLMC is a robust metal containment device with thick lead-lined walls and foam inserts, designed to transport anomalous formations safely within the Zone. It features a heavy, pressure-sealing lid that ensures a secure closure, preventing any radiation leakage. The lead lining is crucial as it effectively blocks all forms of radiation, safeguarding the user from potential exposure to hazardous materials. This is particularly important in the Zone where artefacts can emit harmful levels of radiation, posing serious health risks.\n \n
		Its design takes cues from similar containers used in the storage and transport of radioactive materials outside the Zone. Lead is a preferred material for radiation shielding due to its high density. It is commonly used in the construction of containers for radioactive waste and medical isotopes, ensuring that radiation is contained and does not pose a threat to handlers. However, an LLMC cannot be attached to a belt, meaning users cannot benefit from any potential positive properties of artefacts while they are stored within. \n \n
		The LLMC is an extremely common choice for basic storage and transport and provides high shielding for its weight profile. Artefacts must be removed from the container prior to use or sale.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] artefact storage container\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] shielding capability: 50+ mSv/sec\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_lead_box_closed_name">
		<text>Lead-lined Metal Container (Full)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_lead_box_closed_descr">
		<text>The LLMC is a robust metal containment device with thick lead-lined walls and foam inserts, designed to transport anomalous formations safely within the Zone. It features a heavy, pressure-sealing lid that ensures a secure closure, preventing any radiation leakage. The lead lining is crucial as it effectively blocks all forms of radiation, safeguarding the user from potential exposure to hazardous materials. This is particularly important in the Zone where artefacts can emit harmful levels of radiation, posing serious health risks.\n \n
		Its design takes cues from similar containers used in the storage and transport of radioactive materials outside the Zone. Lead is a preferred material for radiation shielding due to its high density. It is commonly used in the construction of containers for radioactive waste and medical isotopes, ensuring that radiation is contained and does not pose a threat to handlers. However, an LLMC cannot be attached to a belt, meaning users cannot benefit from any potential positive properties of artefacts while they are stored within. \n \n
		The LLMC is an extremely common choice for basic storage and transport and provides high shielding for its weight profile. Artefacts must be removed from the container prior to use or sale.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] artefact storage container\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] shielding capability: 50+ mSv/sec\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<!--
		SLEEPING
	-->

	<string id="st_itm_sleepbag_name">
		<text>Sleeping Bag</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_sleepbag_descr">
		<text>A durable sleeping bag for camping in the field. Made with a tough, water-resistant polyester shell and a soft, insulated interior lining made from synthetic fibers. The insulation provides adequate heat retention for temperatures down to -10°C, making it suitable for usual climate conditions in the exclusion zone. The drawstring hood offers additional warmth for colder conditions. The bag shows some minor signs of use on the outer layer, and the zipper may occasionally snag. \n \n
		Sleeping bags of different models are widely used to offer a more personal place of rest and may be moved between bases and hideouts. Bags do not offer protection against dangerous wildlife, radiation, or other environmental hazards. Sleeping in the open may attract predators.\n \n
		%c[d_orange]Instructions: %c[ui_gray_3]Find a safe spot to set up the sleeping bag. There should be adequate space to place the bag in its fully rolled out position. Use the beg when standing in a chosen spot to unroll it. Use the leftover compression bag to pack up the sleeping bag. Note that unpacking a sleeping bag may take some time.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] utility item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] portable camping gear\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_compression_bag">
		<text>Compression Bag</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_compression_bag_descr">
		<text>A compression bag designed to compactly store and transport sleeping bags, made from high-denier nylon with reinforced stitching. It features four adjustable straps with heavy-duty buckles to allow users to compress a sleeping bag to a fraction of its original size. To use, place the sleeping bag inside, secure the top closure, and evenly tighten each strap to remove excess air and reduce bulk. Minor abrasions on the exterior do not affect functionality.\n \n
		%c[d_orange]Instructions: %c[ui_gray_3]While standing in close proximity of a rolled out sleeping bag, use the compression bag to pack it up. The wrapped sleeping and compression bag will be picked up as one unit for easy transport. When using the sleeping bag later, you will receive the compression bag as a leftover for later use. Note that packing up a sleeping bag may take some time.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] utility item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] auxiliary transport item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_tent_name">
		<text>Camping Tent</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_tent_descr">
		<text>A Vityaz M-B2 A-frame camping tent, constructed from strong, weather-resistant polyester fabric with reinforced with fiberglass poles and a 1000D polyethylene floor for protection against rough terrain and moisture. The exterior is treated with a water-resistant coating, ensuring protection against light to moderate rainfall. The model also features inverted and taped seams to prevent leakage. Provides good ventilation through mesh windows and a zippable entrance.\n \n
		Frequent use may lead to minor issues like wear on the tent's fabric, particularly at stress points, or fraying of the guy lines. Periodic inspection and application of seam sealer is recommended and can extend the tent's life. This model provides shelter for up to two occupants. Camping tents are commonly used by operatives, researchers, and independent stalkers working predominantly outside of major bases. When used in conjunction with a sleeping bag, the tent offers a home away from Rostok to rest.\n \n
		%c[d_orange]Instructions: %c[ui_gray_3]Find a suitable outdoor location to set up the tent. The area should be flat, free of debris, and some distance away from buildings and bases. Use the tent when standing in the chosen spot to assemble it. Note that setting up a tent may take some time.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] utility item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] portable camping gear\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_tent_bag">
		<text>Camping Tent Bag</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_tent_bag_descr">
		<text>A tent duffel bag for secure and convenient transportation of camping tents. The model is made from rugged, water-resistant 900D polyester fabric for extended use and hazardous environments. The bag features a wide U-shaped opening with a heavy-duty YKK zipper to allow easy access to both the tent and accessories. Comes with reinforced carry handles and a padded shoulder strap for versatile carrying options. \n \n
		%c[d_orange]Instructions: %c[ui_gray_3]While standing in close proximity of a camping tent, use the tent bag to pack it up. The wrapped tent and tent bag will be picked up as one unit for easy transport. When using the tent later, you will receive the tent bag as a leftover for later use. Note that packing up a tent may take some time.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] utility item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] auxiliary transport item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<!--
		OTHER
	-->

	<string id="st_itm_mapkit">
		<text>Anomaly Map</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_mapkit_descr">
		<text>A large printed map of sections of the exclusion zone with markings for concentrated fields of anomalous effects. Attached to it are a number of personal notes, some printed and annotated, some written by hand. The map and some of its attached sheets have marked locations and brief descriptions.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	

</string_table>