<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<string_table>

	<!--
		ITEMS
	-->

	<string id="st_prt_i_ammo">
		<text>Ammo Parts</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_i_ammo_descr">
		<text>A collection of spare ammo parts, consisting of primers, casings, bullets, and powder charges. The primers are brass-cupped with a reliable ignition composition, ensuring consistent firing. Casings are predominantly brass, with some steel variants, showing moderate wear but still functional. The bullets range from lead-core to full metal jacket, suitable for a variety of calibers. The powder charges are securely sealed in moisture-resistant packets to prevent degradation. The pieces all have wildly varying conditions and require careful inspection before use.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_i_paper">
		<text>Paper Sheets</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_i_paper_descr">
		<text>A bundle of paper sheets, most of them torn or otherwise damaged, loosely bound together for safekeeping. The paper quality varies, with some sheets being yellowed and brittle while others remain relatively intact but stained from water damage. Some appear to have been ripped from books, magazines, and newspapers, some are higher quality poster print material. Paper scrap may be useful for various crafting applications or for making quick notes or starting fires. The paper's fragility and inconsistent quality can limit utility. In the Zone, scrap paper is a common resource valued for a number of crafting and repair tasks.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_i_textolite">
		<text>Textolite Base</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_i_textolite_descr">
		<text>A multi-layered textolite base, constructed of cotton fabric, impregnated with thermoreactive tactifying resin, with substantial structural integrity. The material consists of several thin sheets of cotton fabric bonded together under heat and pressure, resulting in a dense, durable composite. The surface shows signs of previous use, with scuffs and minor delamination at the edges, yet retains much of its original strength. Textolite's high resistance to mechanical stress and thermal stability makes it an invaluable scrap crafting material in the Zone. However, its weight and occasional brittleness under extreme conditions require careful handling during repurposing.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit repair item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_textile_patch_b">
		<text>Cloth Sheet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_textile_patch_b_descr">
		<text>A stack of cloth sheets, consisting of varying sizes and fabric types, showing signs of previous use and fraying at the edges. These sheets, predominantly cotton with occasional polyester blends, are versatile crafting materials. They can be cut and stitched to patch up clothing, providing essential durability and warmth. Their absorbent nature also makes them ideal for spreading oils and cleaning solvents, aiding in weapon maintenance and general cleanliness. Despite some wear and discoloration, these cloth sheets remain a valuable resource in the Zone, offering multiple practical applications for survival and upkeep.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit repair item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_textile_patch_m">
		<text>Textile Sheet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_textile_patch_m_descr">
		<text>A stack of military-grade textile sheets, known for their rugged durability and tactical versatility. These sheets, made from a blend of nylon and polyester, exhibit high resistance to tearing and abrasion. They are valued for their relatively low cost and are considered a staple for crafting and repair needs in the Zone. Medium-grade sewing equipment is sufficient for most applications, though advanced adhesive solutions are recommended for creating watertight or reinforced seams. Despite their robustness, careful handling is advised to maintain their integrity under prolonged use. These textile sheets are essential for constructing shelters, repairing gear, and improvising protective clothing.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit repair item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		</text>
	</string>
		
	<string id="st_textile_patch_e">
		<text>Reinforced Textile Sheet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_textile_patch_e_descr">
		<text>A thick textile patch reinforced with Kevlar padding. High-quality sewing kits and adhesives are required for application. This material offers substantial durability and protection, suitable for patching up armored vests or heavy-duty clothing. Though effective in enhancing ballistic resistance, its rigidity can reduce flexibility and comfort.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit repair item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_prt_i_capacitors">
		<text>Pack of Capacitors</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_i_capacitors_descr">
		<text>A pack of capacitors, essential for rectifying alternating current, storing electrical energy, and bypassing noise in circuits. These components are crucial for maintaining the functionality of electronic devices in the Zone. Proper handling and precise installation are necessary to avoid potential failures or electrical hazards.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_prt_i_transistors">
		<text>Box of Transistors</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_i_transistors_descr">
		<text>A box of high-quality BJT transistors capable of converting and amplifying electrical oscillations. These transistors are integral in signal processing and power management systems. Despite their small size, improper handling can lead to circuit malfunctions and reduced device reliability.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_prt_i_resistors">
		<text>Box of Resistors</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_i_resistors_descr">
		<text>A box of resistors, the most common components in electronics. They limit and direct the passage of electrical current through circuit branches, ensuring proper voltage distribution. These resistors are vital for circuit stability but require precise specification to avoid overheating or failure.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_i_copper">
		<text>Copper Wire</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_i_copper_descr">
		<text>A roll of thin strand pure copper wire, highly conductive and essential for numerous electrical applications. Copper wire can be scavenged from a number of common electronics, like disassembled radios or walkie-talkies. Its pliability and resistance to corrosion make it invaluable for repairs and makeshift electronic projects. Salvaged copper wire may be found in moderately used condition and may require some cleaning to remove oxidation and ensure optimal conductivity before it can be used in new applications.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_prt_i_wood">
		<text>Wooden Parts</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_i_wood_descr">
		<text>Assorted pieces of wide-grained, light cedar wood, known for its durability and resistance to decay. Preserved wood is a valued material in the Zone. It can be used in various crafting and repair projects. The wood's natural oils offer some protection against pests and environmental wear. The pieces often show signs of previous use, with some scratches and minor cracks.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_prt_i_scrap">
		<text>Metal Scrap</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_i_scrap_descr">
		<text>A collection of metal bits and pieces, including various grades of steel and aluminum alloys. These scraps are usually leftovers from broken equipment, offering a diverse range of potential uses in repair and construction. Despite their irregular shapes and sizes, they can be repurposed for reinforcing structures, crafting tools, or as makeshift weapon parts. Many of the pieces shows signs of rust and wear, necessitating some cleaning and reshaping before proper use.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_prt_i_fasteners">
		<text>Fasteners</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_i_fasteners_descr">
		<text>A mixed assortment of screws, washers, nuts, nails, and small metal plates, varying in type and size. Fasteners of all kinds are used for securing and assembling components in various repair and construction tasks, a vital part in maintaining the integrity of equipment and gear in the demanding conditions of the Zone. They are typically scavenged from old buildings, machinery, or torn body armor. Scavenged parts often show moderate signs of rust and deformation but are still usable with some restorative effort.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_prt_i_plastic">
		<text>Plastic Film</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_i_plastic_descr">
		<text>Low-density polyethylene film, packaged in small sheets or rolls. This thin, flexible plastic is used for a variety of purposes including isolating areas, wrapping items for protection, or creating temporary barriers. Its light weight and ease of manipulation make it a versatile material in the Zone. However, it is prone to tearing and may require careful handling and frequent replacement. May be repurposed for a number of technical and medical applications.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_i_glass">
		<text>Glass Pieces</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_i_glass_descr">
		<text>Shards of transparent, colorless glass. These pieces vary in size and thickness, typically resulting from broken containers or windows. Glass is fragile and can be dangerous when handled without proper protection. In the Zone, such shards can serve as makeshift cutting tools or reflective signals but are prone to breakage and pose a risk of injury. Handle with care, as even minor mishandling can lead to serious cuts or contamination.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_prt_i_ceramic">
		<text>Ceramic Base</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_i_ceramic_descr">
		<text>A rounded base made from high-density ceramic material. This base is often utilized for its insulating properties and resistance to heat, making it suitable for various industrial applications. Though durable, ceramic is brittle and can shatter upon impact. Within the Zone, it can be repurposed for equipment that requires a non-conductive surface. The primary drawback is its susceptibility to breakage under extreme conditions.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_prt_i_leather">
		<text>Leather Roll</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_i_leather_descr">
		<text>A tightly wound roll of cured leather. The leather is tough, flexible, and water-resistant, making it an invaluable resource for repairing gear or crafting protective coverings. It can be cut to size for various uses, such as reinforcing clothing or making custom pouches. Despite its durability, prolonged exposure to the elements in the Zone can cause it to degrade over time. Regular maintenance with oils or wax is recommended to extend its lifespan.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_prt_i_rubber">
		<text>Rubber</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_i_rubber_descr">
		<text>A piece of industrial-grade rubber. The material is valued for elasticity, water resistance, and insulating properties. It can be used in various repairs and modifications, particularly for sealing or insulating equipment. However, rubber can degrade when exposed to harsh chemicals or extreme temperatures common in the Zone. Its versatility makes it a staple in any scavenger's toolkit, though regular inspection for wear and tear is advised.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_prt_i_spring">
		<text>Spring</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_i_spring_descr">
		<text>A small spring from either the trigger assembly or inner workings of an unknown firearm. This compact, coiled metal component is vital for the proper function of many mechanical systems, providing tension and force in precision movements. Springs are common in various applications, from weapons to machinery, due to their durability and resilience. However, they can lose tension over time and require replacement. In the Zone, a reliable spring can be the difference between a functioning weapon and a fatal misfire. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_prt_i_triggermechanism">
		<text>Trigger Mechanism</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_i_triggermechanism_descr">
		<text>The trigger mechanism and assembly from an unknown firearm. This intricate part includes the trigger, sear, and associated components, crucial for the firing operation. While originally specific to a single model, the mechanism can be modified to fit a variety of weapons, demonstrating versatility in field repairs. Despite its adaptability, improper modification can lead to malfunctions, making careful fitting essential. Such a mechanism is invaluable for maintaining weapon reliability in the unpredictable conditions of the Zone. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_prt_i_pistolgrip">
		<text>Pistol Grip</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_i_pistolgrip_descr">
		<text>A pistol grip from an unknown firearm. These ergonomic handles are designed to provide a comfortable and secure hold, reducing recoil and improving accuracy. Crafted from durable materials, they can withstand harsh conditions and frequent use. Though intended for a specific model, they can be reshaped or modified to fit a wide range of weapons. In the Zone, a reliable pistol grip can enhance a shooter's performance, but improper fitting may result in discomfort or reduced control. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<!--
		RIFLES
	-->

	<!-- Barrels-->

	<string id="st_barrel_1">
		<text>18.5mm Barrel (R)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_barrel_1_descr">
		<text>Barrels from an 18.5mm double-barrel shotgun, manufactured from hardened steel with a blued finish. Each barrel measures 710mm in length and features a smooth bore with a slight constriction towards the muzzle for improved shot patterning. The twin barrels are precisely aligned, allowing for quick follow-up shots. Delivers powerful, close-range stopping power with the right type of ammunition. Commonly found in Baikal MP-27, IZh-27, and similar model shotguns.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] shotgun component (barrel)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_barrel_2">
		<text>18.5mm Barrel (R)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_barrel_2_descr">
		<text>Barrels from an 18.5mm cock double-barrel shotgun, manufactured from hardened steel with a blued finish. Each barrel measures 710mm in length and features a smooth bore with a slight constriction towards the muzzle for improved shot patterning. The twin barrels are precisely aligned, allowing for quick follow-up shots. Delivers powerful, close-range stopping power with the right type of ammunition. Commonly found in Baikal MP-27, IZh-27, and similar model shotguns.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] shotgun component (barrel)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_barrel_3">
		<text>18.5mm Barrel (K)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_barrel_3_descr">
		<text>Barrel from an 18.5mm smooth-bore rifle, manufactured from hardened steel with a blued finish. Each barrel measures 710mm in length and features a smooth bore with a slight constriction towards the muzzle for improved shot patterning. The twin barrels are precisely aligned, allowing for quick follow-up shots. Delivers powerful, close-range stopping power with the right type of ammunition. Commonly found in Baikal MP-27, IZh-27, and similar model shotguns.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] rifle component (barrel)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_barrel_4">
		<text>7.62mm Barrel (V)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_barrel_4_descr">
		<text>Barrel from a 7.62mm rifle, precision-manufactured from chrome-molybdenum steel. Measuring 520mm in length, it features a 1:10 twist rate for optimal bullet stabilization and accuracy. The interior is chrome-lined to enhance durability and resist corrosion, while the exterior is finished with a phosphate coating for additional protection. Designed for robust performance, this barrel ensures reliable operation and consistent accuracy in various conditions. Commonly found in AK-47, SVD Dragunov, and similar model rifles.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] rifle component (barrel)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_barrel_5">
		<text>7.92mm Barrel (V)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_barrel_5_descr">
		<text>Barrel from a 7.92mm rifle, manufactured from cold hammer-forged steel. With a length of 600mm and a 1:9.5 twist rate, it provides excellent bullet stability and accuracy. The bore is chrome-lined to resist wear and corrosion, and the exterior is treated with a manganese phosphate finish for enhanced durability. Designed for precision and reliability, this barrel is suited for consistent performance in demanding situations. Commonly found in Mauser K98k, MG42, and similar model rifles.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] rifle component (barrel)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_barrel_6">
		<text>9mm Barrel-suppressor (AS/PP)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_barrel_6_descr">
		<text>A 9mm barrel-suppressor, integrated into an automatic special-purpose rifle. Manufactured from high-grade stainless steel with a matte black finish, it measures 300mm in length. The internal suppressor features advanced baffle design to minimize muzzle flash and reduce noise signature significantly. The rifling is precision-engineered with a 1:10 twist rate to ensure optimal bullet stabilization and accuracy. This barrel-suppressor combination enhances stealth capabilities while maintaining reliable performance and durability. Commonly found in AS Val and VSS Vintorez rifles.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] rifle component (barrel)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_barrel_7">
		<text>7.62mm Barrel (A|V)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_barrel_7_descr">
		<text>A barrel from a semi-automatic or automatic 7.62mm rifle, manufactured from cold hammer-forged steel. Measuring 415mm in length, it features a 1:12 twist rate for stable and accurate projectile flight. The bore is chrome-lined for enhanced durability and corrosion resistance, while the exterior is finished with a phosphate coating for added protection. Engineered for reliability and precision, this barrel is suitable for a variety of tactical and combat applications. Commonly found in AK-47, SVD Dragunov, and similar model rifles.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] rifle component (barrel)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_barrel_8">
		<text>5.45mm Barrel (А)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_barrel_8_descr">
		<text>A barrel from an automatic 5.45mm rifle, precision-manufactured from chrome-molybdenum steel. With a length of 415mm and a 1:8 twist rate, it ensures superior bullet stabilization and accuracy. The bore is chrome-lined to enhance durability and provide resistance against corrosion, while the exterior features a phosphate coating for added protection. This barrel is designed to deliver consistent performance and reliability in diverse operational conditions. Extended wear or variable quality during manufacturing may affect overall performance. Commonly found in AK-74 and RPK-74 rifles.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] rifle component (barrel)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_barrel_9">
		<text>5.56mm Barrel (A)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_barrel_9_descr">
		<text>A barrel from an automatic 5.45mm rifle, crafted from high-strength chrome-molybdenum steel. Measuring 415mm in length, it features a 1:8 twist rate for optimal bullet stabilization and accuracy. The bore is chrome-lined to resist wear and corrosion, and the exterior is coated with a protective phosphate finish. Designed for consistent performance and durability, this barrel ensures reliable operation in a variety of conditions. Extended wear or variable quality during manufacturing may affect overall performance. Commonly found in M16, HK416, and similar model rifles.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] rifle component (barrel)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_barrel_10">
		<text>7.62mm Barrel (P)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_barrel_10_descr">
		<text>A barrel from a 7.62mm rifle with an integrated gas regulator, constructed from chrome-molybdenum steel. Measuring 520mm in length, it features a 1:10 twist rate for precise bullet stabilization. The chrome-lined bore enhances durability and corrosion resistance, while the phosphate-coated exterior provides additional protection. The gas regulator allows for adjustable gas flow, optimizing the rifle’s performance under various conditions and ammunition types. Engineered for reliability and versatility, this barrel ensures consistent accuracy and operational efficiency. Commonly found in FN FAL, HK G3, and similar model rifles.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] rifle component (barrel)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_barrel_11">
		<text>9mm Barrel (AS/PP)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_barrel_11_descr">
		<text>A barrel from an automatic special-purpose 9mm rifle, constructed from high-strength stainless steel. Measuring 254mm in length, it features a 1:10 twist rate for optimal bullet stabilization and accuracy. The bore is precision-crafted and chrome-lined to resist wear and corrosion, while the exterior is treated with a matte black nitride finish for enhanced durability. Designed for reliable performance in various tactical scenarios, this barrel ensures consistent accuracy and effective operation. Commonly found in SIG MPX and CZ Scorpion Evo 3 rifles.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] rifle component (barrel)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_barrel_12">
		<text>7.62mm Barrel (PP)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_barrel_12_descr">
		<text>A barrel from the legendary PPSh submachine gun system, manufactured from hardened steel. Measuring 269mm in length, it features a smooth bore with a 1:10 twist rate for effective bullet stabilization. The barrel’s robust construction ensures durability and reliability, while the design accommodates the high rate of fire characteristic of the PPSh. Widely regarded for its performance in close-quarters combat, this barrel has played a crucial role in the historical significance of the PPSh, providing consistent accuracy and rapid fire capability. Commonly found in PPSh-41 and PPS-43 submachine guns.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] rifle component (barrel)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_barrel_13">
		<text>12.7x55mm Barrel (Barrel)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_barrel_13_descr">
		<text>A barrel from an automatic 12.7x55mm rifle, constructed from high-grade chrome-molybdenum steel. Measuring 400mm in length, it features a 1:8 twist rate for optimal stabilization of heavy, subsonic bullets. The bore is chrome-lined to enhance durability and resist corrosion, while the exterior is treated with a black nitride finish for additional protection and reduced glare. Designed for robust performance, this barrel ensures reliable operation and accuracy, suitable for high-impact, close-quarters engagements and specialized tactical applications. Commonly found in VKS Vykhlop and ShAK-12 rifles.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] rifle component (barrel)\n
		</text>
	</string>


	<!-- Trigger Mechanisms -->

	<string id="st_trigger_components_1">
		<text>Single-mode Hammer Type Trigger</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_trigger_components_1_descr">
		<text>A single-mode hammer type trigger, manufactured from high-strength steel. This trigger operates in single action mode, where pulling the trigger releases a pre-cocked hammer to strike the firing pin. It provides straightforward functionality and dependable firing control. Commonly found in Colt Single Action Army and Browning Hi-Power pistols.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] rifle component (trigger)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_trigger_components_2">
		<text>Double-mode Hammer Type Trigger</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_trigger_components_2_descr">
		<text>A double-mode hammer type trigger, manufactured from hardened steel. This mechanism supports both single and double action modes, with the trigger either cocking and releasing the hammer or just releasing it. It offers greater control over firing. Commonly found in Smith &amp; Wesson Model 10 and SIG Sauer P226 pistols.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] rifle component (trigger)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_trigger_components_3">
		<text>Triple-fire Hammer Type Trigger</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_trigger_components_3_descr">
		<text>A triple-fire hammer type trigger, manufactured from high-grade steel. This system allows for single, burst, and fully automatic firing modes by varying the hammer's operation. It provides advanced operational flexibility. Commonly found in M16 and AK-47 rifles.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] rifle component (trigger)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_trigger_components_4">
		<text>Single-fire Mode Trigger Mechanism with Firing Pin</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_trigger_components_4_descr">
		<text>A single-fire mode trigger mechanism with firing pin, manufactured from durable materials. The trigger directly activates the firing pin for single-shot operation. It ensures reliable performance with minimal maintenance. Commonly found in Ruger No. 1 and Remington 700 rifles.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] rifle component (trigger)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_trigger_components_5">
		<text>Double-fire Mode Trigger Mechanism with Firing Pin</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_trigger_components_5_descr">
		<text>A double-fire mode trigger mechanism with firing pin, manufactured from high-quality components. This system supports both single and burst fire modes, with the trigger controlling the firing pin's action. It offers selectable firing modes for different scenarios. Commonly found in HK G3 and FN FAL rifles.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] rifle component (trigger)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_trigger_components_6">
		<text>Trigger Mechanism with Hammer (R)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_trigger_components_6_descr">
		<text>A trigger mechanism with hammer for a double-barrel shotgun, manufactured from hardened steel. This mechanism uses a hammer to strike the firing pin, ensuring reliable ignition. It provides traditional hammer-fired reliability. Commonly found in Baikal MP-27 and IZh-27 shotguns.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] shotgun component (trigger)\n
		</text>
	</string>


	<!-- Breech Blocks -->

	<string id="st_bolt_carrier_1">
		<text>Sliding Bolt Carrier with Turning Bolt Lock (R)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bolt_carrier_1_descr">
		<text>A sliding bolt carrier with a turning bolt lock, produced by Eastern manufacturers. Crafted from high-strength steel, this mechanism ensures secure locking and reliable cycling. The turning bolt lock provides a robust and precise engagement with the chamber, enhancing the overall durability and performance of the firearm. Commonly found in AK-47 and SVD Dragunov rifles.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] rifle component (carrier)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_bolt_carrier_2">
		<text>Sliding Bolt Carrier with Turning Bolt Lock (R)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bolt_carrier_2_descr">
		<text>A sliding bolt carrier with a turning bolt lock, produced by Eastern manufacturers, from special automatic weapons. Manufactured from premium-grade steel, this component is designed for high-performance automatic firearms. The turning bolt lock mechanism ensures precise and secure chambering, supporting the demanding requirements of specialized military and tactical operations. Commonly found in AK-74 and AN-94 rifles.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] rifle component (carrier)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_bolt_carrier_3">
		<text>Sliding Bolt Carrier with Turning Bolt Lock (NATO)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bolt_carrier_3_descr">
		<text>A longitudinally-sliding breech block with lock turn, produced by NATO, from a standard caliber automatic rifle. Constructed from hardened steel, this breech block mechanism facilitates smooth and reliable cycling. The lock turn feature ensures secure chamber engagement, contributing to the consistent and dependable performance expected from NATO-standard rifles. Commonly found in M16 and HK416 rifles.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] rifle component (carrier)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_bolt_carrier_4">
		<text>Sliding Bolt Carrier with a Locking Bias</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bolt_carrier_4_descr">
		<text>A sliding bolt carrier with a locking bias. Engineered from durable materials, this bolt carrier features a unique locking bias mechanism that enhances the stability and security of the bolt during firing. It provides reliable operation and improved accuracy by maintaining consistent lockup with the chamber. Commonly found in FAMAS and SA80 rifles.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] rifle component (carrier)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_bolt_carrier_5">
		<text>Half-free Sliding Bolt Carrier</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bolt_carrier_5_descr">
		<text>A half-free sliding bolt carrier with a roller brake. Manufactured from robust steel, this mechanism incorporates a roller brake system to control the bolt's movement, reducing recoil and improving cycling efficiency. The half-free design balances reliability and performance, making it suitable for various automatic firearms. Commonly found in G36 and AUG rifles.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] rifle component (carrier)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_bolt_carrier_6">
		<text>Sliding Bolt Carrier with Locking Bolt</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bolt_carrier_6_descr">
		<text>A sliding bolt carrier with locking bolt. Manufactured from high-strength steel using precision machining techniques, this mechanism ensures secure locking and smooth cycling. The locking bolt provides tight engagement with the chamber, reducing wear and enhancing the firearm's reliability and longevity. Commonly found in AR-15 and FN SCAR rifles.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] rifle component (carrier)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_bolt_carrier_7">
		<text>Lever-type Bolt Carrier with Locking Wedge</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bolt_carrier_7_descr">
		<text>A lever-type bolt carrier with a locking wedge. Manufactured from durable materials and incorporating advanced machining, this mechanism features a lever-operated bolt carrier and a locking wedge for secure chamber engagement. This design minimizes recoil and ensures consistent cycling, making it suitable for high-precision applications. Commonly found in M1 Garand and SVT-40 rifles.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] rifle component (carrier)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_bolt_carrier_8">
		<text>Choke from Double-barrel Shotgun (R)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bolt_carrier_8_descr">
		<text>A choke from a double-barrel shotgun. Manufactured from high-quality steel and precision-engineered, this choke fits securely at the muzzle end to control the spread of shot. It improves accuracy and shot patterning, making it essential for hunting and sport shooting. The careful design and manufacturing process ensure a consistent and tight fit, enhancing overall performance. Commonly found in Baikal MP-27 and IZh-27 shotguns.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] shotgun component (carrier)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_bolt_carrier_9">
		<text>Choke from Double-barrel Shotgun (R)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bolt_carrier_9_descr">
		<text>A choke from a double-barrel shotgun. Manufactured from hardened steel and produced with exacting tolerances, this choke regulates the dispersion of shot to enhance accuracy and effectiveness. It is designed to fit precisely, ensuring consistent and reliable performance for shooting enthusiasts, with a focus on improving shot consistency and target acquisition. Commonly found in Baikal MP-27 and IZh-27 shotguns.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] shotgun component (carrier)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_bolt_carrier_10">
		<text>Sliding Bolt Carrier with Turning Bolt Lock (NATO)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bolt_carrier_10_descr">
		<text>A sliding bolt carrier with turning bolt lock, product of NATO member countries, for a large-caliber automatic rifle. Engineered from premium-grade steel and utilizing advanced heat treatment processes, this mechanism ensures robust locking and reliable cycling for high-caliber rounds. The turning bolt lock provides secure chamber engagement, reducing stress on components and supporting the rigorous demands of large-caliber automatic rifles. Commonly found in FN MAG and M60 machine guns.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] rifle component (carrier)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_bolt_carrier_11">
		<text>Longitudinal-a Sliding Free Bolt Carrier (PP)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bolt_carrier_11_descr">
		<text>A longitudinally sliding free bolt carrier, from a submachine gun. Manufactured from high-strength materials and designed with precision engineering, this free-floating bolt carrier mechanism ensures smooth and efficient cycling. Its design allows for rapid fire and minimal recoil, enhancing the submachine gun's reliability and control in fast-paced engagements. Commonly found in MP5 and Uzi submachine guns.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] submachine gun component (carrier)\n
		</text>
	</string>


	<!-- Breech Heads -->

	<string id="st_bolt_1">
		<text>Dropping-block Breech (R)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bolt_1_descr">
		<text>A dropping-block breech from a smooth-bore shotgun or rifle with lever locking mechanism. Manufactured from high-strength steel, the ledges of the wedge are in good condition, showing minimal wear. This breech mechanism provides reliable locking and smooth operation, enhancing the firearm's overall durability and performance. Commonly found in Winchester 1885 and Ruger No.1 rifles.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] shotgun/rifle component (breech)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_bolt_2">
		<text>Rotating Locking Head (2 Locks) (P)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bolt_2_descr">
		<text>A rotating locking head with two stops from a machine gun with a longitudinally-sliding breech block with lock turn. Constructed from hardened steel, the locking heads are in good condition with minimal signs of usage. This design ensures secure chamber engagement and reliable cycling, critical for maintaining consistent performance in automatic fire. Commonly found in PKM and RPD machine guns.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] machine gun component (breech)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_bolt_3">
		<text>Rotating Locking Head (2 Locks) (K)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bolt_3_descr">
		<text>A rotating locking head with two stops from either an automatic or semi-automatic smoothbore rifle, with a longitudinally-sliding breech block with lock turn. Manufactured with precision from durable materials, this component provides tight and reliable locking. The design enhances the firearm's operational reliability and accuracy. Commonly found in Saiga 12 and Vepr 12 shotguns.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] rifle component (breech)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_bolt_4">
		<text>Rotating Locking Head (2 Locks) (V)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bolt_4_descr">
		<text>A rotating locking head with two stops from a rifle with a longitudinally-sliding breech block with a locking bias and a longitudinally-sliding shutter with a "bolt" lock. Produced from high-grade steel, this mechanism ensures secure and stable locking. The dual-stop design minimizes wear and enhances the rifle's firing stability and accuracy. Commonly found in AK-47 and SKS rifles.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] rifle component (breech)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_bolt_5">
		<text>Rotating Locking Head (3 Locks) (V)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bolt_5_descr">
		<text>A rotating locking head with two stops from a rifle with a longitudinally-sliding breech block with lock turn. Engineered from premium materials, this locking head ensures tight chamber engagement and reliable operation. The design supports consistent performance and longevity of the rifle. Commonly found in HK G3 and FN FAL rifles.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] rifle component (breech)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_bolt_6">
		<text>Rotating Locking Head (2 Locks) (А)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bolt_6_descr">
		<text>A rotating locking head with two stops from a machine gun with a longitudinally-sliding breech block with lock turn. Constructed from robust steel, this component shows minimal signs of wear, ensuring dependable locking and smooth cycling. The design enhances the machine gun's reliability and performance in sustained fire conditions. Commonly found in PKM and RPK machine guns.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] machine gun component (breech)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_bolt_7">
		<text>Rotating Locking Head (4 Locks) (AS)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bolt_7_descr">
		<text>A rotating locking head with four locks from a special automatic rifle with a longitudinally-sliding breech block with lock turn. Manufactured from high-strength steel, this locking head provides secure and precise chamber engagement. The four-lock design enhances stability and durability, ensuring reliable performance in specialized automatic rifles. Commonly found in AS Val and VSS Vintorez rifles.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] rifle component (breech)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_bolt_8">
		<text>Rotating Locking Head (6 Locks) (A)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bolt_8_descr">
		<text>A rotating locking head with six locks from a machine gun with a longitudinally-sliding breech block with lock turn. Constructed from robust, hardened steel, this component ensures tight and secure locking. The six-lock configuration maximizes reliability and consistency, crucial for the sustained fire capabilities of machine guns. Commonly found in M60 and FN MAG machine guns.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] machine gun component (breech)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_bolt_9">
		<text>Rotating Locking Head (7 Locks) (A)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bolt_9_descr">
		<text>A rotating locking head with seven locks from a machine gun with a longitudinally-sliding breech block with lock turn. Made from premium-grade steel, this locking head offers superior chamber engagement and stability. The seven-lock design provides enhanced durability and reliable cycling, supporting high-performance operation in demanding conditions. Commonly found in PKM and NSV machine guns.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] machine gun component (breech)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_bolt_10">
		<text>Rotating Locking Head (8 Locks) (A)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bolt_10_descr">
		<text>A rotating locking head with eight locks from a machine gun with a longitudinally-sliding breech block with lock turn. Engineered from high-strength materials, this locking head ensures optimal secure locking. The eight-lock configuration delivers maximum stability and reliability, essential for maintaining consistent performance during extended automatic fire. Commonly found in M240 and M134 Minigun machine guns.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] machine gun component (breech)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_bolt_11">
		<text>Supercharger with Hammer from a Double-barrel Shotgun (R)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bolt_11_descr">
		<text>Right and left supercharger with hammer from a double-barrel shotgun. Manufactured from high-quality steel, these superchargers ensure smooth and reliable cycling. The integrated hammers provide consistent striking power, enhancing the overall performance and dependability of the firearm. Commonly found in Baikal MP-27 and IZh-27 shotguns.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] shotgun component (breech)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_bolt_12">
		<text>Hammers from a Hammer-type Double-barrel Shotgun (R)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bolt_12_descr">
		<text>Right and left hammers from the double-barrelled horizontal shotgun. Manufactured from durable steel, these hammers are precision-engineered for reliable ignition. Their robust design ensures consistent performance and longevity, critical for maintaining the functionality of the firearm. Commonly found in Baikal MP-27 and IZh-27 shotguns.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] shotgun component (breech)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_bolt_13">
		<text>Rotating Locking Head (2 Locks) (A) (NATO)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bolt_13_descr">
		<text>Rotating locking head with two stops from a large-caliber automatic rifle produced by NATO countries, with a sliding bolt carrier with turning bolt lock. Manufactured from premium-grade steel, this locking head provides secure and precise chamber engagement. The two-stop design ensures stable locking and reliable cycling, essential for the high performance of large-caliber automatic rifles. Commonly found in FN SCAR and HK417 rifles.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] rifle component (breech)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_bolt_14">
		<text>Rotating Locking Head (А/PP)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bolt_14_descr">
		<text>Rotating locking head from either the PP or an automatic rifle with a longitudinal, half-free sliding bolt carrier. Manufactured from high-strength materials, this component ensures tight chamber engagement and smooth operation. The design supports reliable performance in both personal defense weapons and automatic rifles. Commonly found in MP5 and Uzi submachine guns.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] rifle component (breech)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_bolt_15">
		<text>Drummer with Mainspring (PP)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bolt_15_descr">
		<text>Drummer with the mainspring from some domestic PP with a longitudinal sliding-free bolt carrier. Manufactured from durable steel, this drummer and mainspring assembly ensures consistent firing pin strikes. It supports the dependable cycling and performance of domestically produced personal defense weapons. Commonly found in Vityaz-SN and PP-19 Bizon submachine guns.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] submachine gun component (breech)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_bolt_16">
		<text>Drummer with Mainspring (PP) (NATO)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bolt_16_descr">
		<text>Drummer with the mainspring from some imported PP with a longitudinal, sliding-free bolt carrier. Manufactured from high-quality materials, this drummer and mainspring assembly provides reliable firing pin strikes. It enhances the performance and consistency of imported personal defense weapons. Commonly found in MP5 and UMP submachine guns.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] rifle component (breech)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_bolt_17">
		<text>Drummer with Mainspring (PP) (PPSh)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bolt_17_descr">
		<text>Drummer with the mainspring from some Soviet PP, like the PP of Shpagin's system with a longitudinal, sliding-free bolt carrier. Manufactured from robust steel, this drummer and mainspring assembly ensures reliable ignition and consistent performance. It maintains the historical reliability and functionality of Soviet-designed personal defense weapons. Commonly found in PPSh-41 and PPS-43 submachine guns.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] submachine gun component (breech)\n
		</text>
	</string>


	<!-- Gas Tubes, etc. -->

	<string id="st_gas_tube_1">
		<text>Gas Tube (K)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_gas_tube_1_descr">
		<text>Gas tube from a smoothbore carbine. Manufactured from high-strength steel, this gas tube channels propellant gases from the barrel to the action, ensuring efficient cycling of the firearm. Its precision-engineered design enhances durability and performance, making it a critical component for the reliable operation of smoothbore carbines. Commonly found in Saiga 12 and Vepr 12 carbines.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] rifle component (gas tube)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_gas_tube_2">
		<text>Handguard (R)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_gas_tube_2_descr">
		<text>Mobile handguard from a pump-action shotgun. Manufactured from durable polymer, this handguard provides a secure grip and smooth operation during reloading. It is designed to withstand the stresses of repeated use, offering enhanced control and reliability in various conditions. The mobile mechanism allows for efficient cycling of the shotgun action. Commonly found in Remington 870 and Mossberg 500 shotguns.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] shotgun component (handguard)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_gas_tube_3">
		<text>Gas Tube (V)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_gas_tube_3_descr">
		<text>Gas tube from a self-loading rifle. Manufactured from precision-engineered steel, this gas tube plays a vital role in directing propellant gases to cycle the action. It features a robust construction that ensures consistent gas regulation and reliable operation. Its design optimizes the performance of self-loading rifles, contributing to smoother firing cycles and improved durability. Commonly found in SKS and AK-47 rifles.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] rifle component (gas tube)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_gas_tube_4">
		<text>Gas Tube (AS/PP)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_gas_tube_4_descr">
		<text>Gas tube from a special automatic rifle using a 9mm calibre. Manufactured from high-grade steel, this gas tube is designed to handle the unique demands of 9mm automatic rifles. It effectively channels gases to ensure reliable cycling and reduced recoil. The robust design supports the specialized performance requirements, providing consistent and efficient operation in high-stress environments. Commonly found in AS Val and VSS Vintorez rifles.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] rifle component (gas tube)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_gas_tube_5">
		<text>Gas Tube (A/V) (R)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_gas_tube_5_descr">
		<text>Gas tube from a semi-automatic or automatic rifle of an Eastern European type. Manufactured from high-quality steel, this gas tube efficiently channels propellant gases to cycle the action. It is designed to withstand the high pressures and heat generated during firing, ensuring reliable and consistent operation in Russian-made rifles. Commonly found in AK-74 and SVD Dragunov rifles.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] rifle component (gas tube)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_gas_tube_6">
		<text>Gas Tube (A/V) (NATO)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_gas_tube_6_descr">
		<text>Gas tube from a semi-automatic or automatic rifle of a NATO type. Manufactured from premium-grade steel, this gas tube directs gases to the action to ensure smooth cycling. Its robust construction is tailored to meet NATO standards, providing durability and reliability in various conditions. Commonly found in M16 and FN FAL rifles.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] rifle component (gas tube)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_gas_tube_7">
		<text>Gas Tube (P)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_gas_tube_7_descr">
		<text>Gas tube from a machine gun. Manufactured from hardened steel, this gas tube is designed to handle the high gas pressures and volume typical of machine gun operation. It ensures efficient cycling and sustained fire capability. Commonly found in PKM and RPK machine guns.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] machine gun component (gas tube)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_gas_tube_8">
		<text>Ejector (V)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_gas_tube_8_descr">
		<text>Ejector from a rifle with a sliding bolt carrier with locking bolt. Manufactured from high-strength steel, this ejector is engineered to reliably expel spent cartridges from the chamber. It is designed to work seamlessly with the sliding bolt carrier and locking bolt mechanism, ensuring consistent and efficient ejection in high-performance rifles. Commonly found in AK-47 and SKS rifles.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] rifle component (gas tube)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_gas_tube_9">
		<text>Ejector from Over-under Double-barrel Shotgun (R)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_gas_tube_9_descr">
		<text>Ejector (extractor) from an over-under double barrel shotgun. Manufactured from durable steel, this ejector ensures smooth and reliable extraction of spent shells. It is precisely engineered to fit the over-under double barrel shotgun design, enhancing the firearm's overall performance and ease of use. Commonly found in Baikal MP-27 and IZh-27 shotguns.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] shotgun component (ejector)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_gas_tube_10">
		<text>Ejector from Over-under Double-barrel Shotgun (R)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_gas_tube_10_descr">
		<text>Ejector from an over-under double barrel shotgun. Manufactured from robust steel, this ejector is designed for reliable and efficient extraction of spent cartridges. Its precise fit and durable construction ensure consistent performance. Commonly found in Baikal MP-27 and IZh-27 shotguns.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] shotgun component (ejector)\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_gas_tube_11">
		<text>Gas Tube (PP)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_gas_tube_11_descr">
		<text>Gas tube from the MP5 submachine gun with a handle. Manufactured from high-grade steel, this gas tube is designed to handle the pressures and gas flow of the MP5 submachine gun. The integrated handle provides additional control and ease of use during operation. Commonly found in various MP5 models, like the MP5A1, MP5 MLI, or the MP5K.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] submachine gun component (gas tube)\n
		</text>
	</string>


	<!--
		PISTOLS
	-->

	<!-- Barrels -->

	<string id="st_prt_w_p_barrel_1">
		<text>9x18mm Barrel (Barrel)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_w_p_barrel_1_descr">
		<text>A 9x18mm handgun barrel, manufactured from high-strength steel. This barrel features precise rifling to ensure optimal bullet stabilization and accuracy. It is designed to handle the pressures of the 9x18mm round, providing reliable performance and durability. Commonly found in firearms such as the Makarov PM and the P-83 Wanad.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] handgun component (barrel)\n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_prt_w_p_barrel_2">
		<text>9x19mm Barrel (Barrel)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_w_p_barrel_2_descr">
		<text>A 9x19mm handgun barrel, manufactured from high-grade steel. This barrel is engineered with precision rifling to enhance accuracy and consistency. It is built to withstand the higher pressures of the 9x19mm round, ensuring reliable performance. This barrel type is widely used in pistols like the Glock 17, SIG Sauer P226, and Beretta 92FS.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] handgun component (barrel)\n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_prt_w_p_barrel_3">
		<text>.45 Barrel (Barrel)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_w_p_barrel_3_descr">
		<text>A .45 handgun barrel, manufactured from hardened steel. This barrel features deep rifling for superior bullet stabilization and accuracy. Designed to handle the substantial pressures of the .45 ACP round, it ensures reliable performance and long-term durability. Commonly used in firearms such as the Colt M1911, SIG Sauer P220, and the Heckler &amp; Koch USP45.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] handgun component (barrel)\n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_prt_w_p_barrel_4">
		<text>5.7mm Barrel (Barrel)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_w_p_barrel_4_descr">
		<text>A 5.7mm handgun barrel, manufactured from premium steel. This barrel includes precise rifling to optimize accuracy and performance. It is designed to manage the unique pressures of the 5.7x28mm round, providing consistent reliability. This barrel is typically found in pistols like the FN Five-seven and the Ruger-57.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] handgun component (barrel)\n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_prt_w_p_barrel_5">
		<text>7.62mm Barrel (Barrel)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_w_p_barrel_5_descr">
		<text>A 7.62mm handgun barrel, manufactured from high-strength steel. This barrel features meticulously engineered rifling for enhanced accuracy. It is built to handle the pressures of the 7.62mm round, ensuring dependable performance. Commonly used in firearms such as the Tokarev TT-33 and the CZ 52.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] handgun component (barrel)\n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_prt_w_p_barrel_6">
		<text>9x18mm Barrel (enclosed) (Barrel)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_w_p_barrel_6_descr">
		<text>An enclosed 9x18mm handgun barrel, manufactured from durable steel. This enclosed barrel design features precise rifling for improved accuracy and stabilization. It is optimized for the 9x18mm round, providing reliable operation within the firearm's enclosed system. Typically found in compact and concealed carry pistols like the P-64 and the P-83 Wanad.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] handgun component (barrel)\n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_prt_w_p_barrel_7">
		<text>.357 Barrel (Barrel)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_w_p_barrel_7_descr">
		<text>A .357 revolver barrel, manufactured from robust steel. This barrel is designed with deep rifling to ensure excellent bullet stabilization and accuracy. It is built to withstand the high pressures of the .357 Magnum round, providing reliable performance and durability. Commonly used in revolvers such as the Smith &amp; Wesson Model 686, Ruger GP100, and Colt Python.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] handgun component (barrel)\n</text>
	</string>

	<!-- Trigger Mechanisms -->

	<string id="st_prt_w_p_trigger_1">
		<text>Single-action Trigger Mechanism</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_w_p_trigger_1_descr">
		<text>A single-action trigger mechanism, manufactured from high-strength steel. This mechanism requires the hammer to be manually cocked before each shot, providing a lighter and more consistent trigger pull. Commonly found in firearms such as the Colt Single Action Army and Browning Hi-Power.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] handgun component (trigger)\n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_w_p_trigger_2">
		<text>Double-action Trigger Mechanism</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_w_p_trigger_2_descr">
		<text>A double-action trigger mechanism, manufactured from durable materials. This mechanism allows the trigger to both cock and release the hammer, providing a heavier but more consistent trigger pull with each shot. Commonly used in revolvers like the Smith &amp; Wesson Model 10 and semi-automatic pistols like the SIG Sauer P226.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] handgun component (trigger)\n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_w_p_trigger_3">
		<text>Double-action (DA/SA) Trigger Mechanism</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_w_p_trigger_3_descr">
		<text>A double-action (DA/SA) trigger mechanism, manufactured from high-grade steel. This mechanism offers the flexibility of both double-action and single-action modes, allowing for an initial heavy pull followed by lighter subsequent pulls. Commonly found in firearms such as the Beretta 92FS and the Heckler &amp; Koch USP.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] handgun component (trigger)\n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_w_p_trigger_4">
		<text>"MP412" Double-action Trigger Mechanism</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_w_p_trigger_4_descr">
		<text>An "MP412" double-action trigger mechanism, manufactured from robust steel. This mechanism features a double-action operation, allowing the trigger to both cock and release the hammer, ensuring a consistent trigger pull. Specifically designed for the MP412 REX revolver, enhancing its reliability and performance.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] handgun component (trigger)\n</text>
	</string>
	
	
	<!-- Recoil Spring Assemblys -->

	<string id="st_prt_w_p_spring_1">
		<text>9mm Recoil Spring Assembly (Soviet)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_w_p_spring_1_descr">
		<text>A Soviet 9mm recoil spring assembly, manufactured from high-tensile steel. This assembly is designed to absorb and mitigate the recoil forces generated during firing, ensuring smoother cycling and improved control. Commonly used in Soviet-era pistols such as the Makarov PM and Stechkin APS.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] handgun component (recoil spring)\n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_w_p_spring_2">
		<text>9mm Recoil Spring Assembly (Russian)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_w_p_spring_2_descr">
		<text>A Russian 9mm recoil spring assembly, manufactured from durable steel. This assembly effectively manages recoil, enhancing the reliability and longevity of the firearm. It is typically found in modern Russian handguns like the Yarygin PYa and the MP-443 Grach.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] handgun component (recoil spring)\n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_w_p_spring_3">
		<text>.45 Recoil Spring Assembly (Spring)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_w_p_spring_3_descr">
		<text>A .45 recoil spring assembly, manufactured from high-grade steel. This assembly is engineered to handle the substantial recoil forces of the .45 ACP round, ensuring consistent performance and reducing wear on the firearm. Commonly found in pistols such as the Colt M1911 and the SIG Sauer P220.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] handgun component (recoil spring)\n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_w_p_spring_4">
		<text>9mm Recoil Spring Assembly (Western)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_w_p_spring_4_descr">
		<text>A Western 9mm recoil spring assembly, manufactured from premium materials. This assembly is designed to efficiently manage recoil, ensuring reliable operation and longevity. It is commonly used in popular Western handguns like the Glock 19, SIG Sauer P226, and Beretta 92FS.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] handgun component (recoil spring)\n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_w_p_spring_5">
		<text>7.62mm Recoil Spring Assembly (Spring)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_w_p_spring_5_descr">
		<text>A 7.62mm recoil spring assembly, manufactured from high-strength steel. This assembly is built to handle the recoil forces of the 7.62mm round, providing smooth cycling and enhancing firearm durability. Commonly used in firearms such as the Tokarev TT-33 and the CZ 52.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] handgun component (recoil spring)\n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_w_p_spring_6">
		<text>Recoil Spring Assembly (R1 DE 6") (Spring)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_w_p_spring_6_descr">
		<text>A recoil spring assembly for the R1 DE 6", manufactured from robust materials. This assembly is designed to manage the substantial recoil generated by large caliber rounds, ensuring reliable operation and reducing wear. Specifically designed for the Desert Eagle, enhancing its performance and longevity.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] firearm component\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] handgun component (recoil spring)\n</text>
	</string>
	
	<!--
		OUTFITS
	-->

	<!-- Fabrics and Hardware -->

	<string id="st_prt_o_fabrics_1">
		<text>Cloth Sheets</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_fabrics_1_descr">
		<text>A stack of cloth sheets, made from a variety of materials like cotton, polycotton, wool, and leather. These materials provide a reasonable balance of comfort and durability. They are suitable for basic outfit work and repair tasks. Cotton and polycotton offer breathability and softness, while wool provides body heat retention. Leather enhances durability and adds protective qualities, making these sheets versatile for various practical applications.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_o_fabrics_2">
		<text>Synthetic Cloth Sheets</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_fabrics_2_descr">
		<text>A stack of synthetic cloth sheets, blended with materials such as polyester and lycra. These textiles offer versatility and durability, suitable for constructing or repairing outfits that require flexibility and resilience. Polyester adds strength and resistance to wear and tear, while lycra ensures elasticity. This combination is ideal for situations where both comfort and durability are essential.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_o_fabrics_3">
		<text>Durable Textiles</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_fabrics_3_descr">
		<text>A stack of durable textiles, made from materials such as polyester, leather, and canvas. These sheets are designed to withstand harsh environmental conditions, offering excellent durability and protection. Polyester provides strength and resistance to elements, leather offers toughness and a degree of water resistance, and canvas adds robustness. These textiles are suitable for heavy-duty repairs and reinforcement of gear.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_o_fabrics_4">
		<text>Mil-Spec Textiles</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_fabrics_4_descr">
		<text>A stack of mil-spec textiles, made from military-grade materials including rubber and ballistic nylon. These fabrics are valued for their protective qualities, low price, and high versatility. Ballistic nylon offers superior abrasion resistance and durability, while rubber provides flexibility and waterproofing. Joint protections integrated into these textiles enhance their protective capabilities, making them suitable for high-stress and tactical applications.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- Retardants / Protective Textiles -->

	<string id="st_prt_o_retardant_1">
		<text>Layered Fire Retardant Fabrics</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_retardant_1_descr">
		<text>Textiles that are more resistant to fire through chemical treatment or manufactured fireproof fibers.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_o_retardant_2">
		<text>Layered Chemical/Shock Retardant Fabrics</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_retardant_2_descr">
		<text>Textiles that are more resistant to electric shock and chemical particles through chemical treatment or manufactured fibers.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_o_retardant_3">
		<text>Grade-B RPVC Treated Fabrics</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_retardant_3_descr">
		<text>Rigid Polyvinyl Chloride (RPVC) is a non-flammable material that is resistant to weathering. RPVC can also be UV stabilized to provide higher protection against anomalous hazards.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_o_retardant_4">
		<text>Grade-A RPVC Vinyl Fabrics</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_retardant_4_descr">
		<text>Rigid Polyvinyl Chloride (RPVC) is a non-flammable material that is resistant to weathering. RPVC can also be UV stabilized to provide higher protection against anomalous hazards.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_o_retardant_5">
		<text>PVC/Rubber Coated Fabrics</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_retardant_5_descr">
		<text>A tough and durable PVC coated polyester and rubber-fiber fabric designed for use in providing protection against hazards.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_o_retardant_6">
		<text>PVC/Carbon-fiber Fabrics</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_retardant_6_descr">
		<text>A tough and durable PVC coated polyester and carbon-fiber fabric designed for use in providing protection against hazards.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_o_retardant_7">
		<text>Insulating Magnesium Grid Inserts</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_retardant_7_descr">
		<text>This magnesium grid acts as dielectric layers to protect the outfit and its wearer from powerful electric shocks and psi-waves. It can also offer protection against other hazards.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_o_retardant_8">
		<text>Insulating Reinforced Magnesium-oxide Grid</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_retardant_8_descr">
		<text>This magnesium grid acts as dielectric layers to protect the outfit and it's wearer from powerful electric shocks and psi-waves. It can also offer protection against other hazards.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_o_retardant_9">
		<text>Polymer Sheets (Mismuth-sulfate Coating)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_retardant_9_descr">
		<text>The thermal degradation behaviour of bismuth-sulfate makes it a great choice for outfits used inside the Zone as it can provide protection against environmental hazards.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_o_retardant_10">
		<text>Polymer Sheets (Barium-sulfate Coating)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_retardant_10_descr">
		<text>The thermal degradation behaviour of barium-sulfate makes it a great choice for outfits used inside the Zone as it can provide protection against environmental hazards.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_o_retardant_11">
		<text>Aluminized Layers of Retardant Fabrics</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_retardant_11_descr">
		<text>Multi-layer Aluminized fabrics are specifically designed for protective apparel and shields used in environments that pose serious fire or safety risks associated with radiant heat and chemical sources. In addition, these fabrics offer great isolation against psi-waves.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_o_retardant_12">
		<text>Aluminized Fiberglass Fabrics</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_retardant_12_descr">
		<text>Multi-layer Aluminized fiberglass fabrics are specifically designed for protective apparel and shields used in environments that pose serious shock or safety risks associated with radiant heat and chemical sources. In addition, these fabrics offer great isolation against psi-waves effects.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_o_retardant_13">
		<text>PBI-blended Fabrics</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_retardant_13_descr">
		<text>PBI-blended fabrics have been recognized and trusted in the fire service over the years as the leading high-performance protective fire resistant fabrics.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_o_retardant_14">
		<text>PBI-blended Fabrics w/ Polyester Treatment</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_retardant_14_descr">
		<text>PBI-blended fabrics have been recognized and trusted in the fire service over the years as the leading high-performance protective fire resistant fabrics.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_o_retardant_15">
		<text>Activated Carbon Cloth (ACC) Fabrics</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_retardant_15_descr">
		<text>Originally developed for use in chemical warfare suits, Activated Carbon Cloth has many relevant uses in defense, industrial, and medical applications. It considerably enhances the efficacy of both advanced and active wound dressings, along with providing great protection from radiation particles.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_o_retardant_16">
		<text>Active Charcoal-treated Non-woven Fabrics</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_retardant_16_descr">
		<text>Originally developed for use in chemical warfare suits. Activated Carbon Cloth has many relevant uses in defense, industrial, and medical applications. It considerably enhances the efficacy of both advanced and active wound dressings, along with providing great protection from radiation particles.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_o_retardant_17">
		<text>Insulating Constantan Inserts</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_retardant_17_descr">
		<text>Inserts made of constantan sheets acting as dielectric layers to protect the outfit and its wearer from electric shocks, psi-waves and radioactive materials.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_o_retardant_18">
		<text>Insulating Constantan Inserts w/ Fiberglass Coating</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_retardant_18_descr">
		<text>Inserts made of constantan sheets and fiberglass-coated fabrics acting as dielectric layers to protect the outfit and its wearer from electric shocks, psi-waves and radioactive materials.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_o_retardant_19">
		<text>Insulating Fiberglass "Polyester" Fabrics</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_retardant_19_descr">
		<text>High temperature resistant fabrics woven from "E" glass fibers and coated with a Vermiculite based film providing extended service temperatures up to 1500°F and good shock resistance up to 20Kv. In a place like the Zone, these fabrics can come in handy against anomalous hazards.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_o_retardant_20">
		<text>Insulating Fiberglass "Satin Weave" Fabrics</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_retardant_20_descr">
		<text>High temperature resistant fabrics woven from "E" glass fibers and coated with a Vermiculite based film providing extended service temperatures up to 1700°F and good shock resistance up to 25Kv. In a place like the Zone, these fabrics can come in handy against anomalous hazards.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- Ballistic Inserts -->

	<string id="st_prt_o_ballistic_1">
		<text>Kevlar K129 Plates w/ Reinforced Ceramic Inserts</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_ballistic_1_descr">
		<text>Kevlar plates are widely known for their protective capabilities, absorbing the impact of firearm projectiles with moderate ease. They constitute a lightweight alternative to heavy steel inserts. These have been reinforced with ceramic inserts.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_o_ballistic_2">
		<text>Kevlar Protera Plates w/ Reinforced Ceramic Inserts</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_ballistic_2_descr">
		<text>Kevlar plates are widely known for their protective capabilities, absorbing the impact of firearm projectiles with moderate ease. They constitute a lightweight alternative to heavy steel inserts. These have been reinforced with Protera plates.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_o_ballistic_3">
		<text>Kevlar K129 Plates w/ Polycarbonate Composite</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_ballistic_3_descr">
		<text>Kevlar plates are widely known for their protective capabilities, absorbing the impact of firearm projectiles with moderate ease. They constitute a lightweight alternative to heavy steel inserts. These have been reinforced with a polycarbonate composite.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_o_ballistic_4">
		<text>Kevlar K129 Plates w/ Carbon-fiber Composite</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_ballistic_4_descr">
		<text>Kevlar plates are widely known for their protective capabilities, absorbing the impact of firearm projectiles with moderate ease. They constitute a lightweight alternative to heavy steel inserts. These have been reinforced with a carbon-fiber composite.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_o_ballistic_5">
		<text>Kevlar AP Steel Plates</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_ballistic_5_descr">
		<text>Kevlar plates are widely known for their protective capabilities, absorbing the impact of firearm projectiles with moderate ease. They constitute a lightweight alternative to heavy steel inserts. These have been reinforced with a carbon-fiber composite.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_o_ballistic_6">
		<text>Kevlar AP Plates w/ Reinforced Titanium Composite</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_ballistic_6_descr">
		<text>Kevlar plates are widely known for their protective capabilities, absorbing the impact of firearm projectiles with moderate ease. They constitute a lightweight alternative to heavy steel inserts. These have been reinforced with additional titanium composite.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_o_ballistic_7">
		<text>Kevlar K119 Plates w/ Polycarbonate Inserts</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_ballistic_7_descr">
		<text>Kevlar plates are widely known for their protective capabilities, absorbing the impact of firearm projectiles with moderate ease. They constitute a lightweight alternative to heavy steel inserts. These have been reinforced with polycarbonate inserts.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_o_ballistic_8">
		<text>Kevlar K119 Plates w/ Carbon-fiber Inserts</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_ballistic_8_descr">
		<text>Kevlar plates are widely known for their protective capabilities, absorbing the impact of firearm projectiles with moderate ease. They constitute a lightweight alternative to heavy steel inserts. These have been reinforced with carbon-fiber inserts.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_o_ballistic_9">
		<text>Grade-B Polyethylene Plates w/ Expanded Carrier</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_ballistic_9_descr">
		<text>Polyethylene plates that provide extra protection to vital areas. These hard armor plates have proven effective against all handgun rounds and a range of rifles. These upgraded ballistic vests have become standard in military use.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_o_ballistic_10">
		<text>Grade-A Polyethylene Plates w/ Expanded Carrier</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_ballistic_10_descr">
		<text>Polyethylene plates that provide extra protection to vital areas. These hard armor plates have proven effective against all handgun rounds and a range of rifles. These upgraded ballistic vests have become standard in military use.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_o_ballistic_11">
		<text>Kevlar K119 Plates</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_ballistic_11_descr">
		<text>Kevlar plates are widely known for their protective capabilities, absorbing the impact of firearm projectiles with moderate ease. They constitute a lightweight alternative to heavy steel inserts.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_o_ballistic_12">
		<text>Reinforced Kevlar K119 Plates</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_ballistic_12_descr">
		<text>Kevlar plates are widely known for their protective capabilities, absorbing the impact of firearm projectiles with moderate ease. They constitute a lightweight alternative to heavy steel inserts. These have been further reinforced with additional Kevlar.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_o_ballistic_13">
		<text>Polyethylene Lightweight Armor Plates</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_ballistic_13_descr">
		<text>Polyethylene plates that provide extra protection to vital areas. These hard armor plates have proven effective against all handgun rounds and a range of rifles. These upgraded ballistic vests have become standard in military use.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_o_ballistic_14">
		<text>Polyethylene Armor Plates (Improvised)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_ballistic_14_descr">
		<text>Polyethylene plates that provide extra protection to vital areas. These hard armor plates have proven effective against all handgun rounds and a range of rifles. These upgraded ballistic vests have become standard in military use. These have been put together within the Zone using a variety of used and worn pieces.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_o_ballistic_15">
		<text>Carbon Nanotube Layers w/ Kevlar-49 Fabrics</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_ballistic_15_descr">
		<text>Carbon nanotubes (CNTs) have great potential as a ballistic-resistant material. The remarkable properties of CNTs makes them an ideal candidate for reinforcing polymers and other materials and is often used in applications such as bullet-proof vests. These are reinforced with Kevlar-49 fabrics.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_o_ballistic_16">
		<text>Carbon Nanotube Layers w/ Kevlar-29 Fabrics (Reinforced)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_ballistic_16_descr">
		<text>Carbon nanotubes (CNTs) have great potential as a ballistic-resistant material. The remarkable properties of CNTs makes them an ideal candidate for reinforcing polymers and other materials and is often used in applications such as bullet-proof vests. These are reinforced with Kevlar-29 fabrics.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_o_ballistic_17">
		<text>Polyethylene Fiber Layers w/ Polycarbonate Inserts</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_ballistic_17_descr">
		<text>Polyethylene plates that provide extra protection to vital areas. These hard armor plates have proven effective against all handgun rounds and a range of rifles. These upgraded ballistic vests have become standard in military use. These have been reinforced with polycarbonate inserts.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_o_ballistic_18">
		<text>Reinforced Polyethylene Fiber Layers</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_ballistic_18_descr">
		<text>Polyethylene plates that provide extra protection to vital areas. These hard armor plates have proven effective against all handgun rounds and a range of rifles. These upgraded ballistic vests have become standard in military use. These have been reinforced with polycarbonate inserts.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_o_ballistic_19">
		<text>Carbon-fiber Layers</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_ballistic_19_descr">
		<text>Carbon-fiber is light weight, flexible and is able to withstand high temperatures.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_prt_o_ballistic_20">
		<text>Reinforced Carbon-fiber Layers</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_ballistic_20_descr">
		<text>Carbon-fiber is light weight, flexible and is able to withstand high temperatures. These have been further reinforced with additional layers.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scrap item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<!-- Supportive Installations -->

	<string id="st_prt_o_support_1">
		<text>Exoskeleton Frame</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_prt_o_support_1_descr">
		<text>Mechanical frame powered by a system of electric motors, pneumatics, levers and hydraulics that give the wearer both superior protection as well as greatly increased physical strength.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] workshop item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] outfit component\n
		</text>
	</string>

</string_table>