<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<string_table>

	<!-- Headgear -->

	<string id="st_helm_exo_name">
		<text>Exoskeleton Helmet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_exo_descr">
		<text>A robust steel helmet manufactured in the same Ukrainian factories as the exoskeleton armors. It features an integrated British SF10 gas mask, widely available on surplus markets following its replacement by the General Service Respirator (GSR). The helmet offers substantial protection against ballistic impacts and shrapnel, making it suitable for high-risk operations in the Zone. Its design ensures compatibility with most exoskeleton models, providing a comprehensive defense solution.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_helm_battle">
		<text>Sphere M12 Helmet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_battle_dolg">
		<text>Duty Sphere M12 Helmet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_battle_freedom">
		<text>Freedom Sphere M12 Helmet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_battle_descr">
		<text>An aluminium/titanium helmet with a cloth exterior for camouflage. It includes pockets for additional armor inserts, enhancing its protective capabilities. This helmet is commonly used by military stalkers and Spetsnaz, often paired with PSZ-series body armor. The Sphere M12 Helmet provides excellent combat-oriented protection, making it one of the most reliable choices in the Zone.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_helm_hardhat">
		<text>Surplus Steel Helmet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_hardhat_descr">
		<text>An outdated steel army helmet with a retractable visor. It offers basic protection against ballistic threats and shrapnel. Commonly found in surplus markets, it's often used by rookie stalkers seeking affordable head protection. Despite its age, it provides a reliable option for relatively low-threat environments.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_helm_protective">
		<text>SSP-99 Screen Helmet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_protective_descr">
		<text>A high-quality helmet made by the same Defense Research Institute that produced the SSP-99 and SEVA bodysuits. It allows for complete isolation from the conditions of an anomalous environment. A closed-cycle air filtration system supplies the wearer with consistently cool, clean air. This helmet is well-suited for extended operations in highly contaminated zones.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_helm_respirator">
		<text>Refitted PBF Gas Mask Kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_respirator_freedom">
		<text>Freedom PBF Gas Mask Kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_respirator_dolg">
		<text>Duty PBF Gas Mask Kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_respirator_descr">
		<text>A ShMB gas mask refitted with external 40mm filters for greater functionality. Generally, masks like this offer respectable protection in areas of increased radioactivity, but suffer from a high failure rate in toxic environments. This refit improves its usability but does not fully mitigate its weaknesses.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_helm_resp">
		<text>Respirator</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_resp_descr">
		<text>A basic plastic and rubber respirator, used to protect the wearer from inhaling harmful dusts, fumes, vapors, or gases. Widely used by rookies due to its light weight and economical environmental protection. However, it provides negligible physical protection and is guaranteed to fail in more heavily irradiated areas.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_helm_respirator_gp5">
		<text>GP-5 Gas Mask</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_respirator_gp5_descr">
		<text>A GP-5 gas mask, a model originally designed to protect the Soviet populace from radioactive fallout. The filters of this GP-5 have been restored with a great deal of care. Compared to gas mask kits of similar price and availability, this reconditioned device boasts greater protection against radiation but an even higher failure rate in toxic environments.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_helm_bandana">
		<text>Bandana</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_bandana_descr">
		<text>An ordinary fabric bandana worn by conscripts, support corps, and rear-echelon troops in the Military. Made from simple cotton fabric, it offers minimal protection. Stalkers will often drape it around their mouth and nose to avoid breathing in toxic or radioactive particles, but this protection is unreliable at best.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_helm_rp_bala">
		<text>Balaclava</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_rp_bala_descr">
		<text>A regular black fabric balaclava. Made from a blend of cotton and polyester, it provides basic insulation and comfort. Stalkers often use it to cover their mouth and nose to avoid breathing in toxic or radioactive particles, though this protection is unreliable at best.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_helm_cloth_mask">
		<text>Cloth Mask</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_cloth_mask_descr">
		<text>A simple piece of cloth, folded into a mask. Typically made from cotton or other breathable fabrics. Stalkers use it to cover their mouth and nose to avoid breathing in toxic or radioactive particles, but this protection is unreliable at best.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_helm_m40">
		<text>M40 Gas Mask</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_m40_descr">
		<text>An M40 model gas mask providing respectable radiation and chemical protection for extended periods. It comes equipped with a multilayered 40-millimetre breathing filter. This durable mask is a reliable choice for those frequently encountering hazardous environments.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_helm_metro">
		<text>"Apocalypse" Helmet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_metro_descr">
		<text>Believed to have been created by the faction known as "Final Day", this helmet resembles a Czech M10 Gas Mask with heavy armor plating modifications. When the faction dissolved, these helmets gradually entered into circulation. It offers a balance of respiratory and ballistic protection, favored by veteran stalkers.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_helm_tactic">
		<text>Sphere-08 Helmet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_tactic_descr">
		<text>A modern, high-quality helmet with a built-in air filtration system based on Western models. The design consists of several layers of Kevlar and composite dielectric materials. Most commonly used by the Zone's Spetsnaz operators, especially in conjunction with the PS5 body armor series. It provides excellent protection and reliability in the field.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="helm_spartan">
		<text>Cz-M10 Spartan Helmet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_spartan_descr">
		<text>A helmet commissioned by extremely influential stalkers, based on the design of the 'Apocalypse' helmet formerly used by the faction "Final Day". This helmet is lighter and more protective than its predecessor, comparing favorably to modern combat helmets such as the 'Sphere' series. It offers enhanced mobility and protection.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="helm_dolg_battle">
		<text>Duty Sphere M12</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_dolg_battle_descr">
		<text>A modified version of the standard M12 helmet, designed for use by the Duty faction. Made from aluminium and titanium alloys with a cloth exterior for camouflage. It offers enhanced ballistic protection and integrates with their tactical gear for improved performance in combat.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="helm_dolg_battle_redline">
		<text>Duty Sphere M12 "Red Line"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_dolg_battle_redline_descr">
		<text>A special edition of the Duty Sphere M12 helmet featuring reinforced armor and advanced communication systems. Constructed from high-grade aluminium and titanium, with additional protective layers. It is designed for high-risk missions, providing superior protection and situational awareness.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="helm_dolg_vintage">
		<text>PSM-4 Combat Helmet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_dolg_vintage_descr">
		<text>An older model combat helmet used by the Duty faction. Made from durable steel, it provides solid protection and is valued for its durability and reliability in combat situations.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="helm_ach7">
		<text>ACH-7 Headgear Set</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_ach7_descr">
		<text>A modern version of the surplus steel helmet, known as the ACH-7 (Advanced Compound Headgear, 7 Parts). Constructed from advanced composite materials for improved ballistic protection. Its lack of a respiratory device makes it an extremely poor choice for the Zone's conditions.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="helm_ach7ex">
		<text>ACH-7EX Headgear Set</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_ach7ex_descr">
		<text>An upgraded version of the ACH-7, including a respiratory system. Made from composite materials with integrated air filtration. The ACH-7EX boasts chemical and radiological protection somewhere between that of a GP-5 and a PBF kit, making it more suitable for Zone conditions.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="helm_eo21">
		<text>EO-21 PBFM Gas Mask</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_eo21_descr">
		<text>An EO-21 PBFM gas mask providing enhanced protection against chemical and biological threats. Made with robust rubber and plastic, it is favored by experienced stalkers for its reliability and durable construction.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="helm_dolg_eo21_red">
		<text>EO-21 PBFM Krasnyy</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_dolg_eo21_red_descr">
		<text>A specialized version of the EO-21, tailored for the Duty faction. Featuring additional protective layers and improved filtration systems. Suitable for the most hazardous areas of the Zone.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="helm_eo21sawnoff">
		<text>EO-21 PBFL Gas Mask</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_eo21sawnoff_descr">
		<text>A variant of the EO-21 designed for lightweight and flexible use. Made from rubber and plastic for ease of wear. It offers moderate protection and is ideal for quick deployment scenarios.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="helm_dolg_eo21sawnoff">
		<text>Duty EO-21 PBFL</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_dolg_eo21sawnoff_descr">
		<text>A lightweight version of the EO-21 gas mask, customized for the Duty faction. Made from flexible rubber and plastic materials. It combines mobility with adequate protection against airborne threats.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="helm_gp5">
		<text>GP-5 Gas Mask</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_gp5_descr">
		<text>A classic Soviet-era GP-5 gas mask known for its simplicity and effectiveness. Made from rubber with a built-in filter system. Restored to working condition, it offers decent protection against radiation and chemical threats.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="helm_ppm88">
		<text>PPM-88 Gas Mask</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_ppm88_descr">
		<text>A Russian gas mask well suited for CBRN (Chemical, Biological, Radiological, Nuclear) ecological hazards. Made from durable rubber and equipped with advanced filtration. In the Zone, it can be considered a functional and spiritual successor to the GP-5, offering enhanced protection and comfort for extended use.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="helm_m50">
		<text>M50z Gas Mask</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_m50_descr">
		<text>An M50 gas mask tweaked for better functionality in the Zone. Constructed from advanced polymer materials. Overall, it is considered an improvement over the M40, providing superior protection and durability.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="helm_ranger">
		<text>GP-10z Ranger Gas Mask</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_ranger_descr">
		<text>A gas mask based on the GP-10, designed primarily to protect the wearer from Controllers and Poltergeists. Made from reinforced rubber with specialized filters. It offers specialized protection against psychic threats, making it a valuable asset in the Zone.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="helm_dolg_tactic_red">
		<text>Duty Sphere 08 Krasnyy</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_dolg_tactic_red_descr">
		<text>A high-end helmet with reinforced armor and advanced filtration systems. Specifically designed for the Duty faction's elite forces. Made from multiple layers of Kevlar and composite materials, providing exceptional protection in combat.
		</text>
	</string>

	<!-- Novice outfits -->

	<string id="novice_outfit_name">
		<text>Leather Jacket</text>
	</string>
	<string id="novice_outfit_description">
		<text>A warm leather anorak worn over a turtleneck sweater, tucked into jeans and hiking boots. The outfit of choice among naive or inexperienced stalkers. An inadequate choice for the Zone's harsh conditions.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="novice_outfit_camo_name">
		<text>Firearm Enthusiast's Jacket</text>
	</string>
	<string id="novice_outfit_camo_description">
		<text>A warm leather anorak worn over a turtleneck sweater, tucked into jeans and hiking boots. Formerly owned by a typical firearm enthusiast, it sports several advantages over an ordinary jacket, namely a camouflage pattern, higher quality material and more pockets to hold belongings. Still an inadequate choice for the Zone's harsh conditions.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="novice_outfit_tourist_name">
		<text>Tourist’s Jacket</text>
	</string>
	<string id="novice_outfit_tourist_description">
		<text>A warm leather anorak with an integrated backpack, worn over a turtleneck sweater, tucked into jeans and hiking boots. It seems the previous owner really loved hiking. The educated choice of materials and weight management system makes this more useful than most leather jackets. Still an inadequate choice for the Zone's harsh conditions.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="csky_novice_outfit_name">
		<text>Clear Sky Leather Jacket</text>
	</string>
	<string id="csky_novice_outfit_description">
		<text>A soft blue leather anorak worn over a turtleneck sweater, tucked into jeans and hiking boots. These simple suits are assembled in large quantities by Clear Sky's tailors for use within the faction. An inadequate choice for the Zone's harsh conditions.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="dolg_novice_outfit_name">
		<text>Duty Leather Jacket</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_novice_outfit_description">
		<text>A dark leather anorak worn over a turtleneck sweater, tucked into jeans and combat boots. Formerly used only as relaxed wear for off-duty Dutyers, these simple suits were never intended for use by those on active service. An inadequate choice for the Zone's harsh conditions.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="bandit_novice_outfit_name">
		<text>Black Leather Jacket</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_novice_outfit_description">
		<text>A black leather jacket commonly associated with the Zone's bandits and crooks. Mostly worn to intimidate rookies from other factions, it provides very little protection. An inadequate choice for the Zone's harsh conditions.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="bandit_novice_alt_outfit_name">
		<text>Armored Leather Jacket</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_novice_alt_outfit_description">
		<text>Jackets like this first entered circulation among Bandits thanks to Quartermaster Morgan, a corrupt supplier who formerly belonged to the Duty faction. Offers protection comparable to a standard Military service outfit. An inadequate choice for the Zone's harsh conditions.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="redline_novice_outfit_name">
		<text>Redline Leather Jacket</text>
	</string>
	<string id="redline_novice_outfit_description">
		<text>A snazzy bright red leather anorak worn over a turtleneck sweater, tucked into jeans and hiking boots. An inadequate choice for the Zone's harsh conditions.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="svoboda_novice_outfit_name">
		<text>Freedom Leather Jacket</text>
	</string>
	<string id="svoboda_novice_outfit_description">
		<text>A camouflaged leather anorak worn over a turtleneck sweater, tucked into jeans and combat boots. Such attire is typically only worn by Freedomers. An inadequate choice for the Zone's harsh conditions.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<!-- Overcoats -->

	<string id="monolith_trenchcoat_outfit_name">
		<text>Monolith Overcoat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trenchcoat_freedom_brown_outfit_name">
		<text>Heavy Freedom Overcoat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trenchcoat_dolg_brown_outfit_name">
		<text>Heavy Duty Overcoat</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="trenchcoat_outfit_name">
		<text>Overcoat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trenchcoat_outfit_description">
		<text>A long, heavy overcoat in a brown and dark beige color. The outer layer is made from a durable, water-resistant fabric that shields the wearer from rain and moisture. The interior is lined with a coarse, synthetic material that provides minimal insulation against cold weather. While the overcoat offers basic protection against rain and wind, it lacks any proper protective properties.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="trenchcoat_brown_outfit_name">
		<text>Heavy Brown Overcoat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trenchcoat_brown_outfit_description">
		<text>A long, thick overcoat worn over a butchered scientist suit. The outer layer is made from a durable, water-resistant fabric that shields the wearer from rain and moisture. The interior is lined with a coarse, synthetic material providing minimal insulation against cold weather. Although the closed-cycle system and several other features have been stripped off, the end result still compares favorably to many basic stalker suits.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="trenchcoat_green_outfit_name">
		<text>Heavy Green Overcoat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trenchcoat_green_outfit_description">
		<text>A long, thick green overcoat worn over a butchered scientist suit. The outer layer is crafted from a robust, water-resistant fabric offering protection from rain and moisture. The interior features a coarse, synthetic lining that provides minimal insulation against the cold. Despite the removal of the closed-cycle system and other features, it still compares favorably to many basic stalker suits.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="greh_trenchcoat_outfit_name">
		<text>Sin Heavy Overcoat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_trenchcoat_outfit_description">
		<text>A long, thick overcoat worn over a butchered scientist suit. The exterior is made from a sturdy, water-resistant material that repels rain and moisture. Inside, a coarse, synthetic lining offers minimal insulation against cold weather. While the closed-cycle system and several other features have been stripped off, the end result still compares favorably to many basic stalker suits. The outer shell appears to have some faded bloodstains on it.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- Exploration -->

	<string id="travel_outfit_name">
		<text>"Voyager" Stalker Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_outfit_description">
		<text>A Zone-built protective suit, designed and manufactured by local mechanics. The outer layer is made from a durable, water-resistant fabric that provides protection from the elements. The interior is lined with a breathable mesh for comfort during extended wear. This high-quality outfit is intended for extended exploration within the Zone, making it a suit of choice for many artefact and mutant hunters.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="nomad_outfit_name">
		<text>"Nomad" Stalker Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="nomad_outfit_description">
		<text>A Zone-built protective suit, designed and manufactured by local mechanics. The suit features a lightweight outer shell made from a blend of nylon and polyester for flexibility and durability. The interior is padded with high-density foam to provide comfort and slight insulation. This high-quality outfit feels exceptionally light and comfortable to wear, reflecting the craftsmanship and familiarity with the Zone's conditions.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="antirad_outfit_name">
		<text>GP-5MvC Anti-rad Bodysuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="antirad_outfit_description">
		<text>A suit developed and designed by frequent visitors of the 100 Rads and the Barkeep, who supported the project financially. Based on the Sunrise suit, it integrates a common but reliable GP-5 gas mask with lightweight oxygen tanks carried on the back. The suit itself is made from a combination of lead-lined fabric and radiation-resistant materials, offering substantial protection against radioactive environments.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="hybrid_outfit_name">
		<text>Hybrid Armored Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="hybrid_outfit_description">
		<text>A suit created by the Kiev Defense Research Institute for the purpose of guarding researchers in the Zone. Constructed with budget constraints, it features a blend of Kevlar and ceramic plate inserts for ballistic protection. The outer layer is a heavy-duty, water-resistant fabric. Despite not being officially commissioned, a few of these suits found their way into the Zone, providing decent protection for those who acquired them.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="wastelander_outfit_name">
		<text>"Wastelander" Stalker Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="wastelander_outfit_description">
		<text>A protective suit, designed and built by local mechanics. This outfit features a lightweight outer shell made from a blend of synthetic fibers for flexibility and durability. It possesses a spacious Class IIIA vest made from aramid fibers and lightweight ceramic inserts for enhanced protection. Essentially, it is a more nimble, stalker-made version of the Berill-5M suit, offering a balance of mobility and defense.
		</text>
	</string>


	<!-- CS outfits -->

	<string id="csky_light_novice_outfit_name">
		<text>CS-1 Body Armor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="csky_light_novice_outfit_description">
		<text>A light suit worn by Clear Sky's novice researchers. The outer layer is constructed from a durable, water-resistant fabric, while the interior is lined with a breathable mesh for comfort. It provides more than adequate protection from the anomalous phenomena found within the Swamps, making it ideal for beginners.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="csky_light_outfit_name">
		<text>CS-2a Body Armor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="csky_light_outfit_description">
		<text>An upgrade to the CS-1 bodysuit intended for conducting rapid search operations in areas of low risk. The suit features a lightweight composite material exterior and enhanced padding for improved mobility and comfort. This design allows for quick movement while still offering sufficient protection against minor threats.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="csky_medium_outfit_name">
		<text>CS-3a Body Armor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="csky_medium_outfit_description">
		<text>A heavier but still comfortable outfit worn by members of Clear Sky. Made with reinforced Kevlar and ceramic plate inserts, it provides more than adequate protection, especially in combat situations. The suit balances durability with comfort, ensuring wearers are well-protected without sacrificing mobility.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="csky_heavy_outfit_name">
		<text>CS-3b Body Armor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="csky_heavy_outfit_description">
		<text>A robust suit formerly issued to Clear Sky assault squads. Constructed from heavy-duty Kevlar with reinforced ceramic plating, it offers excellent protection. After the faction’s infamous failure against the NPP in 2011, this armor serves as a reminder that even an excellent protective bodysuit cannot guarantee safety on the wrong side of the perimeter.
		</text>
	</string>

	
	<!-- NBC outfits -->

	<string id="nbc_outfit_name">
		<text>Tactical Stalker Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="nbc_outfit_description">
		<text>A 'Sunrise' stalker suit with the vest switched out for a special pocketed load-bearing alternative. The suit is constructed from a combination of durable nylon and polyester with reinforced stitching for extra durability. This solid suit is ideal for scavengers on a budget, providing ample storage and decent protection.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="monolith_nbc_outfit_name">
		<text>Tactical Monolith Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_nbc_outfit_description">
		<text>A Monolith suit with the vest switched out for a special pocketed load-bearing alternative. Made from heavy-duty synthetic fibers, it offers good resistance to wear and tear. This suit is a cost-effective option for scavengers, balancing practicality and protection.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="cs_nbc_outfit_name">
		<text>CS-2t Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cs_nbc_outfit_description">
		<text>A CS-2b stalker suit with the vest switched out for a special pocketed load-bearing alternative. Crafted from high-quality, water-resistant fabric, this suit ensures durability and comfort. It’s a solid choice for scavengers on a budget, providing necessary protection and ample storage space.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="nbc_merc_outfit_name">
		<text>"Twilight" LB Tactical Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="nbc_merc_outfit_description">
		<text>A Mercenary "Twilight" suit with the vest switched out for a special pocketed load-bearing (LB) alternative. The suit features a rugged, breathable fabric designed to withstand harsh conditions. This practical suit is perfect for budget-conscious scavengers, combining utility with sufficient protection.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="nbc_freedom_outfit_name">
		<text>"Sentinel of Freedom" Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="nbc_freedom_outfit_description">
		<text>A Sentinel of Freedom suit with the vest switched out for a special pocketed load-bearing alternative. Constructed from tough, abrasion-resistant materials, it offers good protection and flexibility. This suit is a reliable option for scavengers looking for a cost-effective yet durable solution.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="nbc_dolg_outfit_name">
		<text>PS5-Mt Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="nbc_dolg_outfit_description">
		<text>A PS5-M suit with the vest switched out for a special pocketed load-bearing alternative. Made from a blend of Kevlar and reinforced fabric, it provides excellent protection and durability. This suit is ideal for scavengers on a budget, offering practical storage and reliable defense.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="bandit_nbc_outfit_name">
		<text>"Sunset" LB Tactical Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_nbc_outfit_description">
		<text>A "Sunset" bandit suit with the vest switched out for a special pocketed load-bearing (LB) alternative. The suit is constructed from high-strength synthetic materials, ensuring durability and flexibility. This budget-friendly suit is suitable for scavengers, providing essential protection and storage options.
		</text>
	</string>

	
	<!-- Assault vest -->

	<string id="light_loner_outfit_name">
		<text>Interceptor Body Armor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="light_loner_outfit_description">
		<text>An old IBA (Interceptor Body Armor) suit imported from the West and modified for the Zone's conditions. Constructed with Kevlar and ceramic plate inserts, it offers substantial ballistic protection. The modifications include additional pockets and improved ergonomics for carrying equipment essential for survival in the Zone.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="light_freedom_outfit_name">
		<text>Defender of Freedom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="light_freedom_outfit_description">
		<text>Rumored to be supplied to the Freedom faction directly from an unknown source, this suit is based on the somewhat outdated IBA system. Modified with high-strength synthetic fibers for greater comfort and mobility, it is tailored for the unique conditions of the Zone. Enhanced with modern ballistic plates, it provides reliable protection against most threats.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="light_voen_outfit_name">
		<text>Military Stalker IBAz Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="light_voen_outfit_description">
		<text>An Interceptor Anomalous Body Armor System (IBAz) that ended up in the hands of the Military. Compared to the standard model, this suit features ergonomic improvements and includes advanced materials such as Kevlar and lightweight composite plates. It also boasts greater protection against psychic interference, making it well-suited for military operations in the Zone.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="light_monolit_outfit_name">
		<text>Monolith IBAz Assault Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="light_monolit_outfit_description">
		<text>An Interceptor Anomalous Body Armor System (IBAz) that ended up in the hands of the Monolith. This suit includes ergonomic enhancements and advanced protective materials, offering superior ballistic protection with Kevlar and composite plates. Additionally, it provides improved defense against psychic interference, a useful property for Monolith operatives.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="light_dolg_outfit_name">
		<text>IBAz Universal Protection Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="light_dolg_outfit_description">
		<text>An old IBA suit imported from the West and modified for the Zone's conditions. The Duty variant is uncomfortably heavy but has received extensive upgrades, including reinforced Kevlar and ceramic armor plates for enhanced protection against ballistic and chemical threats. This suit is designed to withstand the harshest conditions encountered by Duty members.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="light_merc_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary IBAz Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="light_merc_outfit_description">
		<text>A well-kept Interceptor Anomalous Body Armor System (IBAz) sold directly to the Mercenaries from various Western sources. Constructed with high-strength Kevlar and ceramic plates, it offers superior ballistic protection. While a bit uncomfortable, this suit is overall more advanced and protective than the standard models circulating in the Zone.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="light_isg_outfit_name">
		<text>UNISG IBAz Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="light_isg_outfit_description">
		<text>A strong but somewhat outdated combat suit. Made from durable synthetic fibers and reinforced with ballistic plates, it offers reliable protection against armed threats. Considered the bare minimum of what should be worn in situations where conflict with armed SSU forces seems inevitable, providing essential defensive properties in hostile environments.
		</text>
	</string>


	<!-- Sunrise suits -->

	<string id="stalker_outfit_name">
		<text>"Sunrise" Stalker Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_outfit_description">
		<text>A Zone-built protective suit, designed and manufactured by local mechanics. The Sunrise is one of the oldest stalker suits in existence, featuring a durable nylon and polyester blend exterior with reinforced stitching for added durability. It is widely considered the bare minimum protection a stalker should have for serious trips into the Zone.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="stalker_outfit_camo_name">
		<text>"Chameleon" Stalker Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_outfit_camo_description">
		<text>A Zone-built protective suit, designed and manufactured by local mechanics. The "Chameleon" variant includes a camouflaged exterior made from a blend of high-strength synthetic fibers, providing good concealment and moderate protection. It is favored for its ability to blend into the surroundings while offering decent protection in the Zone.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="stalker_outfit_alt_name">
		<text>"Hipster" Stalker Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_outfit_alt_description">
		<text>A Zone-built protective suit, designed and manufactured by local mechanics. The "Hipster" suit features a unique design with lightweight, breathable fabrics for improved comfort and mobility. It offers basic protection and is popular among those who prioritize style and flexibility over heavy armor.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="stalker_drought_outfit_name">
		<text>"Drought" Stalker Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_drought_outfit_description">
		<text>A Zone-built protective suit, designed and manufactured by local mechanics. For a stalker suit, the "Drought" possesses above-average ballistic protection, utilizing reinforced Kevlar and ceramic plate inserts. However, it is considerably less comfortable to wear due to its heavier and more rigid construction.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="stalker_predator_outfit_name">
		<text>"Predator" Stalker Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_predator_outfit_description">
		<text>A Zone-built protective suit, designed and manufactured by local mechanics. An overall upgrade over the "Drought" suit, the "Predator" features enhanced ballistic protection with Kevlar and lightweight composite plates, and is significantly more comfortable to wear. It enjoys popularity among greenhorns and experts alike thanks to its low maintenance costs and great modification potential.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="stalker_autumn_outfit_name">
		<text>"Autumn" Stalker Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_autumn_outfit_description">
		<text>A Zone-built protective suit, designed and manufactured by local mechanics. Favored among newer artifact hunters and creative hit men, the "Autumn" suit features a chemically resistant outer layer made from specialized synthetic fabrics, allowing easier traversal of chemical anomalous fields.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="stalker_vineleaf_outfit_name">
		<text>"Vineleaf" Stalker Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_vineleaf_outfit_description">
		<text>A Zone-built protective suit, designed and manufactured by local mechanics. The "Vineleaf" suit includes a camouflage pattern made from durable synthetic materials, providing both concealment and protection. Its design is optimized for blending into vegetative environments while maintaining moderate ballistic resistance.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="stalker_bear_outfit_name">
		<text>"Bear" Stalker Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_bear_outfit_description">
		<text>A Zone-built protective suit, designed and manufactured by local mechanics. The "Bear" suit's improved protection against ballistics has been achieved through an unnamed home-made anomalous compound, integrated into its Kevlar-reinforced fabric. This suit provides exceptional defense at the cost of added weight and reduced comfort.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="stalker_salamander_outfit_name">
		<text>"Salamander" Stalker Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_salamander_outfit_description">
		<text>A Zone-built protective suit, designed and manufactured by local mechanics. An economical choice with great upgrade potential, the "Salamander" features basic protection with room for enhancements. Ironically, despite its name, it demonstrates a poor ability to safely channel heat, making it less suitable for high-temperature environments.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="stalker_graphite_outfit_name">
		<text>"Graphite" Stalker Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_graphite_outfit_description">
		<text>A Zone-built protective suit, designed and manufactured by local mechanics. Independently designed by a few optimistic stalkers to withstand psy-storms, the "Graphite" suit features a blend of lead-lined fabric and specialized synthetic materials to shelter the wearer's nervous system. Although the original endeavor failed, the recovered designs offer unique protection against psychic threats.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="stalker_tigerstripe_outfit_name">
		<text>"Tigerstripe" Stalker Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_tigerstripe_outfit_description">
		<text>A Zone-built protective suit, designed and manufactured by local mechanics. One of the heavier stalker suits available, the "Tigerstripe" is designed for those who prefer to make their money as hired killers or fighters. It features reinforced ballistic protection with multiple layers of Kevlar and ceramic plates, making it ideal for combat situations.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ecologist_guard_outfit_name">
		<text>ISRIT Guard Jumpsuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ecologist_guard_outfit_description">
		<text>A basic suit originally intended as spare equipment for Professor Hermann's "Iskra Scientific Research and Investigation Team". Made from durable synthetic fabrics, it provides moderate protection. It has since become a relatively cheap protective bodysuit for Ecologist guards working all over the Zone.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="cs_stalker_outfit_name">
		<text>CS-2b Body Armor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cs_stalker_outfit_description">
		<text>Unlike other suits in the CS-1, 2, and 3 series, this body armor was only created after the faction's massive losses at the Chernobyl NPP. It features a focus on protecting the wearer from anomalous environments with reinforced materials and advanced filtration systems. Widely considered the first proper successor to the CS-1 suit, it prioritizes safety over armoring for battle.
		</text>
	</string>



	<!-- REVISION MARKER -->



	<!-- STS (Special Tactical Suits) -->

	<string id="svoboda_light_outfit_name">
		<text>Wind of Freedom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="svoboda_light_outfit_description">
		<text>A Zone-built tactical suit, designed and custom-made by Freedom mechanics. This comfortable bodysuit features a durable, breathable fabric exterior treated with a special solution known as 'Horizon' to increase resistance to chemical anomalies. The interior is lined with moisture-wicking materials, ensuring comfort during extended use in the Zone.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="monolith_outfit_name">
		<text>Monolith X-18 Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_outfit_description">
		<text>A tactical suit of unknown origins, associated with the Monolith faction. Constructed from high-strength synthetic fibers and reinforced with ballistic plates, it offers substantial protection. Scores of these suits were found in containers and lockers underneath the X18 facility in Dark Valley. There are theories among stalkers that these suits predate the creation of the Zone.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="bandit_sun_outfit_name">
		<text>"Sunset" Tactical Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_sun_outfit_description">
		<text>A Zone-built tactical suit, designed and manufactured by local mechanics. Its design resembles the Monolith X-18 suit but with its conventional NBC features stripped down in favor of greater insulation from thermal and electrical threats. The outer layer is made from heat-resistant and electrically-insulating materials. Mostly used by Bandits in Dark Valley to clear out the poltergeists that occasionally escape from the local lab.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="merc_sun_outfit_name">
		<text>"Twilight" Tactical Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_sun_outfit_description">
		<text>A Zone-built tactical suit, designed and manufactured by local mechanics. Its design resembles a Monolith X-18 suit, featuring a blend of durable synthetic fabrics and reinforced with lightweight ballistic plates. This suit is often salvaged by Mercs from their costly skirmishes in Limansk, providing a balance of protection and mobility.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="merc_nighthunter_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary STS-N Body Armor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_nighthunter_outfit_description">
		<text>Sometimes nicknamed the "Nighthunter", this slightly heavy special tactical suit is used by Mercenaries in both nocturnal and urban combat scenarios. Constructed from reinforced Kevlar and ceramic plates, it offers excellent protection while maintaining flexibility for close-quarters combat.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="merc_wolven_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary STS-W Body Armor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_wolven_outfit_description">
		<text>A general purpose protective suit, sometimes nicknamed the "Wolven", a comfortable special tactical suit used by Mercenaries in both exploratory expeditions and stealth operations. Made from lightweight, noise-dampening fabrics and reinforced with ballistic fibers, it provides good protection and exceptional mobility for covert missions.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="isg_outfit_name">
		<text>UNISG Mk1 Tactical Body Armor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="isg_outfit_description">
		<text>A UNISG tactical protective suit, based on a standard bodysuit design used by Western special forces. Similar outfits are common to many militaries throughout the world. Constructed from high-strength synthetic fibers and reinforced with Kevlar plates, this is the bare minimum a UNISG operative can expect to be fitted with, offering reliable protection in various combat scenarios.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="isg_merc_outfit_name">
		<text>UNISG Mk2 Tactical Body Armor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="isg_merc_outfit_description">
		<text>A special UNISG tactical protective suit. The model is an improvement over the original Mk-1 design, much better suited for the Zone's demanding conditions. Enhanced with additional layers of Kevlar and advanced composite materials, it offers superior protection and comfort. These improvements were commissioned by UNISG based on the limited data recovered from their less fortunate predecessors.
		</text>
	</string>

	
	<!-- LCS (Light Combat Suit) -->

	<string id="merc_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary LC Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_outfit_description">
		<text>A light combat suit, one of the most common outfits used by the Zone's Mercenaries. Its design is based on suits used by Western special forces, featuring a lightweight Kevlar weave and minimal ceramic plate inserts. Adequate for basic operations, but the quality is lacking when compared to standard Spetsnaz gear. Many variants are made from this suit's base design.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="merc_fighter_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary LC-F Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_fighter_outfit_description">
		<text>A variation of the standard LC outfit, referred to as the "Fighter" by Mercenaries. Made from high-strength synthetic fibers, it is designed for operations requiring stealth and speed. The lightweight construction provides flexibility and comfort, making it ideal for quick, covert missions. Many variants are made from this suit's base design.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="banditmerc_outfit_name">
		<text>Fenced LC Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="banditmerc_outfit_description">
		<text>A light combat suit obtained to armor local Bandit gangs. Based on Western special forces designs, it is constructed from low-quality materials, including substandard Kevlar and poorly assembled ceramic plates. This suit offers minimal protection, highlighting the irony of Bandits being ripped off by their suppliers. Many variants are made from this suit's base design.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="renegademerc_outfit_name">
		<text>Renegade LC Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="renegademerc_outfit_description">
		<text>A light combat suit acquired through dubious means to armor local groups of Renegades. Modeled after Western special forces gear, it features a comfortable and lightweight construction using synthetic fibers and basic ballistic protection. Surprisingly pleasant to wear despite its origins. Many variants are made from this suit's base design.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="merc_sunset_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary LCz Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_sunset_outfit_description">
		<text>A Mercenary light combat suit modified for use in the Zone. This suit includes reinforced Kevlar layers and additional storage pockets. It is a genuine improvement for newer Mercenaries and serves as a reliable alternative to the faction's special tactical suits. Many variants are made from this suit's base design.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="merc_scout_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary LC-S Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_scout_outfit_description">
		<text>An LC-F suit modified and nicknamed the "Scout". Made from lightweight, breathable fabrics with added ballistic protection, it is a very comfortable suit. The modifications make it a good choice for Mercenaries who want to explore the Zone's anomalies on a budget. Many variants are made from this suit's base design.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="merc_jackal_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary LTS-J Body Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_jackal_outfit_description">
		<text>A light tactical suit, nicknamed "Jackal" after a past leader figure well known among mercenaries. Made from reinforced Kevlar with a sophisticated weight distribution system, it provides excellent comfort and protection. Favored among experienced Mercenaries for its balance of defense and mobility.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="merc_coyote_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary MTS-C Body Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_coyote_outfit_description">
		<text>A medium tactical suit nicknamed "Coyote". Constructed from advanced composite materials and reinforced with ballistic plates, it is widely considered the successor of the LTS-J body suit. Despite its higher price, most Mercenaries prefer it for its superior protection and comfort.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="greh_armored_outfit_name">
		<text>Irij Flak Armor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_armored_outfit_description">
		<text>A comfortable and ergonomic arming suit used to outfit Sin's followers en masse. It consists of a ballistic vest over an environmental bodysuit, made from high-strength synthetic fibers. These suits provide decent protection against ballistic threats and moderate shielding against environmental hazards.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="greh_armored_camo_outfit_name">
		<text>Vyriy Flak Armor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_armored_camo_outfit_description">
		<text>An advanced variant of regular Sin flak armor, typically gifted to the faction's more loyal and devout members. Made from reinforced ballistic materials and featuring enhanced environmental protection. These suits provide decent protection against ballistic threats and moderate shielding against environmental hazards.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="dolg_voin_outfit_name">
		<text>PS6-V Warrior Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_voin_outfit_description">
		<text>A modern, updated variant of the original PS5-M universal protection bodysuit. Made from a blend of Kevlar and advanced composites, it is more than adequate for all of the Zone's conditions and is markedly comfortable for a Duty suit. Initially intended to replace its predecessor entirely, but higher production cost has kept the PS6-V model in use.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="isg_lcs_outfit_name">
		<text>UNISG LC Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="isg_lcs_outfit_description">
		<text>A light combat suit model adapted for use by UNISG troops. Based on Western special forces designs, it features high-strength synthetic fibers and basic ballistic protection. Suitable for a variety of operations in the Zone.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="isg_lcs_camo_outfit_name">
		<text>UNISG LC-C Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="isg_lcs_camo_outfit_description">
		<text>A modified light combat suit model adapted for use in the Zone by UNISG troops. Constructed from lightweight, breathable materials and enhanced with camouflage patterns, it is light weight and comfortable. Ideal for reconnaissance and stealth operations.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="isg_lcs_urban_outfit_name">
		<text>UNISG LC-UC Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="isg_lcs_urban_outfit_description">
		<text>A modified light combat suit model adapted for urban combat by UNISG troops. Based on Western special forces designs, it features advanced composite materials and reinforced ballistic protection. Compares favorably in combat to many other outfits in its class, but still falls short of what a Spetsnaz operator would be wearing.
		</text>
	</string>

	<!-- Berill-5M Armored Suits -->

	<string id="army_outfit_name">
		<text>Military Service Outfit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="army_outfit_description">
		<text>A basic outfit contracted by the Ukrainian government in a production effort that was outsourced to the lowest bidder. The outer layer is made from basic synthetic fibers and does not provide any meaningful environmental or ballistic protection. Typically issued to helicopter pilots, tank drivers, rear-echelon personnel, conscripts, and enlisted servicemen. Generally only seen on the outermost perimeter of the Zone where combat is less likely.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="specops_outfit_name">
		<text>Berill-5M Armored Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="specops_outfit_description">
		<text>An armored suit designed for use by special operations, comprising military PS5 series body armor with beryllium sputter modified for use in the Zone. The suit features advanced composite materials and beryllium coating for enhanced ballistic protection and radiation resistance. Designed for intense rapid-insertion assault operations, this outfit is standard issue for most Spetsnaz operators in the Zone.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="specops_dolg_outfit_name">
		<text>PS5-B Battle Armor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="specops_dolg_outfit_description">
		<text>A special purpose battle armor, commonly used by Duty faction operatives. This outfit comprises military PS5 series body armor with beryllium sputter modified for use in the Zone. The suit uses high-density ballistic fibers and ceramic plates, offering superior protection and ergonomics compared to a standard PS5-M universal protection suit.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="specops_merc_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary B-5M Armored Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="specops_merc_outfit_description">
		<text>Spetsnaz body armor acquired and repurposed by contracted mercenary mechanics in the Zone. Made from advanced Kevlar and ceramic composites, it provides good physical protection while also being remarkably comfortable to wear. Often worn by mercenaries who used to work for the SSU, this suit balances protection and mobility effectively.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="specops_bandit_outfit_name">
		<text>Deserter's B-5M Armored Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="specops_bandit_outfit_description">
		<text>A set of PS5 series body armor with beryllium sputter, acquired through shady means by the Zone's Bandits. Despite showing visible signs of irreparable wear and tear, the suit still offers excellent ballistic protection with its reinforced composite materials and beryllium coating, making it a solid choice for general combat encounters.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="svoboda_heavy_outfit_name">
		<text>Guardian of Freedom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="svoboda_heavy_outfit_description">
		<text>A set of Spetsnaz body armor that has been "liberated" for use in the Freedom faction. Treated with "Sovereign", an anomalous compound developed by the faction, it provides enhanced protection against anomalous effects. Its exact composition or anomalous properties have not been documented by Zone researchers. Made from high-strength Kevlar and beryllium-coated composites. When available, the armor is used by Freedom members tasked with defending the barrier and the main faction base against Monolith incursions.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="dolg_specops_red_outfit_name">
		<text>PS5-B2 Veteran Battlesuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_specops_red_outfit_description">
		<text>A set of former Spetsnaz body armor, bolstered with more substantial protection. Made from high-density ballistic fibers and reinforced ceramic plates, it offers excellent combat protection. However, it has an infamous failure rate in areas of extreme anomalous activity. Duty  veterans often still advocate for the PS5-B2 model's use and are rumored to claim, "you do not need protection from anomalies once you know how to spot them."
		</text>
	</string>


	<!-- PS5-M Universal protection suit -->

	<string id="dolg_outfit_name">
		<text>PS5-M Universal Protection Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_outfit_description">
		<text>An older version of the Duty-developed protective bodysuit, constructed from durable Kevlar and composite materials. It provides balanced protection against ballistic threats and environmental hazards and has a solid balance in cost and utility. Well-suited for recruits who may prefer the familiarity of stalker suits over heavier battle armor models.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="dolg_scout_outfit_name">
		<text>PS5-R Scout Vest</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_scout_outfit_description">
		<text>An older Duty-developed protective suit developed alongside the PS5-M universal protection outfit. Made from lightweight synthetic fibers and Kevlar, it offers minimal ballistic protection but is designed for mobility. Originally intended to protect Duty scouts in the early days of the Zone's existence, these suits are now mostly retired, kept in reserve for Duty recruits in desperate circumstances.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="dolg_red_outfit_name">
		<text>PS5-M Hunter Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_red_outfit_description">
		<text>A Duty-developed heavier variant of the PS5-M universal protection suit, made with reinforced Kevlar and additional padding. It trades some ballistic protection in favor of better defense against common mutant attacks. Specifically designed for Duty units intending to hunt mutants, this suit compares well even to modern Duty suits in its overall properties.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="svoboda_heavy_outfit_2_name">
		<text>Sentinel of Freedom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="svoboda_heavy_outfit_2_description">
		<text>An older, slightly heavier stalker bodysuit designed and manufactured by Freedom mechanics. Constructed from robust synthetic materials and Kevlar, it offers decent protection despite its slightly dated design and some wear and tear on the outside materials. Younger Freedomers value these suits highly, not only for their functionality but also for the stories and legacy they carry.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="bandit_ps5_outfit_name">
		<text>Fenced PS5-M Universal Protection Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_ps5_outfit_description">
		<text>A modified PS5-M universal protection suit, made from durable Kevlar and composite materials, offering balanced protection. Armor like the PS5-M first entered circulation among Bandits thanks to Quartermaster Morgan, a corrupt supplier formerly associated to the Duty faction. The suit trades some physical protection for greater comfort and defense against anomalies. These suits are a major sore point for the Duty faction, and retrieving them from anarchists and criminals is a high priority.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="greh_ps5_outfit_name">
		<text>Volos Flak Armor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_ps5_outfit_description">
		<text>Based on the PS5-M universal protection suit, the Volos Flak armor is a model manufactured by mechanics of Sin, based off a Duty-developed original design. The armor is made from high-quality Kevlar and composite materials. It is unknown how it came into the possession of Sin, but Duty have voices their concern about their armor designs being appropriated by fanatics and lunatics. The recovery of these suits is an unspoken priority for Duty. Despite the controversy, the suit itself is of good quality and is more than adequate for the Zone's various conditions.
		</text>
	</string>

	
	<!-- Skat-9 Military Armored Suits -->

	<string id="military_outfit_name">
		<text>Skat-9 Armored Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="military_merc_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary Skat-9 Armored Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="military_monolit_outfit_name">
		<text>Monolith Skat-9 Armored Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="military_freedom_outfit_name">
		<text>Liberated Skat-9 Armored Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="military_sky_outfit_name">
		<text>CS-4b Armored Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="military_bandit_outfit_name">
		<text>Looted Skat-9 Armored Suit</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="military_outfit_description">
		<text>A high quality military-grade armor, designed specifically for combat operations in the Zone. Comprising a PSZ-12p heavy military armored suit, built-in compensation suit, and an anomalous protection bodysuit, it offers exceptional ballistic protection and resistance to environmental hazards. Although originally intended for the sole use of Military stalkers and experienced Spetsnaz operators, this armor occasionally finds its way into factions outside of the Military through unknown means.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="dolg_heavy_outfit_name">
		<text>PSZ-9d Body Armor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_heavy_outfit_description">
		<text>A high quality protective bodysuit developed by defense research institutes in Kiev, adopted by Duty faction mechanics. The PSZ-9d body armor features a combination of Kevlar and advanced ceramic plates, providing excellent ballistic protection capable of stopping rifle bullets. Additionally, it offers robust defense against the Zone's anomalous hazards. Typically reserved for Duty members who have proven themselves significantly, this armor is both highly prized and effective.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="dolg_pantsir_outfit_name">
		<text>PSZ-7p Shell Armor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_pantsir_outfit_description">
		<text>A high quality intermediate protective bodysuit, with an enhanced design adopted by Duty faction mechanics. The armor is more protective than Duty's regular PS5 universal protection suit, yet less expensive and easier to produce than the PSZ-9d body armor variant. Made from durable composite materials and reinforced with lightweight ballistic fibers, it provides excellent protection for combat encounters. Its ease of maintenance and repair makes it ideal for Duty operatives working far from friendly territory, such as investigators venturing into the northern reaches of the Zone.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="dolg_heavy_redline_outfit_name">
		<text>PSZ-9kl Command Armor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_heavy_redline_outfit_description">
		<text>A high-end protective suit, adopted by Duty faction mechanics. Made from advanced Kevlar and reinforced with thick ceramic plates, it offers substantial protection against ballistic threats and environmental hazards. The armor is said to have been favored by the late Duty Lieutenant Colonel Shulga. Though Shulga rarely left his operational base in Yanov, he feared assassination and thus preferred heavy protection. He was later presumed dead after leading a mass assault into the city of Pripyat. Veteran Duty operatives occasionally wear models like the PSZ-9kl to honor his legacy.
		</text>
	</string>


	<!-- Scientific outfits -->

	<string id="scientific_outfit_name">
		<text>SEVA Bodysuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="scientific_outfit_description">
		<text>An intermediate level protective suit designed and produced by the Kiev Defense Research Institute. It combines a CBRN (Chemical, Biological, Radiological, Nuclear) jumpsuit with a specially-treated Class II Kevlar vest. The SEVA is designed with a closed-cycle respiratory module and an external isolation coating against environmental hazards. The suit is a superior alternative to almost all Zone-made protective suits and offers balanced ballistic, strike, and anomalous protection with moderate weight. Commonly used by experienced research personnel and artifact hunters venturing into hostile territory.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="svoboda_scientific_outfit_name">
		<text>Watchman of Freedom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="svoboda_scientific_outfit_description">
		<text>A suit of "Sentinel" body armor produced by Freedom mechanics, built with a robust blend of Kevlar and synthetic fibers. Specially treated materials provide good protection and durability during prolonged exploration of anomalous fields. Designed for observing anomalous phenomena in the Zone, it is a reliable choice for Freedom faction's field researchers.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="monolith_scientific_outfit_name">
		<text>Monolith Scientific Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_scientific_outfit_description">
		<text>A Monolith scientific suit that includes a flak vest of unknown origin. It features unique modifications for enhanced radiation resistance at the cost of greater vulnerability to psy-fields. According to reports, similar models are worn by Monolith forces defending the Brain Scorcher in Radar and its southern barrier, deployment can sometimes also be observed in and around Red Forest.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="cs_scientific_outfit_name">
		<text>CS-4a SEVA Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cs_scientific_outfit_description">
		<text>An unofficial variant of the SEVA intermediate level protective suit, a series designed and produced by the Kiev Defense Research Institute. It combines a CBRN (Chemical, Biological, Radiological, Nuclear) jumpsuit with a specially-treated Class II Kevlar vest. The SEVA is designed with a closed-cycle respiratory module and an external isolation coating against environmental hazards. The CS-4a variant has some internal changes made by Clear Sky faction mechanics to better fit it to the needs of researchers and guard personnel. Like other SEVA variants, it has balanced protection with moderate weight.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="cs_scientific_outfit_good_name">
		<text>CS-4a Pathfinder</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cs_scientific_outfit_good_description">
		<text>An unofficial variant of the SEVA intermediate level protective suit, a series designed and produced by the Kiev Defense Research Institute. It combines a CBRN (Chemical, Biological, Radiological, Nuclear) jumpsuit with a specially-treated Class II Kevlar vest and some additional changes made to the inside linings for added comfort and weight distribution. The SEVA series is designed with a closed-cycle respiratory module and an external isolation coating against environmental hazards. The Pathfinder model is credited to Clear Sky resident technician Novikov. Compared to many SEVA models, the CS-4a Pathfinder is extremely comfortable to move around in, making it a high-demand suit among Clear Sky and other factions.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="bandit_scientific_outfit_name">
		<text>Scavenged SEVA Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_scientific_outfit_description">
		<text>An unofficial variant of the SEVA intermediate level protective suit, a series designed and produced by the Kiev Defense Research Institute. It combines a CBRN (Chemical, Biological, Radiological, Nuclear) jumpsuit with a specially-treated Class II Kevlar vest with some custom modifications, as well as replaced internal parts and patched outside materials. This model has been repurposed by bandits, making it one of the higher quality mixed protective outfits commonly used by experienced members. Bandits use these suits to organize ambushes and attacks on stalkers within anomalous fields and radiation pockets, despite their general disinterest in scientific research.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="isg_scientific_outfit_name">
		<text>UNISG SEVA Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="isg_scientific_outfit_description">
		<text>A special design SEVA intermediate level protective suit, a subvariant commissioned by the first iteration of UNISG from the Kiev Defense Research Institute with assistance from experienced mechanics stationed in the Zone. Like other variants, it combines a CBRN (Chemical, Biological, Radiological, Nuclear) jumpsuit with a specially-treated Class II Kevlar vest with some custom modifications. It is designed with a closed-cycle respiratory module uses experimental coatings and weaves that aim to provide enhanced protection and durability against radiation and anomalous effects. Some of the changes are hard to determine and the mechanical work on the suit is undocumented.
		</text>
	</string>

	<!-- REVISION MARKER -->

	<string id="merc_scientific_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary SEVA Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_scientific_outfit_description">
		<text>A SEVA intermediate level protective suit designed and produced by the Kiev Defense Research Institute. It combines a CBRN (Chemical, Biological, Radiological, Nuclear) jumpsuit with a specially-treated Class II Kevlar vest. The SEVA is designed with a closed-cycle respiratory module and an external isolation coating against environmental hazards. This particular model was commissioned by mercenaries and customized by local mechanics. The variant features durable synthetic fibers and Kevlar weave. Commonly used by experienced operatives on artifact-hunting contracts. Provides good protection but lacks some more recent psy-protection properties available for modern variants.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="merc_combat_scientific_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary Pathfinder</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_combat_scientific_outfit_description">
		<text>A SEVA intermediate level protective suit designed and produced by the Kiev Defense Research Institute. It combines a CBRN (Chemical, Biological, Radiological, Nuclear) jumpsuit with a specially-treated Class IIIA ballistic vest, a notable upgrade to base models. The SEVA is designed with a closed-cycle respiratory module and an external isolation coating against environmental hazards. This particular variant was commissioned by mercenaries, features higher quality materials and a higher ballistic protection class. The Pathfinder variant was initially produced as a token of goodwill by Clear Sky to help cover rising research costs.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="dolg_scientific_outfit_name">
		<text>PS5-9Md Universal Scientific Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_scientific_outfit_description">
		<text>A SEVA intermediate level protective suit designed and produced by the Kiev Defense Research Institute. It combines a CBRN (Chemical, Biological, Radiological, Nuclear) jumpsuit with a specially-treated Class II Kevlar vest. The SEVA is designed with a closed-cycle respiratory module and an external isolation coating against environmental hazards. This is a customized Duty variant of the standard SEVA design, adding a durable synthetic weave to augment its overall resistance to anomalous effects (primarily corrosive and thermal). Commonly used by Duty units on exploratory or scientific missions to the northern parts of the Zone.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="dolg_scientific_red_outfit_name">
		<text>PS5-9Md Light Scientific Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_scientific_red_outfit_description">
		<text>A lightweight SEVA intermediate level protective suit designed and produced by the Kiev Defense Research Institute. It combines a CBRN (Chemical, Biological, Radiological, Nuclear) jumpsuit with a specially-treated Class IIIA Kevlar vest, a notable upgrade to the base design. The SEVA is designed with a closed-cycle respiratory module and an external isolation coating against environmental hazards. The model is a variant of the PS5-9Md Duty base design made with lighter materials and features a higher ballistic protection class, as well as improved weight distribution. Its modifications come with slightly reduced protection against anomalous effects. Commonly used by Duty field researchers and units on exploratory missions.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="dolg_scientific_wood_outfit_name">
		<text>PS5-9Md Light Pathfinder</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_scientific_wood_outfit_description">
		<text>A lightweight SEVA intermediate level protective suit designed and produced by the Kiev Defense Research Institute. It combines a CBRN (Chemical, Biological, Radiological, Nuclear) jumpsuit with a specially-treated Class II Kevlar vest. The SEVA is designed with a closed-cycle respiratory module and an external isolation coating against environmental hazards. This variant has been commissioned by Duty officials for their needs and modified and produced by Clear Sky. It is made from lighter synthetic materials at the expense of some of its protective capabilities. A common choice for Duty field operatives.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="bandit_scientific_dark_outfit_name">
		<text>Patchwork SEVA Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_scientific_dark_outfit_description">
		<text>A scavenged SEVA intermediate level protective suit, originally designed and produced by the Kiev Defense Research Institute. It combines a CBRN (Chemical, Biological, Radiological, Nuclear) jumpsuit with a specially-treated Class II Kevlar vest. The SEVA is designed with a closed-cycle respiratory module and an external isolation coating against environmental hazards. This variant has been heavily modified and repaired multiple times by Bandit mechanics with mixed materials. The base is made from high-strength materials but repeated changes made to its components reduce its overall protective capabilities. Compared to the base design, it has a lower weight profile. Commonly used by more experienced Bandits and stalkers working on a lower budget.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="renegade_scientific_outfit_name">
		<text>Renegade SEVA Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="renegade_scientific_outfit_description">
		<text>A SEVA intermediate level protective suit designed and produced by the Kiev Defense Research Institute. It combines a CBRN (Chemical, Biological, Radiological, Nuclear) jumpsuit with a specially-treated Class II Kevlar vest. The SEVA is designed with a closed-cycle respiratory module and an external isolation coating against environmental hazards. This variant has been extensively modified for improved protection against thermal hazards and blunt trauma compared to the standard SEVA design. Commonly used by Renegade members in the northern parts of the Zone. A solid alternative to various other light combat or hand-made suits available.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="merc_scientific_armored_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary SEVA Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_scientific_armored_outfit_description">
		<text>An intermediate level protective suit designed and produced by the Kiev Defense Research Institute. It combines a CBRN (Chemical, Biological, Radiological, Nuclear) jumpsuit with a specially-treated Class II Kevlar vest. The SEVA is designed with a closed-cycle respiratory module and an external isolation coating against environmental hazards. This variant was commissioned by mercenaries and modified to use high-strength synthetic fibers and extra Kevlar weave for added ballistic protection. Commonly used by experienced mercenaries who are contracted to guide high profile research personnel and artifact hunters looking to travel into the more dangerous parts of the Zone.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="monolith_scientific_light_outfit_name">
		<text>Monolith Patchwork Scientific Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_scientific_light_outfit_description">
		<text>A SEVA-like intermediate level protective suit built from scratch by unknown mechanics within the Monolith faction. It combines a CBRN (Chemical, Biological, Radiological, Nuclear) jumpsuit with a specially-treated Class II Kevlar vest. The SEVA is designed with a closed-cycle respiratory module and an external isolation coating against environmental hazards. Compared to commonly traded models, this Monolith variant features high-strength materials and some added ballistic and strike protection at the expensive of the wearer's comfort, alongside average protection against anomalies. Its exact role within the faction is unknown.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ace_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary ACE Scientific Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ace_outfit_description">
		<text>An intermediate to high-end level protective suit, one of the most technologically advanced bodysuits in the Zone. The ACE armor system incorporates a next-generation CBRN (Chemical, Biological, Radiological, Nuclear) jumpsuit and a pocketed Kevlar vest with Class III plate inserts. Like its less advanced SEVA counter-part, the ACE is designed with a closed-cycle respiratory module. It uses state-of-the-art materials such as selectively-permeable coatings and external treatment for enhanced protection against environmental hazards. The ACE is optimized for maximum anomaly protection for its weight class while also providing high wearer comfort. Only rarely found due to its high cost, used by experienced mercenaries, high-profile researchers, and operatives working on a blank check.
		</text>
	</string>


	<!-- SSP-99 -->

	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_orange_name">
		<text>SSP-99 Bodysuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_orange_description">
		<text>The SSP-99 is a current-generation CBRN suit specially designed for the Zone's conditions and is used by scientific expeditions for extended forays into anomalous fields. When combined with the SSP-99 screen helmet, it includes an integrated air-filtering and air-conditioning system. Its design is specifically tailored for maximum durability in thermal, chemical, and electrical fields.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_grn_name">
		<text>SSP-99M Bodysuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_grn_description">
		<text>High quality modified SSP-99 suit. A Kevlar underlayer has been added to reduce the risk of suit puncture from hostile mutants. Provides improved protection from biological anomalies compared to the SSP-99.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_white_name">
		<text>SSP-99 "Diamond"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_white_description">
		<text>The SSP-99 is a current-generation CBRN suit specially designed for the Zone's conditions and is used by scientific expeditions for extended forays into anomalous fields. When combined with the SSP-99 screen helmet, it includes an integrated air-filtering and air-conditioning system. Its design is specifically tailored for maximum durability in thermal and chemical fields. The "Diamond" variant also gives superior protection from electricity.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_blue_name">
		<text>SSP-99M "Sapphire"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_blue_description">
		<text>High quality modified SSP-99 suit. A Kevlar underlayer has been added to the suit to reduce the risk of suit puncture from hostile mutants. The "Sapphire" model provides excellent protection against short-range psi-emissions.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_red_name">
		<text>SSP-99М "Ruby"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_red_description">
		<text>High quality modified SSP-99 suit. A Kevlar underlayer has been added to the suit to reduce the risk of suit puncture from hostile mutants. The "Ruby" model provides improved protection against melee attacks, and includes an integrated wound healing system.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_yello_name">
		<text>SSP-99 Topaz</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_yello_description">
		<text>The SSP-99 is a current-generation CBRN suit specially designed for the Zone's conditions and is used by scientific expeditions for extended forays into anomalous fields. When combined with the SSP-99 screen helmet, it includes an integrated air-filtering and air-conditioning system. The "Topaz" variant provides increased protection from radiation.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<!-- Heavy combat suits -->

	<string id="exolight_outfit_name">
		<text>Exosuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="exolight_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel with many of the attachment points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="dolg_exolight_outfit_name">
		<text>PSZ-10d Duty Battlesuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_exolight_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel with many of the attachment points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. This suit is typically found in the hands of elite Duty warriors, especially those assigned to guard VIPs or launch exceedingly dangerous raids on enemy stalkers.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="svoboda_exolight_outfit_name">
		<text>Warrior of Freedom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="svoboda_exolight_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel with many of the attachment points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. Only the most respected members of Freedom will ever be found wearing a suit like this.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="merc_exolight_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary Exosuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_exolight_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel with many of the attachment points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. An outfit of choice for the captains and bodyguards of Mercenary companies requiring top of the line ballistic protection.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="bandit_exolight_outfit_name">
		<text>Looted Exosuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_exolight_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel with many of the attachment points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. Both imposing and highly intimidating in appearance, this outfit is a favorite among the Zone's most powerful outlaws.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="monolith_exolight_outfit_name">
		<text>Monolith Exosuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_exolight_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel with many of the attachment points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. A favorite among the Monolith's battle preachers and tactical masters who claim the confines of the suit to be as comforting as the Sarcophagus itself.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="military_exolight_outfit_name">
		<text>Military Stalker Exosuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="military_exolight_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel with many of the attachment points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. Considered too cumbersome by the Ukrainian government, these suits are never issued to any unit or individual. Thus soldiers, Military stalkers and the occasional veteran must always find and pay for it through their own means.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="cs_exolight_outfit_name">
		<text>CS-5 Exosuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cs_exolight_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel with many of the attachment points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. These outfits are smuggled in from Ukrainian factories near the borders of the Zone.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="isg_exolight_outfit_name">
		<text>UNISG Exosuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="isg_exolight_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel with many of the attachment points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. A rare sight, since most ISG operatives prefer increased mobility over raw protective power.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="exo_wood_outfit_name">
		<text>Woodland Exosuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="exo_wood_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel with many of the attachment points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. This model includes an early-generation CBRN jumpsuit lined with Kevlar.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="bandit_exo_earth_outfit_name">
		<text>Fenced Exosuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_exo_earth_outfit_description">
		<text>.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="freedom_exo_vineleaf_outfit_name">
		<text>Hero of Freedom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_exo_vineleaf_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel with many of the attachment points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. This variant includes an old CBRN jumpsuit lined with Kevlar and an additional attachment slot.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="exo_dolg_outfit_name">
		<text>PSZ-10d Duty Battlesuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="exo_dolg_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel with many of the attachment points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. This suit is typically found in the hands of elite Duty warriors, especially those assigned to guard VIPs or launch exceedingly dangerous raids.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="exo_dolg_red_outfit_name">
		<text>PSZ-10d Venator Battlesuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="exo_dolg_red_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel with many of the attachment points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. This particular variant is typically found in the hands of elite Duty huntsmen, where its greater defense against mutants is utilized.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="exo_dolg_wood_outfit_name">
		<text>PSZ-10l Forest Battlesuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="exo_dolg_wood_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel with many of the attachment points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. This variant includes an older CBRN jumpsuit with Kevlar weave and additional steel reinforcement. Typically found with elite Duty members, particularly those conducting short operations in the northern reaches of the Zone.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="exo_dolg_urban_outfit_name">
		<text>PSZ-10g Urban Battlesuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="exo_dolg_urban_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel with many of the attachment points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. Additionally, it is only useful in melee and ranged fights, since it offers no anomaly protection whatsoever. Old and exceedingly heavy, it's possible that suits like this were used by the Duty faction to raid Pripyat and clash with Freedom back in 2012.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="exo_merc_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary Heavy Armor TB-1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="exo_merc_outfit_description">
		<text>.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="exo_merc_urban_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary Urban Exosuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="exo_merc_urban_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel with many of the attachment points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. Additionally, it is only useful in melee and ranged fights, since it offers no anomaly protection whatsoever. An outfit of choice for the captains and bodyguards of Mercenary companies operating in areas like Limansk or Pripyat.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="exo_merc_wood_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary Woodland Exosuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="exo_merc_wood_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel with many of the attachment points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. This variant includes an old CBRN that has unfortunately not been modified for the Zone.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="exo_merc_grass_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary Grassland Exosuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="exo_merc_grass_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel with many of the attachment points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. This variant includes an asbestos-weave jumpsuit.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<!-- Proptotype Exoskeleton -->

	<string id="stalker_proto_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>"Sunrise" Exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_proto_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>A stalker bodysuit, specially designed to be fitted with the servos and batteries of an exoskeleton, allowing the wearer to carry significantly more equipment than they could under any other circumstances. Compared to a full exoskeleton, it provides less protection, but is also considerably lighter.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="svoboda_light_proto_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>Wind of Freedom Exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="svoboda_light_proto_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>A Wind of Freedom bodysuit, specially designed to be fitted with the servos and batteries of an exoskeleton, allowing the wearer to carry significantly more equipment than they could under any other circumstances. Compared to a full exoskeleton, it provides less protection, but is also considerably lighter.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="dolg_proto_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>PS5-M Exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_proto_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>A PS5-M universal protection bodysuit, specially designed to be fitted with the servos and batteries of an exoskeleton, allowing the wearer to carry significantly more equipment than they could under any other circumstances. Compared to a full exoskeleton, it provides less protection, but is also considerably lighter.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="dolg_heavy_proto_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>PSZ-9d Exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_heavy_proto_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>A PSZ-9d armored bodysuit, specially designed to be fitted with the servos and batteries of an exoskeleton, allowing the wearer to carry significantly more equipment than they could under any other circumstances. Compared to a full exoskeleton, it sacrifices raw ballistic protection for greater functionality in anomalous fields.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="military_proto_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>Skat-9 Exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="military_proto_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>The very first iteration of the military exoskeleton, modified to fit with the servos and batteries of a modern exoskeleton. Compared to a third-generation exo, it sacrifices raw ballistic protection for greater functionality in anomalous fields.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="monolith_proto_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>X-18 Exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_proto_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>An armor made by either Monolithians or an unknown manufacturer. It has been specially modified to fit with the servos and batteries of an exoskeleton, allowing the wearer to carry significantly more equipment than they could under any other circumstances. Compared to a full exoskeleton, it provides less protection, but is also considerably lighter.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="cs_stalker_proto_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>CS-2b Exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cs_stalker_proto_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>A set of CS-2b body armor that has been specially modified to fit with the servos and batteries of an exoskeleton, allowing the wearer to carry significantly more equipment than they could under any other circumstances. Compared to a full exoskeleton, it provides less protection, but is also considerably lighter.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ecolog_proto_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>SSP-99M Exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ecolog_proto_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>A unique armor system composed of an exoskeleton-powered SSP-99M jumpsuit with an anomaly-resistant Class IIA Kevlar vest placed on top. The durable exo-frames are capable of providing mechanical support for carrying heavy loads even through anomaly fields. Ideal for aiding researchers during deep incursions into the Zone.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="isg_proto_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>UNISG Tactical Exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="isg_proto_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>A UN-branded special tactical bodysuit, specially designed to be fitted with the servos and batteries of an exoskeleton, allowing the wearer to carry significantly more equipment than they could under any other circumstances. Compared to a full exoskeleton, it provides less protection, but is also considerably lighter.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<!-- Exoskeletons -->

	<string id="exo_outfit_name">
		<text>Exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="exo_outfit_description">
		<text>An experimental sample of a military exoskeleton consisting of a steel-reinforced Kevlar jumpsuit and a tactical vest with Class IV inserts, all carried by powered limbs and servomotors. Was never mass-produced due to extraordinary cost and some design flaws though small batches are made in underground facilities outside Ukraine.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="dolg_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>PSZ-10d Exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>Excellent high-tech armor consisting of a steel-reinforced Kevlar jumpsuit and a tactical vest with Class IV inserts, all carried by powered limbs and servomotors. Domestically developed by one of the research institutes, specifically for the Duty faction. Is slowly being phased out in favor of cheaper, more practical suits, and the few Exosuits in active service tend to be in the hands of Duty's oldest veterans.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="svoboda_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>Paragon of Freedom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="svoboda_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>An excellent bodysuit produced by Freedom’s finest artisans consisting of a steel-reinforced Kevlar jumpsuit and a tactical vest with Class IV inserts, all carried by powered limbs and servomotors. While not always the most practical suit to maintain, it is undeniably powerful, and as such is entrusted only to Freedom's finest warriors and guardsmen.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="merc_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary Exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>An experimental sample of a military exoskeleton of western production consisting of a steel-reinforced Kevlar jumpsuit and a tactical vest with Class IV inserts, all carried by powered limbs and servomotors.. While not always the most practical suit to maintain in the Zone, it simultaneously allows the wearer to be both heavily armed and extremely well armored, with enough strength to carry a weeks worth of supplies. Most often worn by veteran Mercenary captains expected to lead their men through hellish conditions.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="monolith_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>Monolith Exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>High-tech armor consisting of a steel-reinforced Kevlar jumpsuit and a tactical vest with Class IV inserts, all carried by powered limbs and servomotors. Study samples have revealed that its servos are made of alloys and materials unknown to any field of science in any other part of the world. Wearing this suit feels like being buried under the concrete of the Sarcophagus itself; terrifyingly claustrophobic for most stalkers, but eerily comforting for true servants of the Monolith.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="bandit_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>Stolen Exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>A stolen military exoskeleton customized by outlaws to attack well-guarded facilities and to plunder well-armed stalkers. More martially inclined aspiring Bandit Lords tend to favor this armor, using it as a stark and unquestionable symbol of their strength and authority over lesser criminals.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="military_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>Military Stalker Exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="military_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>The official military exoskeleton. Released in limited quantities by special order to Military stalkers who payed for it themselves. Designed to carry heavy weapons, along with enough ammunition, food and meds to keep the unit supplied for long periods of time. Occasionally fielded in lieu of light vehicles.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="cs_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>CS-5 Exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cs_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>An experimental version of the army exoskeleton smuggled into the Zone from Ukrainian factories before being refurbished by Clear Sky technicians. Generally, suits like these are held in reserve, to be deployed only in times of true crisis. That said, especially trusted comrades and associates of the faction may eventually receive permission to acquire such a suit for their own personal uses, although not without great cost.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ecolog_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>Scientific Exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ecolog_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>An official version of the military exoskeleton, intended for use by the Ecologists' guards. The suit feels almost impervious to small arms, and its advanced servomotors make it an excellent choice for those in entrenched defensive positions, as it greatly aids in the use of heavy defensive weaponry. When out in the field, wearers of this suit are more commonly used to carrying ludicrous amounts of batteries, LLMCs, AAMs and other supplies an accompanying scientist might need when exploring the Zone.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="renegade_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>Renegade Exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="renegade_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>One of a few exoskeletons assembled by the Renegades back in 2011 to help secure their final push into Clear Sky's base. Unfortunately, they were virtually wiped out before their final victory ever came, thanks to the interference of a Mercenary with a trench coat and a marksman rifle. Modern Renegades who wear this armor always go into battle like a man possessed, eager to mete vengeance upon their most hated foes.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="isg_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>UNISG Exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="isg_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>The official version of the UNISG exoskeleton released in limited quantities by special order of the United Nations. While it still possesses many of the design flaws of other exoskeletons, it's nonetheless seen as a great alternative to light command and scout vehicles.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="greh_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>Vyraj Power Armor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>High-tech armor consisting of a steel-reinforced Kevlar jumpsuit and a tactical vest with Class IV inserts, all carried by powered limbs and servomotors. Study samples have revealed that its servos are made of alloys and materials unknown to any field of science in any other part of the world. Wearing this suit creates an unnatural feeling of bliss and calm within the wearer, although whether this sense of security is genuine or not remains to be understood.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<!-- Nosorog exskeletal armor -->

	<string id="dolg_nosorog_outfit_name">
		<text>PSZ-10d Nosorog</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_nosorog_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary Nosorog</text>
	</string>
	<string id="army_nosorog_outfit_name">
		<text>Military Stalker Nosorog</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_nosorog_outfit_name">
		<text>Monolith Nosorog</text>
	</string>
	<string id="isg_nosorog_outfit_name">
		<text>UNISG Nosorog</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="nosorog_outfit_description">
		<text>A next generation exoskeleton, consisting of a doubly reinforced Exosuit. Rumored to have been the brainchild of a now-deceased stalker named "Fang", whose designs were later claimed by all sorts of powerful factions across the Zone. If regular exoskeletons allow stalkers to feel like a light vehicle, the Nosorog almost makes them believe they're a main battle tank, able to withstand incredible punishment while carrying tremendous ordnance.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="freedom_nosorog_outfit_name">
		<text>Champion of Freedom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_nosorog_outfit_desc">
		<text>A next generation exoskeleton, consisting of a doubly reinforced Exosuit. Rumored to have been the brainchild of a now-deceased stalker named "Fang", whose designs were later claimed by all sorts of powerful factions across the Zone. If regular exoskeletons allow stalkers to feel like a light vehicle, the Nosorog almost makes them believe they're a main battle tank, able to withstand incredible punishment while carrying tremendous ordnance.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>


	<!-- No group -->	

	<string id="ghillie_outfit_name">
		<text>Ghillie Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ghillie_outfit_description">
		<text>This suit is designed to simulate a ‘heap of foliage.’ Usually this type of suit is worn by snipers and hunters to blend in with the environment and hide themselves from enemies. Ghillie suits are commercially produced, but usually both military personnel and civilians customize and improve them to suit their needs.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

</string_table>