<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<string_table>

	<!--
		tier 1 = very low tier artefact
		tier 2 = low tier artefact
		tier 3 = medium tier artefact
		tier 4 = high tier artefact
		tier 5 = top tier artefact
	-->

	<!--
		- thermal artefact
		- chemical artefact
		- electrical artefact
		- gravitational artefact
		- psychoactive artefact
		- regenerative artefact
	-->

	<!-- 
		BASE ARTEFACTS
	-->

	<string id="st_af_itcher_name">
		<text>Itcher</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_itcher_descr">
		<text>
			A common formation of thermal nature with a hard surface of dense metamorphic rock with deep scars covering the entire body, separated into two layers. The soft, yellow glowing core is of unknown organic nature. It actively consumes excessive heat and remains cool at all times. However, it is not recommended to approach chemical and acid anomalies when in possession of the artefact as it will increase the adverse effects of acids and toxins in the user's bloodstream. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] low tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] thermal artefact\n
			%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] containable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_pin_name">
		<text>Pin</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_pin_descr">
		<text>
			A small formation of thermal anomalies. The look of this artefact suggests that it was an organ of a vascular plant. Further studies showed that other organic tissues are fused deep inside. The stem doesn't hold any useful properties. On the contrary, the small pins reduce the temperature of the user's body and cool all objects in their vicinity. This artefact offers slight psy-protection as it will resonate under the influence of psy-waves. However, it is not recommended to approach chemical and acid anomalies when in possession of the artefact as it will increase the adverse effects of acids and toxins in the user's bloodstream. Radiation output is average on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] low tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] thermal artefact\n
			%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] containable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_cristall_name">
		<text>Crystal</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cristall_descr">
		<text>
			A formation created in intense thermal anomalies under high pressure. Actively consumes excessive heat and remains cool at all times. It will also protect the user against electrical currents. However, exposure to such environments increases the artefact's conductivity due to an unknown mechanism. For this reason, one must weigh the pros and cons of using the Crystal in areas of high conductivity. This artefact is highly sought after by jewellers outside the Zone, as its inner core is not radioactive and is considered exceptionally beautiful when polished and refined. Only the first centimeter of its outer layer emits radiation. Prolonged exposure to even minimal amounts of radioactive material can result in serious harm to the user. Covered with a very hard layer and relatively heavy due to high density. Radiation output is average on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] medium tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] thermal artefact\n
			%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] containable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_fireball_name">
		<text>Fireball</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fireball_descr">
		<text>
			A spherical formation made of red-coloured crystal, most commonly found in the Burner anomaly. It maintains a constant internal temperature of 75 degrees Fahrenheit (24 degrees Celsius), regardless of its surroundings and exposes some of this beneficial effect to an outward area of influence. This allows it to absorb heat from its vicinity and create a protective pocket around the user, preventing flames from causing harm. However, it increases electrical conductivity, raising the probability of electrocution, especially during storms and near electrical anomalies. It is quite heavy due to the high density of the crystal-like material. Radiation output is high on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] high tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] thermal artefact\n
			%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] containable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_blood_name">
		<text>Stone Blood</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_blood_descr">
		<text>
			A reddish formation of compressed fossilised plants, soil, and animal debris, created in chemical anomalies. Can partially neutralize toxins by absorbing them from organic matter and reducing overall toxicity levels in the bloodstream when carried. It additionally accelerates clotting if worn close to the body. However, it makes chemical burns fester, increases susceptibility to corrosive effects, and can catch fire and spontaneously combust under unknown conditions. It is not recommended to keep this artefact in your possession for long periods of time. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] low tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] chemical artefact\n
			%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] containable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_mincer_meat_name">
		<text>Meat Chunk</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_mincer_meat_descr">
		<text>
			A formation with a soft, porous, skin-like texture, resembling a sponge on the outside. The pores on its surface absorb small amounts of suspended toxins and corrosive acids from the environment. It slightly amplifies the damaging effects of psy-fields and seems to store and re-emit them like an organic capacitor. Meat Chunk is also known to conduct electricity much like the skin of a living creature. Reveals its special characteristics only when exposed to certain external conditions. Radiation output is average on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] low tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] chemical artefact\n
			%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] containable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_bracelet_name">
		<text>Bracelet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_bracelet_descr">
		<text>
			A common organic formation, consisting of compressed bryophyte species plants, exposed to high levels of radioaction and chemical transmutatative effects. Provides substantial protection against different types of acidic hazards by gradually increasing the pH of suspended particles to the level of water (pH 7) in a wavering area of influence. When carried, it also neutralizes some of the harmful effects of psy anomalies and the active psy emissions of some mutated creatures. Radiation output is average on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] medium tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] chemical artefact\n
			%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] containable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_baloon_name">
		<text>Bubble</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_baloon_descr">
		<text>
			A compound of several hollow organic formations. This artefact emits a gaseous substance that neutralises chemical or toxic particles inside the body, providing great toxic and chemical protection. It maintains a constant temperature regardless of surroundings, absorbing heat and creating a protective pocket around the user. However, Bubble greatly amplifies the effects of psy-waves and fields produced by mutants and anomalies. Some stalkers have reported feeling intense pain and psychological effects when in possession of a Bubble. Radiation output is high on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] high tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] chemical artefact\n
			%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] containable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_electra_sparkler_name">
		<text>Sparkler</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_sparkler_descr">
		<text>
			A formation with the appearance of translucent spider webs. It is sticky and has glue-like properties, found near electro anomalies. It smooths fluctuations in electric field density and acts as a weak resistor, protecting the wearer from electricity. However, it increases the corrosiveness of acids, leading to accelerated deterioration of equipment and higher damage to tissues. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] low tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] electrical artefact\n
			%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] containable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>


	<string id="st_af_sponge_name">
		<text>Sponge</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_sponge_descr">
		<text>
			An organic formation resembling a living sponge. It sometimes tries to "grab" objects it touches with substantial adhesive strength, making it difficult to properly contain. This artefact acts as a powerful resistor, absorbing lethal doses of electricity. However, it will catch fire when exposed to open flame or even spontaneously combust. Ecologists debate whether this artefact is derived from basic forms of organisms or is an advanced life form with self-awareness. Radiation output is average on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] low tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] electrical artefact\n
			%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] containable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_ring_name">
		<text>Ring</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ring_descr">
		<text>
			A very small formation of electric nature, consisting of two ring-shaped materials of organic origin. When the Ring is given an initial rotational push, it never stops spinning, defying the first law of thermodynamics. The outer ring has high conductivity, absorbing electrical current and grounding it in the inner ring. Prolonged exposure may enhance its flammability, causing it to ignite. Scientists suggest that this artefact inherits gravitational properties from Vortex anomalies. The mechanism behind the disappearance of electrical power inside the second ring is still unknown. Radiation output is average on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] medium tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] electrical artefact\n
			%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] containable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_electra_flash_name">
		<text>Flash</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_flash_descr">
		<text>
			A formation similar in appearance to Moonlight, resembling a plasma globe or lamp. It acts as a powerful resistor, shielding its user from lethal doses of electricity. When worn, it slightly counters harmful effects of psy-anomalies or psy-waves. However, it hinders the healing process, requiring caution when wounded or bleeding. Extremely light and portable. Radiation output is high on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] high tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] electrical artefact\n
			%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] containable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_cristall_flower_name">
		<text>Stone Flower</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cristall_flower_descr">
		<text>
			A formation resembling melted cheese, interspersed with sapphire-like stones. The yellow outer shell gives off radiation, but the non-radioactive blue parts can be extracted for jewellery and industrial purposes. The sapphire-like stones protect from psy-waves and slightly increase resistance to toxicity. However, the artefact can cause objects in its vicinity to heat up and ignite. Due to its density, the weight of Stone Flower has increased beyond normal standards, making it one of the heaviest anomalous creations in the Zone. This quality and appearance make it highly sought after by jewellers. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] low tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] psychoactive artefact\n
			%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] containable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_lobster_eyes_name">
		<text>Lobster Eyes</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_lobster_eyes_descr">
		<text>
			A formation shaped like two eggs fused together, with a thick, high-density outer surface. It offers slightly more psy-protection than Stone Flower, resonating when exposed to psy waves and absorbing some effects. It also consumes excessive heat while remaining cool. Due to its density, Lobster Eyes is quite heavy. Radiation output is average on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] low tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] psychoactive artefact\n
			%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] containable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_electra_moonlight_name">
		<text>Moonlight</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_moonlight_descr">
		<text>
			A unique electrostatic artefact that resonates when exposed to psy fields. Stalkers have learned to fine-tune it to neutralize psy emissions. It also increases electrical protection by reducing conductivity. However, it will catch fire when exposed to open flame or even spontaneously combust. This orb of considerable beauty is sought after by many. Radiation output is average on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] medium tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] electrical artefact\n
			%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] containable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_black_spray_name">
		<text>Black Spray</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_black_spray_descr">
		<text>
			A rare artefact with properties and origins that are not well understood. Resembling other sapphire-like artefacts, its organic stem suggests formation from vascular plants under exposure to psy-fields and electromagnetic waves. It delays light transmission and significantly neutralises psy interferences. However, it amplifies the effects of toxic environments, making it extremely dangerous. Highly sought after by jewellers for its beautiful blue aura. Radiation output is high on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] high tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] psychoactive artefact\n
			%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] containable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_medusa_name">
		<text>Jellyfish</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_medusa_descr">
		<text>
			A common gravitational artefact in the Zone. Slightly shields the body and objects from physical impacts and protects against extreme heat. Quite heavy due to the gravitational field increasing its mass. Increases the negative effects of psy-waves and is a potent conductor. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] low tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] gravitational artefact\n
			%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] containable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_vyvert_name">
		<text>Wrenched</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_vyvert_descr">
		<text>
			A bizarrely-shaped artefact appearing in places with increased gravitational activity. Appears almost organic but is more similar to coral. Provides protection against physical impacts by reducing friction caused by fast objects. Absorbs chemical and toxic elements, providing protection from external toxic agents and chemical particles in the body. Generates a locally directed gravity field which increases its mass, making it heavy. Radiation output is average on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] medium tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] gravitational artefact\n
			%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] containable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_empty_name">
		<text>Empty</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_empty_descr">
		<text>
			Two disks of organic formation (commonly lipids, cellulose, and lignin) with empty space in between. Stabilized by a unique gravitational field, any attempt to press the disks together or pull them apart fails due to rapid changes in the gravitational field. Moving with an Empty is difficult as the gravitational field increases the density of surrounding air, slowing the body down. Reduces friction and provides great protection against physical impacts. Radiation output is average on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] medium tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] gravitational artefact\n
			%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] containable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>


	<string id="st_af_full_empty_name">
		<text>Full Empty</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_full_empty_descr">
		<text>
			Similar to Empty, this artefact consists of two disks of organic formation connected by a unique gravitational field. However, the field in Full Empty is extraordinary: all atoms entering the centre become interactive, releasing photons and creating a "galaxy effect." The density increment of surrounding air is higher compared to Empty, greatly hindering movement. Provides remarkable protection against physical impacts, capable of stopping 9mm bullets at point-blank range. Radiation output is high on the artefact radiation scale. Scientists refer to the light emission as the "galaxy effect," giving the artefact an exceptional orbit of light.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] high tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] gravitational artefact\n
			%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] containable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_night_star_name">
		<text>Nightstar</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_night_star_descr">
		<text>
			A glowing artefact that generates a local directed low-gravity field. Widely used by stalkers along with Gravi to increase maximum load. Due to its beautiful inner core, it is highly sought after by jewellers, but unskilled treatment can cause it to explode. Only the outer core of the artefact emits radiation. Nightstar absorbs toxic and chemical agents from the environment, although the amount absorbed is negligible. Relatively cheap and accessible even to stalkers with tight budgets. Emits an odour of burning flesh near heat sources and may ignite with prolonged exposure. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] low tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] gravitational artefact\n
			%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] containable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_gravi_name">
		<text>Gravi</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_gravi_descr">
		<text>
			Formed from metallic substances exposed to prolonged gravitation, capable of sustaining a powerful anti-gravitational field, reducing the weight of objects in its proximity. Scientist Sakharov at Yantar first discovered that Gravi creates a minute singularity field of anti-gravitational nature at intervals of 30 minutes. Increases electrical conductivity, raising the risk of electrocution, especially during storms and near electrical anomalies. Also increases the negative effects of psy-waves. Radiation output is average on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] medium tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] gravitational artefact\n
			%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] containable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_gold_fish_name">
		<text>Goldfish</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_gold_fish_descr">
		<text>
			A superior version of Gravi, created when three Gravi artefacts interact and get sucked into each other's singularity fields. Discovered by scientist Sakharov at Yantar after a massive blowout/emission hit the Zone. Highly valued and sought after by special agents. Creates a constant anti-gravitational singularity field affecting its vicinity. However, increases the velocity of moving objects inside its radius, causing dangerous impacts. Radiation output is highest on the artefact radiation scale. Rumoured within Ukrainian Spetsnaz circles that Russian agents are acquiring Goldfish for specialized laboratories.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] high tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] gravitational artefact\n
			%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] containable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_dummy_glassbeads_name">
		<text>Mama's Beads</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_glassbeads_descr">
		<text>
			Shaped like a DNA helix, Mama's Beads are created in the Burner anomaly. They constantly pulsate, generating emissions that increase metabolism, accelerating coagulation, and healing wounds. The mechanism behind these effects is still unknown. Mama's Beads also shield the body and objects from extreme heat. However, they increase electrical conductivity, raising the risk of electrocution, especially during storms and near electrical anomalies. Quite dense and heavy for a small artefact. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] low tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] bleeding artefact\n
			%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] containable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_eye_name">
		<text>Eye</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_eye_descr">
		<text>
			This artefact, resembling the human eye, considerably increases metabolism, helping wounds heal quicker. Experienced stalkers say it also brings luck. Soothes pain and is extremely useful for treating wounds. Slightly counters harmful effects of psy-anomalies or psy-waves. Extremely dangerous in chemical anomalies as it amplifies toxicity. Highly recommended to keep it in your backpack, not on your body, when exploring toxic areas. Known colloquially as "copper eye" due to its conductive properties. Radiation output is average on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] medium tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] bleeding artefact\n
			%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] containable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_fire_name">
		<text>Flame</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fire_descr">
		<text>
			Forms in areas of high thermal activity, producing powerful infrared emissions that intensify metabolic processes, healing wounds rapidly. Its healing capabilities are stronger than the Eye artefact, helping stalkers survive severe wounds. Shares positive and negative properties with the Eye: entering a psy-field with Flame is dangerous as it absorbs psy energy and emits it at a considerable rate. Highly recommended to proceed with caution when planning to sell it due to potential radioactive exposure. Can be used as a reusable medkit due to its rapid healing properties. Radiation output is high on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] high tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] bleeding artefact\n
			%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] containable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>


	<string id="st_af_dummy_battery_name">
		<text>Battery</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_battery_descr">
		<text>
			A popular artefact in the Zone, valued for its energizing properties. However, it has adverse effects on the body with prolonged use, hindering blood clotting and increasing the bleeding rate of open wounds. Being a powerful resistor, it shields its user from lethal doses of electricity. It also absorbs heat and conveys it to other objects. Extremely light and portable. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] low tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] regenerative artefact\n
			%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] containable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_dummy_dummy_name">
		<text>Shell</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_dummy_descr">
		<text>
			Composed of two bluish disks connected by semitransparent material of unknown nature. Initially considered devoid of useful properties, it was recently discovered to increase stamina recovery, sometimes inducing hyperactivity. However, it reduces the number of platelets in blood, increasing the bleeding rate. Provides considerable psy protection and absorbs electromagnetic interference, acting as a grounding material. Catches fire or spontaneously combusts when exposed to open flame. Extremely light and portable. Radiation output is average on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] medium tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] regenerative artefact\n
			%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] containable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_ice_name">
		<text>Snowflake</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ice_descr">
		<text>
			Also known as "Radioactive Snowflake," this artefact resembles a white Kolobok. Significantly increases muscle tone, greatly improving stamina recovery. Known for its high radioactivity, stalkers with it are sometimes jokingly called "Radioactive Snowflakes." Increases endurance and offers high protection against electricity, but constant radiation exposure is deadly. Interacts with surrounding energy sources, absorbing and amplifying their effects, making it dangerous in heat, toxic areas, and psy-fields. Light and easy to carry. Radiation output is high on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] high tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] regenerative artefact\n
			%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] containable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_soul_name">
		<text>Soul</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_soul_descr">
		<text>
			A unique organic artefact secreting a slimy goo that dramatically increases wound recovery rate. Valued for its reasonable price and attractive appearance, making it a collector's item. Applying the goo to wounds soothes pain and speeds up healing. Reduces effects of psy-waves and their damage to the brain. However, it drains power from its user. Not very heavy due to low density. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] low tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] regenerative artefact\n
			%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] containable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_fuzz_kolobok_name">
		<text>Kolobok</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fuzz_kolobok_descr">
		<text>
			A relatively rare artefact formation in chemical areas, Kolobok heals most wounds and stops bleeding in minutes. Rumoured to modify the bearer's genetic code, though unproven. It interacts with radioactive particles, making it dangerous in radiation fields. Reduces energy recovery due to sharp needle-like appendages causing small, quickly healing wounds that reduce stamina. Weakens protection against heat and acids due to high flammability. Lightweight and not burdensome to carry. Radiation output is average on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] medium tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] regenerative artefact\n
			%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] containable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_glass_name">
		<text>Firefly</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_glass_descr">
		<text>
			Firefly interacts with unknown fields, speeding up tissue and organ regeneration and normalizing metabolic processes. Can get a badly wounded stalker back on his feet in minutes. However, it can combust when exposed to potent radioactive sources. Weakens the body and increases bleeding rate during healing. Drains stamina and decreases stamina recovery significantly. Rare and highly sought after. Radiation output is high on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] high tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] regenerative artefact\n
			%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] containable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_compass_name">
		<text>Compass</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_compass_descr">
		<text>
			A very rare artefact capable of locating gaps in anomaly fields, allowing safe traversal. Few know how to handle it properly. Shows unique properties under experiments, such as interacting with moving objects, causing them to disappear or teleport. Weakens the body by draining stamina and increasing bleeding rate. Emits dangerous levels of radiation, causing death within minutes when held near the body. Radiation output is highest on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] top tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] gravitational artefact\n
			%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] containable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_oasis_heart_name">
		<text>Heart of the Oasis</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_oasis_heart_descr">
		<text>
			Found at the centre of the legendary Oasis, this artefact is a crystallised plant with healing properties. Dramatically increases wound recovery and provides strong energy to the body. Highly sensitive to outer energy sources and surrounding environment, making interaction with anomaly fields deadly. Radiation output is highest on the artefact radiation scale. A true miracle of the Zone, it is highly prized for its remarkable healing capabilities.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] top tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] regenerative artefact\n
			%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] containable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>


	<string id="st_af_death_lamp_name">
		<text>Death Lamp</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_death_lamp_descr">
		<text>
			"Big, red, and cursed." This is how the locals describe the Death Lamp, also known as the "Seed of Satan." Many traders believe the rumours surrounding the artefact, thus refusing to buy it. Discovered a few years ago by three experienced stalkers, two of whom were found dead with horrific expressions after delivering it to the Ecologists in Yantar. The fate of the third stalker remains unknown. Members of the science team reported nightmare disorder after studying the artefact. The Death Lamp drains vitality and willpower from the user, inducing dizziness and fainting in extreme cases. Radiation output is highest on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] high tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] psychoactive artefact\n
			%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] containable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_monolith_name">
		<text>Volat Emerald</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_monolith_descr">
		<text>
			A unique artefact rarely found outside the northernmost parts of the Zone. Projects a non-contact field that inhibits nearby anomalous phenomena, providing notable protection against most environmental hazards. Can be safely handled without lead containers. However, holding it makes your flesh feel dry and flaky, bones hard and stiff, and ligaments squeaky and brittle. Thick armour or great supernatural vitality is needed for anyone intending to wear this artefact into battle. Origins of artefacts like this are a mystery. Radiation output is highest on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] top tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] gravitational artefact\n
			%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_black_name">
		<text>Black Stone</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_black_descr">
		<text>
			A mysterious formation with an unnaturally dark appearance, cold and slightly vibrating to the touch. The Black Stone artefact seems to protect its user against different kinds of harms, though its exact beneficial properties seem to vary. Carrying the artefact has irreversible negative effects on the body and prolonged use will slowly kill the owner. The method this occurs is unknown, some speculate it is somehow directly draining the life force, absorbing it into itself. There are suspicions among scientific circles that the artefact is a shard of the Monolith itself.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] high tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] psychoactive artefact\n
			%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>


	<!--
		MLR
	-->

	<string id="st_af_misery_bread_name">
		<text>Strange Bread</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_misery_bread_descr">
		<text>An unassuming piece of bread that appears well-preserved on the outside but is completely hardened and unnaturally dense when touched.It was likely formed in gravitational anomalies and was possible created from the compression of multiple loafs into one. Although it potentially holds the nutritional value of an entire bakery, consumption is highly discouraged. The bread does emit a low level of radiation.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] very low tier artefact\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] gravitational artefact\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<!--
		NEW ARTEFACTS
	-->

	<string id="st_af_cocoon_name">
		<text>Cocoon</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cocoon_descr">
		<text>
		A small, irregularly-shaped artefact formed in gravitational anomalies. The exterior structure resembles caterpillar silk, giving it its name. When close to the body, Cocoon reacts to blunt or cutting trauma, spreading a cocoon-like substance over the user that protects from further damage. However, this protection limits the movement of the user each time the artefact activates and the protective layer thickens. Radiation output is average on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] low tier artefact\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] gravitational artefact\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_cell_name">
		<text>Cell</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cell_descr">
		<text>
			An artefact formed in gravitational anomalies, likely due to intense localized magnetic fields. Its interior structure spins perpetually on its axis as long as it is not disturbed. Cell has one noteworthy property: any fast-moving objects in its proximity get partially disintegrated, releasing a hefty amount of radioactive particles. Some stalkers use this to their advantage, preferring to deal with radiation sickness later rather than getting hit by a bullet. Radiation output is high on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] medium tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] gravitational artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_fountain_name">
		<text>Fountain</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fountain_descr">
		<text>
			A common artefact formed in gravitational anomalies. Its bizarre shape makes it highly valued by collectors. Some stalkers claim that possessing this artefact helps them strike better deals with traders, although merchants prefer not to discuss it. The exact mechanism of this effect remains unconfirmed. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] low tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] gravitational artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_spaika_name">
		<text>Spike</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_spaika_descr">
		<text>
			A common artefact formed in gravitational anomalies, resembling petrified wood or bone. Stalkers report that it calms them down and helps them focus in stressful combat situations, improving their aim. However, they also claim the artefact gets 'angry' when they miss their shots, leading to fears of Zone-induced schizophrenia. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] low tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] gravitational artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_signet_name">
		<text>Signet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_signet_descr">
		<text>
			An artefact that appears to be a warped metal nut, occasionally called an "Amulet." Some stalkers keep their Signets instead of selling them, claiming it helps them relax and regenerate after dangerous raids into the Zone. The exact mechanism behind this effect is unknown. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] low tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] psychoactive artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_repei_name">
		<text>Thistle</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_repei_descr">
		<text>
			A common artefact spawned in gravitational anomalies. Despite their prickly appearance, Thistles do not penetrate flesh or damage the body. They react with heavy metals, especially lead, causing bullets shot by the user to become serrated and create heavier bleeding wounds. Bullets near a Thistle will twitch upon contact with iron in human blood, making wounds painful and hard to close. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] low tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] gravitational artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_bat_name">
		<text>Bat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_bat_descr">
		<text>
			A rare and beautiful artefact, consisting of two irregularly-shaped "wings" protecting a lustrous spherical core. Does not emit radiation and is quite heavy. Experienced artefact hunters use its special ability: when activated and placed near another artefact, Bat will extend its "wings," grab the artefact, and force it into its core. The shell then turns to dust, revealing an artefact with stronger properties or a completely different one. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] medium tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] psychoactive artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_sun_name">
		<text>Sun</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_sun_descr">
		<text>
			A rare artefact highly appreciated by collectors. Its exterior shell is unremarkable, but if cracked like a geode, it reveals a swirling luminous core emitting warm yellow light. Suns thrive in actual sunlight, giving users energy when exposed. However, when kept away from natural light, they drain energy from nearby living things. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] medium tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] psychoactive artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>


	<string id="st_af_ear_name">
		<text>Heart</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ear_descr">
		<text>
			A bizarrely-shaped artefact whose crystalline core resembles a miniature human circulatory system. Rumoured to heal dying creatures and people, the interest in obtaining these artefacts has skyrocketed both for sale and for ensuring survival inside the Zone. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] low tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] health artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_chelust_name">
		<text>Chain</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_chelust_descr">
		<text>
			An unusual circular artefact that generates a strong gravitational field when untouched. Despite its weight, it provides minor tiredness and pain alleviation. Those devoted to Vyraj and The Masters can truly realise the artefact's potential. Radiation output is average on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] medium tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] gravitational artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_atom_name">
		<text>Atom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_atom_descr">
		<text>
			A rare artefact resembling the old Bohr model of an atom. Though not radioactive, it produces a small amount of heat. It is valuable to collectors and scientists for its shape and properties. Stalkers suffering from heavy radiation exposure seem rejuvenated when using this artefact, though the effect diminishes over time as does the radiation in their bodies. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] low tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] stamina artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_lighthouse_name">
		<text>Beacon</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_lighthouse_descr">
		<text>
			A clotted mass of superdense ferrous metals, one of the most mysterious artefacts in the Zone. In its active state, it detects when one living thing kills another, no matter the distance, as long as the intent and causality are clear. The murderer is almost instantly 'teleported' to where the victim drew their last breath. Its inner workings baffle even the greatest minds in modern science. Radiation output is high on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] medium tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] psychoactive artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_fire_loop_name">
		<text>Knot</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fire_loop_descr">
		<text>
			Formed in the extreme heat of thermal anomalies, various legends surround this artefact, often deterring stalkers from picking it up. Once activated, Knot always returns to its owner, who can never get rid of it. Some sources talk about superhuman abilities, hearing voices, reckless behaviour, and strange disappearances. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] very low tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] thermal artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_zhelch_name">
		<text>Scar</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_zhelch_descr">
		<text>
			An artefact that embodies the saying "a sound mind in a sound body." Initially used by stalkers to heal wounds and explore mind-altering anomalies, over time, it showed a sinister side. Users exhibited erratic behaviour, especially when recovering from serious injuries. Few are brave enough to use Scars now, with veterans telling chilling stories about its effects around campfires. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] very low tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] psychoactive artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_sandstone_name">
		<text>Sandstone</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_sandstone_descr">
		<text>
			Formed in extreme temperature anomalies, Sandstone possesses an intelligence that allows it to identify a user's weapon. It links itself to the weapon and seeks out an anomaly, infusing lethal elements with corresponding anomalous properties, making them much more damaging. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] very low tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] thermal artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_kislushka_name">
		<text>Sourpuss</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_kislushka_descr">
		<text>
			A hollow spherical artefact resembling a transparent parchment. Covered with a film, it activates when covered in warm blood, using the user's energy to excrete a stimulant that helps bleeding wounds clot and close faster. Popular in the medical world, it fetches a nice price. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] very low tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] health artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_black_angel_name">
		<text>Black Angel</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_black_angel_descr">
		<text>
			An artefact of anomalous minerals twisted into an ominous semi-symmetrical formation. Despite emitting no heat or radiation, it can condense water vapor into steam. When hit by a bullet, it detects the shot's origin and redirects the potential damage back to the shooter. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] medium tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] psychoactive artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_grapes_name">
		<text>Grapes</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_grapes_descr">
		<text>
			A heavy artefact sometimes found in gravitational anomalies, resembling drops of green-tinted amber twisted together. Recently confirmed to activate near ongoing digestion, stimulating metabolism to heal more effectively. Previously considered hearsay, this ability has been validated by scientists. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] very low tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] health artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_skull_miser_name">
		<text>Miser's Skull</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_skull_miser_descr">
		<text>
			A light and fragile artefact consisting of interlinked strands of anomalous plant fibers. Favoured by various scum in the Zone and sometimes referred to as a "Small Wish Granter." When the user kills someone by damaging their brain, the Zone rewards them with currency around the victim. Some believe it's the Zone's way of encouraging murder for peace, while others think it attracts people with riches. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] very low tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] psychoactive artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>


	<string id="st_af_star_phantom_name">
		<text>Phantom Star</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_star_phantom_descr">
		<text>
			This artefact appears to be a plasma-like substance suspended within a striated transparent shell. It generates a weak gravitational field, making it difficult to hold still or balance. When active, Phantom Star affects the minds of nearby living beings, causing the user to become unnoticed until a forceful interaction occurs. It also prevents the owner from engaging in hostility. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] very low tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] psychoactive artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_medallion_name">
		<text>Medal</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_medallion_descr">
		<text>
			An artefact consisting of a small hoop embedded with four triangular shapes and a central sphere. Medal defies logical explanation. It can detect if the user is part of a group and has a mysterious ability to transfer damage intended for the user to someone else in their company. While desirable for selfish reasons, it is not well-received by other stalkers. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] medium tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] psychoactive artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_peas_name">
		<text>Moon</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_peas_descr">
		<text>
			An artefact shaped like a lunar crescent. Its exterior shell continuously generates a dim light that stimulates the user. At night, it makes the user feel rested and energetic, but during daylight, it has the reverse effect. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] very low tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] psychoactive artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_generator_name">
		<text>Generator</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_generator_descr">
		<text>
			An anomalous disk that generates a strong, small electromagnetic field. Not radioactive but can 'spin' perpetually on its axis when the user moves fast. The energy from the artefact connects to nearby drained batteries and devices, restoring their power slowly. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] medium tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] electrical artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_ball_name">
		<text>Ball</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ball_descr">
		<text>
			Despite appearing as a mottled ball of dirt and rock, this artefact is unusually light and bouncy. Believed to be a product of electrical anomalies, it generates a force that can repel living creatures, excluding humans. Activation requires a fast and strong movement between the user and the target, often leading to stalkers kicking mutants. While not advised, it can be effective in dire situations. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] very low tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] electrical artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_fonar_name">
		<text>Lamp</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fonar_descr">
		<text>
			This light, glassy artefact emits a modest amount of near-ultraviolet light. It reacts oddly with certain radio waves, making sources of various transmissions glow. Stalkers use this property to search for hidden stashes at night. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] very low tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] electrical artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_tapeworm_name">
		<text>Tapeworm</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_tapeworm_descr">
		<text>
			A pure silicon dioxide artefact, twisted into an unusual shape by gravitational anomalies. When activated, it sends a strong electric shock to any living creature attacking the user via direct contact, stunning them temporarily. However, it does not distinguish between attackers, including the user. Highly valued by mutant hunters. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] very low tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] electrical artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_moh_name">
		<text>Moss</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_moh_descr">
		<text>
			An artefact formed in electric anomalies. Despite its sharp, jagged appearance, it is soft and pleasing to the touch. When attached to the belt, it detects the contents of the user's stomach. Upon recognizing any raw meat of Zone origin within the digestive system, it activates, using the flesh's energy to fuel stimulating effects, depending on the type of creature consumed. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] very low tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] electrical artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>


	<string id="st_af_serofim_name">
		<text>Seraphim</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_serofim_descr">
		<text>
			Seraphim was long considered nothing but a pretty bauble to be sold. This changed when a veteran group of stalkers returned from a deep excursion with a remarkable story. They were ambushed by a sniper, and their leader was instantly killed, his skull split in half. While sending suppressive fire, they saw his belt light up, and he stood up without a scratch, his helmet still showing entry and exit holes from the sniper's bullet. They retreated and found that the Seraphim artefact the leader kept as a lucky charm was gone, leaving only glowing dust. Since then, those who heard the story hold their Seraphims dear, believing the artefact will bring them back from the dead. No one has been brave enough to test this. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] very low tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] psychoactive artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_elektron_name">
		<text>Electron</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_elektron_descr">
		<text>
			This artefact is a product of electrical anomalies. It is extremely heavy despite its small size and has a unique property. It combines common electro anomalies with other electric charges nearby, using the anomaly as a power source. Fascinatingly, the artefact considers the human body a battery, converting energy into one usable by human cells during physical activity. Despite the painful experience, users enjoy being tireless for a short period. Side effects? Well, none have been reported so far. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] low tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] electrical artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_kogot_name">
		<text>Claw</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_kogot_descr">
		<text>
			A beautiful glass-like artefact occasionally commonly found in and around electrostatic anomalies. When used, it fills its user with a combination of rage and a desire to attack enemies directly, reinvigorating them in the process. A common story associated with this artefact involves a rookie who found a Claw with his friend, only to be chased by a pack of hungry dogs moments later. The "friend" shot the rookie and took off, leaving him to certain death. To everyone's surprise, the betrayed stalker returned to camp, perfectly healthy despite his clothes being torn from dog bites, with only a knife and the artefact hanging by his belt. What happened to the backstabber is better left unsaid. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] very low tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] electrical artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_dragon_eye_name">
		<text>Dragon's Eye</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dragon_eye_descr">
		<text>
			A jagged artefact with the outer appearance of a reptile's eye, formed in thermal anomalies. It has a dangerous and volatile property. When the user secures a kill, there's a small chance for a violent explosion within the victim's body, harming anyone nearby. Superstitious stalkers say it's the Zone itself violently ripping out the souls of the fallen. Most prefer to avoid using it due to the stories of people getting caught in such explosions at unfortunate distances. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] very low tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] thermal artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>


	<string id="st_af_vaselisk_name">
		<text>Basilisk</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_vaselisk_descr">
		<text>
			A dense, rugged artefact with a hard, scaly surface, reminiscent of its mythical namesake. Its primary function is to absorb and dissipate kinetic energy, providing significant resistance to blunt force, cutting, and piercing damage. Despite its durability, it does not offer any regenerative or offensive capabilities. Highly valued by stalkers who prioritize physical protection over other benefits. One of the few artefacts in the Zone that effectively protects against all kinds of physical influences on its user. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] high tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] regenerative artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_geliy_name">
		<text>Helium</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_geliy_descr">
		<text>
			A bright, misshapen artefact found in electrostatic anomalies. It emits a luminous gas that benefits the body by enhancing physical endurance and overall vitality. This gas alleviates fatigue and improves the respiratory system, making it highly sought after. Its efficiency and demand make it valuable both inside and outside the Zone. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] high tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] regenerative artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_gimlet_name">
		<text>Gimlet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_gimlet_descr">
		<text>
			An artefact with strange bowl-shaped petals that are able to release a powerful stimulant vapor that alters the balance of human hormones. Though its practical by stalkers is questionable, it is highly sought after for medical research due to its unique properties and potential in research and development. The vapor can enhance physical and mental performance temporarily, but its long-term effects are unknown. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] high tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] psychoactive artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_arty_save">
		<text>Eye of the Noosphere</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_arty_save_descr">
		<text>
			An extremely powerful artefact with a rounded and smooth appearance. One of the most mysterious artefacts in the Zone, the Eye of the Noosphere can transport its wielder back in time, even under extreme circumstances. It has reportedly even been used to escape death.  A tight squeeze of the artefact activates its ability, creating a restoration point to go back to on activation or death. Frequent use can cause the artefact to change colour, but if discharged too frequently it may cease to function altogether. The Eye gradually restores its power over time, supposedly being fuelled by the anomalous energy of the Zone.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] top tier artefact\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] unclassified artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<!--
		MISSION ARTEFACTS
	-->

	<string id="st_af_ah_s1">
		<text>Aroth-8</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ah_s1_descr">
		<text>
			An experimental and unstable artefact created by artificial means. The circumstances of its formation are unknown. It seems to improve the natural healing process of the body via methods unknown to science. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] unclassified artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_ah_g1">
		<text>Easy</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ah_g1_descr">
		<text>
			A lump of shriveled clay and organic debris. Separation of individual lumps of material seems impossible due to the presence of an unknown and incredibly strong binding agent. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] unclassified artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_ah_g2">
		<text>Easy</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ah_g2_descr">
		<text>
			A lump of shriveled clay and organic debris. Separation of individual lumps of material seems impossible due to the presence of an unknown and incredibly strong binding agent. It gives off a slightly disorienting effect that can cause headaches. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] unclassified artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_ah_o1">
		<text>Magnet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ah_o1_descr">
		<text>
			An artefact created in fire anomalies, consisting mostly of iron, bismuth, cadmium, and nickel. Magnet is characterized by its metallic sheen and slightly irregular shape, resembling a fused mass of metals. The artefact's primary feature is its ability to absorb heat from its surroundings. It also creates a cooling effect, protecting the user from thermal burns and heatstroke. Additionally, the artefact is known to slightly reduce ambient radiation levels. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] unclassified artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_ah_o2">
		<text>Magnet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ah_o2_descr">
		<text>
			An artefact created in fire anomalies, consisting mostly of iron, bismuth, cadmium, and nickel. Magnet is characterized by its metallic sheen and slightly irregular shape, resembling a fused mass of metals. The artefact's primary feature is its ability to absorb heat from its surroundings. It also creates a cooling effect, protecting the user from thermal burns and heatstroke. Additionally, the artefact is known to slightly reduce ambient radiation levels. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] unclassified artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>



	<string id="st_af_ah_r1">
		<text>Mushroom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ah_r1_descr">
		<text>
			An artefact found only in the Dead Forest, south of Lab X-9, containing mostly plant matter. It is believed that the strong psy-fields it was subjugated to during its formation have heavily influenced its shape and properties. When worn by a human subject, the artefact seems to provide a boost in perceived vitality and accelerated wound healing. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] unclassified artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_ah_r2">
		<text>Mushroom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ah_r2_descr">
		<text>
			An artefact found only in the Dead Forest, south of Lab X-9, containing mostly plant matter. It is believed that the strong psy-fields it was subjugated to during its formation have heavily influenced its shape and properties. When worn by a human subject, the artefact seems to provide a boost in perceived vitality and accelerated wound healing. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] unclassified artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_ah_r3">
		<text>Mushroom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ah_r3_descr">
		<text>
			An artefact found only in the Dead Forest, south of Lab X-9, containing mostly plant matter. It is believed that the strong psy-fields it was subjugated to during its formation have heavily influenced its shape and properties. When worn by a human subject, the artefact seems to provide a boost in perceived vitality and accelerated wound healing. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] unclassified artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_ah_r4">
		<text>Mushroom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ah_r4_descr">
		<text>
			An artefact found only in the Dead Forest, south of Lab X-9, containing mostly plant matter. It is believed that the strong psy-fields it was subjugated to during its formation have heavily influenced its shape and properties. When worn by a human subject, the artefact seems to provide a boost in perceived vitality and accelerated wound healing. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] unclassified artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_ah_r5">
		<text>Mushroom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ah_r5_descr">
		<text>
			An artefact found only in the Dead Forest, south of Lab X-9, containing mostly plant matter. It is believed that the strong psy-fields it was subjugated to during its formation have heavily influenced its shape and properties. When worn by a human subject, the artefact seems to provide a boost in perceived vitality and accelerated wound healing. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] unclassified artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_ah_e1">
		<text>Souvenir</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ah_e1_descr">
		<text>
			An artefact with the appearance of a shard of Silica Quartz that is found exclusively in electro anomalies. The materials contained within are remarkably pure, ranging from 99.5% to 99.9% purity. When in proximity of human subjects, it induces a temporary feeling of youthfulness. The origins and mechanisms of its psychic influence are unknown. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] unclassified artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_ah_e2">
		<text>Souvenir</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ah_e2_descr">
		<text>
			An artefact with the appearance of a shard of Silica Quartz that is found exclusively in electro anomalies. The materials contained within are remarkably pure, ranging from 99.5% to 99.9% purity. When in proximity of human subjects, it induces a temporary feeling of youthfulness. The origins and mechanisms of its psychic influence are unknown. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] unclassified artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_ah_h1">
		<text>Sponge</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ah_h1_descr">
		<text>
			An artefact with the appearance of a lump of shriveled clay and organic debris. Separation of individual lumps of material seems impossible due to the presence of an unknown and incredibly strong binding agent. The gravitational properties of the artefact seem to have effects similar to hemophilia, causing increased bleeding. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] unclassified artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_ah_h2">
		<text>Sponge</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ah_h2_descr">
		<text>
			An artefact with the appearance of a lump of shriveled clay and organic debris. Separation of individual lumps of material seems impossible due to the presence of an unknown and incredibly strong binding agent. The gravitational properties of the artefact seem to have effects similar to hemophilia, causing increased bleeding. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] unclassified artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_ah_f1">
		<text>Talking Stone</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ah_f1_descr">
		<text>
			A very rare artefact with an unnaturally symmetrical shape, seemingly of organic origin. When activated and placed in a suitable containment device, it increases the structural and tensile strength of any material it comes in proximity with. The effect appears to be lasting and can also be directed with the appropriate equipment. The artefact was named "Talking Stone" as it frequently releases measurable but barely audible and unintelligible whispers. Radiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] unclassified artefact\n
			%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] uncontainable artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>


</string_table>