<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<string_table>

	<!-- DRX Storyline Documents Quest Item -->

	<string id="drx_sl_quest_item_1_name">
		<text>Encrypted Documents</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_quest_item_1_desc">
		<text>A folder containing an assortment of encrypted documents. The pages appear to be covered in ciphers and cryptographic notations, most definitely hiding sensitive information. Judging by some of the printed logos and legible names, the documents may encompass lab reports detailing experimental findings, scientific data on anomalous activities, or financial records involving covert transactions to fund operations inside the exclusion zone. The condition of the documents hints at them dating at least some years back. Decoding these papers could unveil critical insights into secretive projects or undisclosed activities within the region.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<!-- DRX Storyline Locked Case Quest Item -->

	<string id="drx_sl_quest_item_2_name">
		<text>Locked Case</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_quest_item_2_desc">
		<text>A heavy case with an integrated locking mechanism. The exterior of the case is made from hardened steel with additional titanium alloy plating for reinforcement against physical damage. The surface is covered in scratches, dents, and smudges of dirt. It has some scratched stickers on the outside, most of them illegible. The weight and secure construction of the case indicate something of significant value inside.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<!-- DRX Storyline PDA Quest Item -->

	<string id="drx_sl_quest_item_3_name">
		<text>PDA (Locked)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_quest_item_3_desc">
		<text>A portable hand-held computer that appears to have been locked with an unknown passkey. \n \nThis series of PDAs was developed specifically for use in the Zone and is one of the few electronic devices able to operate without significant interference. All PDAs come in a durable casing, are dust-resistant and waterproof up to a few meters of depth and have special internal shielding to electrical pulses common around anomalies and during emissions. All models come equipped with a GPS module that provides highly accurate geolocation and bearing by evaluating signal pings from a number of antennae and relays inside the perimeter, making it the only viable electronic means of location.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="bad_psy_helmet_name">
		<text>Psy-Helmet (Uncalibrated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bad_psy_helmet_desc">
		<text>A prototype psy protection helmet, an advanced piece of equipment intended to shield the wearer from specific types of psy emissions. The outer shell is made from a durable composite material, lined with layers of a metallic mesh and lead inserts. Includes an integrated electronic module that emits counter-frequency signals to known psy waves, effectively cancelling their harmful effects while the device is powered. The prototype was developed by scientists at the mobile lab at Lake Yantar for exploratory missions into areas known for high levels of psy-emissions, such as the Brain Scorcher and the vicinity of the Miracle Machine. This model has only gone through a baseline callibration process and can only provide limited protection without further tuning.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] limited psy protection\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="good_psy_helmet_name">
		<text>Psy-Helmet (Calibrated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="good_psy_helmet_desc">
		<text>A prototype psy protection helmet, an advanced piece of equipment intended to shield the wearer from specific types of psy emissions. The outer shell is made from a durable composite material, lined with layers of a metallic mesh and lead inserts. Includes an integrated electronic module that emits counter-frequency signals to known psy waves, effectively cancelling their harmful effects while the device is powered. The prototype was developed by scientists at the mobile lab at Lake Yantar for exploratory missions into areas known for high levels of psy-emissions, such as the Brain Scorcher and the vicinity of the Miracle Machine. This model has gone through an extensive callibration process and can provide moderate protection as-is.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] limited psy protection\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="cit_doctors_key_name">
		<text>Room 26 Key</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cit_doctors_key_desc">
		<text>A key with "Hotel Polissya - Room 26" engraved on the side. The key is made from sturdy brass with a nickel plating, a typical choice for apartment keys made in the 1980s. The shaft has precise notches and grooves, normal for standard pin tumbler locks. Despite looking severely weathered, the key appears to be in usable condition.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cit_doctors_key_short_desc">
		<text>A key with "Hotel Polissya - Room 26" engraved on the side. The key is made from sturdy brass with a nickel plating, a typical choice for apartment keys made in the 1980s. The shaft has precise notches and grooves, normal for standard pin tumbler locks. Despite looking severely weathered, the key appears to be in usable condition.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="item_docs_hiden_pri_name">
		<text>Strelok's Manuscript</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_docs_hiden_pri_desc">
		<text>A worn manuscript in leather binding, Strelok's notebook is a relic of immense value to any Stalker. Handwritten by Strelok himself, the pages are filled with cryptic notes, personal accounts from many different points in time, hand-drawn maps, and observations that seem to hint at the Zone's deepest secrets. The leather cover is scuffed and aged, bearing the marks of countless expeditions. On many of the pages, the ink has faded and some loose paperclips seem to indicate that some previously attached pictures could have been lost with time. Judging from its raw content, it'd take another highly experienced stalker to make sense of it all.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="cit_doctors_pda_name">
		<text>Doctor's Notes</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cit_doctors_pda_desc">
		<text>Some notes about the Doctor's conspiracy theories.\n \n
		There are rumours that the Agroprom Institute was used as a front for an unofficial lab in the years preceding the 2006 accident. This lab hosted a number of very unusual experiments. The traders have dug up a lot of information about these laboratories.\n
		I met with the Barkeep. He says he sent Duty scouts to get into the underground vaults of the Dark Valley, called X-18, but they disappeared. There are other rumors regarding a 'psi-brain' mechanism. The whole neighbourhood in Yantar is under the influence of that device. It zombified everyone who came within range. There is another mechanism in the Red Forest radar underground, called lab X-19. That is likely to be the Brain Scorcher.\n
		There is evidence to suggest that the presence of the Brain Scorcher intentionally blocks the road to the North, but no one knows exactly what it is. The Barkeep believes that the Brain Scorcher is man-made, and these mechanisms are not always operating at full strength. He thinks there are periods when their power is lowered to cool down the apparatus. It's time to visit all the underground laboratories in the Zone and find out what kind of secrets they are hiding. I'm too old for this shit. I wish Strelok was still around...\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="item_decoder_name">
		<text>Decoder</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_decoder_desc">
		<text>An electronic lock decoder device designed specifically for bypassing electronic locks installed in the Chernobyl NPP years after the incident. This compact, handheld unit comes in a solid plastic casing with a digital display and a series of input buttons. Although untested, the device may allow access to previously sealed sections of the NPP and connected underground areas.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="pri_decoder_docs_conclusion_txt">
		<text>The manuscript contains a short report on how Fang and Strelok infiltrated a hidden laboratory and their journey there. It mentions of a large Monolith presence in and around the Chernobyl NPP, more specifically under the concrete sarcophagus. This suggests it may be their base of operations with the intent to hide something. Reading further, it states that they discovered a laboratory hidden further to the north under the generators, however they were unable to gain access at the time of writing as they required the use of a decoder.\n \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="item_quest_case_02_name">
		<text>Military Documents</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_quest_case_02_desc">
		<text>A fireproof briefcase containing a collection of classified military documents and reports on investigations performed near Agroprom. The reports talk in detail about how machinery and equipment have gone missing from the institute and how the results of the investigations on their whereabouts were apparently falsified. Many of the pages are severely aged, some have become illegible.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="item_doc_x18_name">
		<text>Biology Research Report</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_doc_x18_desc">
		<text>The report details the study of biological samples sent from lab X-18. The samples were subjected to informational field effects of varying intensities. The report meticulously describes the mutation of living beings following exposure to emissions. The report dates back many years and shows severe signs of wear on most of its pages. Some hand-written additions can no longer be deciphered.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="item_doc_x16_name">
		<text>Psy Research Documents</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_doc_x16_desc">
		<text>A binder of research documents from unknown authors, mostly referring to discoveries concerning the ability of living creatures in the exclusion zone being able to generate directed psy-emissions. It includes a number of field report copies, photographs taken from various mutated creatures, and tables listing measurements of psy fields. A second section details experiments focussed around a large psy field emitting "brain" that was grown as part of research trials conducted in lab X-16 in the past.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="item_doc_x10_name">
		<text>Rainbow Emitter Documents</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_doc_x10_desc">
		<text>A binder containing documents about a device called the "Rainbow Emitter". They detail technical characteristics of a specialized antenna constructed inside the Zone and some deviations from its original planned design. Other pages show schematics, engineering notes, and performance analyses, some log adjustments made and unexpected effects encountered during development and early tests. A note on the reverse side of the last document indicates these records were prepared in Lab X-19, the apparent point of origin to most of the listed work. Scuffs and faded ink on many pages hint at extensive handling and years of storage.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="item_doc_x8_name">
		<text>Transfer Order</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_doc_x8_desc">
		<text>A collection of documents detailing the transfer of the research team and all materials from one laboratory to another complex far to the north. Pages further appear to be personal correspondence about pending research matters relating to the influence of the noosphere. A hand-written reminder says that the passcode to the laboratory was set to the date of the accident in the format "ddmmyyyy". The last item in the folder is a picture of the research team, annotated "N.A. Lebedev, E.F. Kalancha, V.I. Suslov".\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="item_doc_jup_ug_name">
		<text>Experiment Notebook</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_doc_jup_ug_desc">
		<text>A notebook containing detailed logs and reports around an experiment assessing a psy field's effect on an object in another hemisphere. A group of scientists in the Caribbean received the signal but it was altered in a strange way, as though corrected by someone. Though, a possible explanation is that the noosphere theory is correct and the changes were made by the noosphere. The notebook shows severe signs of wear and appears to be many years old.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>


	<string id="item_doc_mon_con_name">
		<text>Prototype Weapon Report</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_doc_mon_con_name_desc">
		<text>A report comprising of a number of documents describing the operating mechanism and main technical characteristics of an advanced electromagnetic device. Some schematics further in appear to indicate that part of the research was focussed on the development of high power weaponry. There is a note inside the documents which reads: "Documents must be returned to the central laboratory at X-8. I will be busy, so deliver them yourself. — N. Lebedev".\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="quest_package_name">
		<text>Package</text>
	</string>
	<string id="quest_package_desc">
		<text>An unmarked package, likely containing sensitive documents or important items. It appears to have been left outside for some time and shows signs of wear on the exterior, with smudges, dents, and scratches indicating rough handling and some exposure to the elements. The seams seem to be in good condition and the contents are probably still intact.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_jup_b32_scanner_device_name">
		<text>Anomalous Activity Scanner</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_b32_scanner_device_desc">
		<text>An anomalous activity scanner for stationary use. It internally combining an artifact detector, power source, and a powerful transmitter. Its core functionality is based on the advanced Veles detector platform. The device sends electromagnetic pulses via a rotating emitter to detect anomalous objects by analyzing alterations in frequency, amplitude, and phase shift. It also generates a low-energy electromagnetic field, using sensors to measure distortions, allowing it to detect a wide range of anomalous formations. The scanner is outfitted with extra processing components and can approximate areas of anomalous activity with a higher fidelity than portable detectors. It is built in a durable, weather-resistant case. The scanner is meant for field work only, it automatically relays any gathered data to the owners receiver on a pre-programmed frequency.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- MLR -->

	<string id="mlr_strelok_item_01">
		<text>Worn Notebook</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mlr_strelok_item_01_desc">
		<text>A worn notebook, likely owned by Strelok. The tattered pages and damaged cover point to extensive use. Inside are detailed notes and hand-drawn maps around accessing an underground complex called X-18. Instructions include proposed routes, some crossed out with further annotations on the side. Other pages list suspected security measures and potential hazards. Parts of the notebook are dedicated to information on what is likely still buried in the depths of X-18.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="blackbox_mlr">
		<text>Flight Data Recorder</text>
	</string>
	<string id="blackbox_mlr_descr">
		<text>A flight data recorder, also commonly known as a "black box". The device records the status of internal systems and crew conversations, saving vital information in the event of an accident. It is built in a crash-resistant case. Black boxes usually consist of two main components, the Flight Data Recorder (FDR) and the Cockpit Voice Recorder (CVR). The FDR monitors and records numerous flight parameters, such as altitude, airspeed, and engine performance, while the CVR captures audio from cockpit microphones and headsets. This particular box appears to have been removed from a crashed airplane or UAV.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="item_pda_map_mlr_name">
		<text>PDA</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_pda_map_mlr_descr">
		<text>A portable hand-held computer with vital functions for the day to day life in the exclusion zone. This particular PDA is filled with a number of annotated maps and personal notes on a number of regions in the exclusion zone. \n \nThis series of PDAs was developed specifically for use in the Zone and is one of the few electronic devices able to operate without significant interference. All PDAs come in a durable casing, are dust-resistant and waterproof up to a few meters of depth and have special internal shielding to electrical pulses common around anomalies and during emissions. All models come equipped with a GPS module that provides highly accurate geolocation and bearing by evaluating signal pings from a number of antennae and relays inside the perimeter, making it the only viable electronic means of location.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- DRX -->

	<string id="drx_x8_documents_name">
		<text>Antenna Installation Documents</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_x8_documents_desc">
		<text>A folder labeled "X8 Antenna Installation" on its cover. It details design and construction of a massive radar installation, presumably the structure supporting the Brain Scorcher. These papers include schematics, construction blueprints, and technical specifications of the antenna array. The documents describe the immense scale of the installation, with highlights on high power radar and transmission capabilities. Handwritten notes and annotations suggest modifications made during the installation process, potentially to enhance its operational range and effectiveness. The documents are stamped with security classifications, indicating their sensitive nature and the importance of the installation in controlling and manipulating the Zone's anomalous activities.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="drx_x16_documents_name">
		<text>Biological Research</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_x16_documents_desc">
		<text>A tightly packed folder containing documents from Lab X-16, detailing a big number of conducted animal experiments. These documents include comprehensive reports on subjects exposed to varying levels of radiation, active and passive psy fields, and unknown anomalous fields. Charts and graphs illustrate physiological and behavioral changes, while detailed logs provide insight into the progression and outcomes of each experiment. Notes on radiation exposure document severe mutations and health declines, while psy field tests reveal disturbing alterations in brain activity and behavior. There are a few remarks on what the researchers call "zombification". The studies on anomalous fields show unpredictable and often extreme effects, highlighting the dangers and unpredictability of these phenomena. Some animals appear to have vanished entirely in experiments with anomalous fields.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="drx_x18_documents_name">
		<text>Experiment Report: B0-D4</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_x18_documents_desc">
		<text>A folder for an experiment report labeled "B0-D4" on the cover. It contains old documents related to a series of psy-wave resonance experiments. The pages detail the setup, procedure, and some of the findings of the experiment. Researchers investigated the effects of resonant psy-waves on biological subjects, using frequency modulation to try to induce specific psychological and physiological responses. Graphs and data tables list measurements taken from subjects during various trials. There are some handwritten annotations suggesting unexpectedly violent results in some of the attempts. A table marked in red seems to pin-point the recommended minimums and maximums for emissions to be most effective. The last few pages seem to be about hypothetical emitter devices, shielding and wave-cancellation gear, and larger machines.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="drx_x19_documents_name">
		<text>Communication Log (21.03.2006)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_x19_documents_desc">
		<text>A folder containing a printed transcription of a radio transmission between scientist groups from the institute. The transcript seems to have been originally printed in Lab X-19. The last few pages are handwritten remarks between multiple parties about the exchange.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="drx_agr_u_documents_name">
		<text>Agroprom Institute Documents</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_agr_u_documents_desc">
		<text>A loose binder of pages about the Agroprom Research Institute. Contains notes, pictures, and a single marked map related to Agroprom showing surrounding roads, options for shelter, and many identified hazards, including threats from mutants and a nearby military presence. The pictures are mostly grainy photographs of underground tunnels, technical equipment, and concrete structures. Many of the notes indicate the documents may have been prepared by Strelok.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="drx_jup_u_documents_name">
		<text>Transportation Records</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_jup_u_documents_desc">
		<text>A binder of detailed transportation records, an assortment of numbered documents detailing the transport of mechanical equipment and tools to the factory complex in the Jupiter region of the exclusion zone. Included are notes and sketches of an underground tunnel system leading to the eastern side. The overall format and some of the names indicate military involvement.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="lx8_history_documents_name">
		<text>Experiment Logs (11.04.2005)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lx8_history_documents_desc">
		<text>A binder of logs and lab reports, documenting the results of experiments conducted in and before 2005 on novel psy-emitters. The logs include observations, data charts, and analyses of emitter components, power sources, and design variations. Entries record the parameters, outcomes, and issues encountered during the trials. The documents follow noted advancements in emitter technology and many failed attempts at optimizing for efficiency and desired wave signatures.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lx8_history_2_documents_name">
		<text>Experiment Logs (24.09.2005)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lx8_history_2_documents_desc">
		<text>A binder of logs and lab reports, documenting the results of experiments conducted in and before 2005 on different psy-wave applications. The logs include observations, data charts, and analyses of psy-wave effects on biological subjects, categorized by application type. Entries  record the parameters, outcomes, and issues encountered during the trials. The documents describe many setbacks and a few breakthroughs. Many pages detail hypothetical future applications and world-changing deployment plans.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lx8_history_3_documents_name">
		<text>Experiment Logs (02.05.2006)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lx8_history_3_documents_desc">
		<text>A binder of logs and lab reports, documenting the results of a long-term biological experiment conducted in and before 2005. The logs are hard to decipher but appear to detail effects of psy-waves on a biological subject. Entries record the parameters, outcomes, and issues encountered during a huge number of consecutive trials. The ultimate outcome of the experiment is unknown.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<!-- Rioc -->

	<string id="st_rioc_sid">
		<text>Sidorovich's Supplies</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_rioc_sid_desc">
		<text>A sealed container with a few scratched up labels and tape on the exterior, likely a lost shipment belonging to Sidorovich. The container is battered but intact, showing signs of having been carried through rough terrain. The contents are unknown but presumed valuable, likely consisting of supplies or equipment. This shipment is essential for completing a trade or delivery mission.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_rioc_duty">
		<text>Fallen Duty PDA</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_rioc_duty_desc">
		<text>A functional PDA model, holding information that appears to confirm that a missing Duty soldier was killed in action. The device is worn and slightly damaged. The data within includes the last known coordinates and logs of the soldier's final movements. It may offer clues for further investigation or closure for Petrenko. Essential for completing a mission related to the Duty faction.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_rioc_ecolog">
		<text>Prototype Detector Laptop</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_rioc_ecolog_desc">
		<text>A rugged laptop with experimental hardware components for anomalous field analysis. According to ecologists, this is a brand new detector prototype destined to change the world of artefact hunting. The casing is durable and built to withstand environmental hazards. Early testing suggests it has advanced sensitivity and range compared to existing models.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	
	<!-- Lost Zone HB -->

	<string id="st_hb_isg_dushman_intel_name">
		<text>Dushman's Intelligence</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hb_isg_dushman_intel_desc">
		<text>A case containing maps and notes provided by Dushman. These documents are intended to aid UNISG in reducing the risks of future missions. The contents include strategic maps, marked points of interest, and detailed observations about enemy movements and safe routes. The information, if accurate, will be invaluable for planning and executing operations in the Zone.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n		
		</text>
	</string>

	<!-- Lost Zone LL -->

	<string id="item_doc_x8_ll_name">
		<text>X-8 Documents</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_doc_x8_ll_desc">
		<text>
		These documents briefly touch on the results of extensive experiments in psy-research conducted by an unknown group. Most notably, the results seem to confirm the existence of a non-contact field of psychic energy which envelops the Earth and a brief description of the sophisticated machinery that could potentially influence the field.\n
		However, 
		</text>
		<text>These documents summarize extensive psy-research experiments conducted by an unknown group. They confirm the existence of a global psychic energy field and describe machinery capable of influencing it. The bulk of these documents are a long list of human test subjects who were exposed to psy-emissions of various frequencies and intensities. Many were noted to have seemingly developed superhuman endurance, intellect or telepathic abilities during the testing. Some are recorded to have later died, others were transferred, and many were left completely unaccounted for, as if they disappeared or escaped.\n \n
		Scribbled along one of the margins is a cryptic note: "Already we have perverted the human form far beyond recognition for the sake of our vision! How much longer will it be before our hubris and sin catches up to us?"\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="strelok_notes_name">
		<text>Strelok's Notebook</text>
	</string>
	<string id="strelok_notes_desc">
		<text>This notebook belonged to Strelok and contains disjointed and cryptic notes. It reveals his crisis about a major decision made years ago and his plans to resupply at Rostok before heading north. The entries reflect a troubled mind, with scattered thoughts and plans scribbled throughout the pages.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_strelok_pendrive_name">
		<text>Strelok's Flash Drive</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_strelok_pendrive_descr">
		<text>An encrypted flash drive containing backups of Strelok's findings over the years. It holds crucial evidence regarding top secret experiments believed to have created the Zone. The data within could provide insights into the Zone's origins and the experiments conducted there.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<!-- Lost Zone MS -->

	<string id="drekavac_notes_name">
		<text>Drekavac's Notes</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drekavac_notes_desc">
		<text>A collection of hand-written notes, reading: "Finally, after several years of arduous preparation, we can continue the Masters' plan. It's regrettable that so many people don't believe us, but sometimes words aren't enough. They're blinded by base human desires. If they insist on continuing their violent ways, we'll treat them with violence. Maybe then they will understand. The seed of Vyraj is budding, and I'm here to spread the paradise further and further beyond. I am the tip of the spear."\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="chernobog_notes_name">
		<text>Chernobog's Notes</text>
	</string>
	<string id="chernobog_notes_desc">
		<text>A collection of hand-written notes, reading: "The Zone is a miracle. The Masters cleansed us. Soon, we thought, the Zone would cleanse the world. But no. Our small paradise was soon trespassed upon by the flawed people of a sinful world. And, in an act of unthinkable atrocity, the beast named Strelok crippled the valiant Monolith, and entered the Masters' chambers to slay their mortal forms. However, I shall not despair. I cannot let this miracle be consumed by the vice and filth of the unworthy. So we, Sin, must embark upon a quest to fulfil the Masters' wish. We shall wage war upon the violent to bring about eternal peace."\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="attackers_pda_name">
		<text>Sin Leader's PDA</text>
	</string>
	<string id="attackers_pda_desc">
		<text>A functional PDA that appears to have belonged to the squad leader of a member of a faction called "Sin". It contains a map of the Red Forest with several marked locations, one of which remains unchecked. The data suggests the squad was pursuing someone and was close to finding them. Additionally, the PDA holds encrypted information that could be valuable for further analysis.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="contact_lost_pda_name">
		<text>Scout Leader's PDA</text>
	</string>
	<string id="contact_lost_pda_desc">
		<text>A functional PDA that appears to have belonged to the leader of a scout team. It includes recorded information about enemy forces before the scout's untimely demise. The data might be of value to someone investigating the team and their fate.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="vodnik_notes_name">
		<text>Vodnik's Notes</text>
	</string>
	<string id="vodnik_notes_desc">
		<text>A collection of hand-written notes, reading: "Many have joined our cause, whether they understood the magnificence of the Zone from the beginning, or required some explanation. I envy the Founders. They were created by the Masters themselves. They could witness the birth of Vyraj! But they cleansed us, judging us worthy, and they'll cleanse our new brothers. Together, we'll spread the word across the whole world."\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<!-- Lost Zone OA -->

	<string id="special_delivery_case_name">
		<text>Sealed Case</text>
	</string>
	<string id="special_delivery_case_desc">
		<text>A sealed case containing undisclosed contents. It is rather heavy and appears to be in good overall condition, suggesting it holds important or valuable items. Judging by some labels on the bottom of the case, it seems to be related to a special delivery mission.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_army_isg_spy_pendrive_name">
		<text>Undercover Agent's Flash Drive</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_army_isg_spy_pendrive_descr">
		<text>An encrypted flash drive from a UNISG operative, most likely containing critical information on the group's goals, movements, or espionage conducted around the work of other factions. It might include evidence that could exert legal or political pressure to force UN troops out of the Zone. The data within is vital for those looking to undermine UNISG's presence and influence in the area.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="jupiter_documents_name">
		<text>Jupiter Factory Documents</text>
	</string>
	<string id="jupiter_documents_desc">
		<text>A binder of what appear to be confidential documents from the Jupiter factory. They likely detail operations, experimental processes, or security protocols relevant to the factory. These papers are labelled all over that they must not leave a circle of trustees. May be of value to information brokers in the Zone.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="decryption_radio_name">
		<text>Military Radio</text>
	</string>
	<string id="decryption_radio_desc">
		<text>A military-grade radio designed to intercept and decrypt nearby transmissions. Its robust construction ensures durability in the field, and its advanced encryption-breaking capabilities make it a highly valuable tool for gathering intelligence. The device is sure to be valuable to someone in the Zone.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<!-- Chimera Scan -->

	<string id="chimera_scan_device_name">
		<text>Brain Wave Scanner</text>
	</string>
	<string id="chimera_scan_device_desc">
		<text>An advanced scanner device designed to record nearby electromagnetic waves, specifically tuned to isolate the neural oscillations of a chimera specimen. It features precise sensors and advanced filtering technology to capture detailed brain wave patterns. Essential for scientific studies on the behavioral and neurological characteristics of chimeras.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<!-- AH AH -->

	<string id="cs_deshefrator_name">
		<text>Decoder</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cs_deshefrator_desc">
		<text>An advanced decoding device sometimes used by Monolith outcasts to eavesdrop on private Monolith conversations that can not be read and recorded with conventional means. It is compact and portable, with the ability to decode encrypted transmissions. A valuable tool for someone looking to gather intelligence in the northern-most parts of the Zone.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_bm16_ohotnik">
		<text>Hunter's BM-16 Shotgun</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_bm16_ohotnik_descr">
		<text>An old BM-16 shotgun marked with Hunter's personal insignia. It is a reliable double-barrel shotgun, favored for its simplicity and stopping power. The weapon shows signs of extensive use but seems to be functional.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="pda_dragun_name">
		<text>Scar's PDA</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pda_dragun_desc">
		<text>A functional PDA with low battery. It has severe scratches on the plastic exterior and on the screen. There are a number of entries stored. One of those seems to stand out: "Strider has assembled a new group to fight the Monolith. Rumor has it that among his men are former members of Lebedev's strike team." This device contains valuable insights into Scar's movements and plans, crucial for those tracking Monolith's activities.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="bar_case_name">
		<text>Heavy Briefcase</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_case_desc">
		<text>A heavy hardcover case with moderate scratches and dents on its exterior. It has a reinforced shell to protect its contents. The case likely contains items of value to Rostok's barman. Delivering this case is crucial for completing a high-priority trade or barter agreement.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="cs_anom_pribor_name">
		<text>Anomalous Activity Scanner</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cs_anom_pribor_desc">
		<text>An advanced scanner device for studying fields of interest to researchers in the Zone. The device uses a number of experimental components to scan anomalous formations. It can record raw data to an internal drive or transmit it to a preconfigured destination over short distances via radio. Models like it are most commonly used by members of Clear Sky.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="cs_informer_pda_name">
		<text>Crutch's PDA</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cs_informer_pda_desc">
		<text>A functional PDA in good condition, with some smudges of dirt on the plastic case. It appears to contain encrypted information related to the Clear Sky faction. The data presumably holds value to certain parties looking to gain insight on communications or strategic plans of Clear Sky.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="crazy_stalker_flash_name">
		<text>Madman's Flash Drive</text>
	</string>
	<string id="crazy_stalker_flash_desc">
		<text>A common flash drive holding encrypted information, likely owned by a stalker called "Madman". It has some scratches and signs of use on the plastic case and contacts. The nature of its contents are unknown but may be of value to interested parties.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="escape_docs_name">
		<text>Roadblock Documents</text>
	</string>
	<string id="escape_docs_desc">
		<text>A binder of what appears to be a military expedition report from the northern part of the Zone. It details troop movements, encounters with anomalies, and strategic positions. These documents may be valuable to certain parties looking into military activities or planning counter-operations. The folder has some light smudges and water damage on the outside but the papers inside are in good condition.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_voen_scaner">
		<text>Anomalous Activity Scanner</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_voen_scaner_desc">
		<text>An advanced device for the measurement of anomalous activity, originally designed for military personnel and members of scientific research groups for field work. Each scanner is protected by a unique code that encrypts all recorded data, limiting its use to authorized personnel. It contains a number of components for scanning and analysis of anomalous fields and formations found in the exclusion zone. This device is highly advanced but of little value to traders due to its security measures.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] quest item\n
		</text>
	</string>

</string_table>